<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...759..145H</bibcode>
			<title>Constraints on the Ubiquity of Coronal X-Ray Cycles</title>
			<authors>Hoffman, John; Gnther, Hans M.; Wright, Nicholas J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 759, Issue 2, article id. 145, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>11/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...759..145H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.490..323H</bibcode>
			<title>The exoplanet next door</title>
			<authors>Hand, Eric</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 490, Issue 7420, pp. 323 (2012).</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.490..323H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....144...64D</bibcode>
			<title>The Solar Neighborhood. XXVIII. The Multiplicity Fraction of Nearby Stars from 5 to 70 AU and the Brown Dwarf Desert around M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Dieterich, Sergio B.; Henry, Todd J.; Golimowski, David A.; Krist, John E.; Tanner, Angelle M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 144, Issue 2, article id. 64, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;19&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....144...64D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...753..156K</bibcode>
			<title>Further Defining Spectral Type "Y" and Exploring the Low-mass End of the Field Brown Dwarf Mass Function</title>
			<authors>Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Gelino, Christopher R.; Cushing, Michael C.; Mace, Gregory N.; Griffith, Roger L.; Skrutskie, Michael F.; Marsh, Kenneth A.; Wright, Edward L.; Eisenhardt, Peter R.; McLean, Ian S.; Mainzer, Amanda K.; Burgasser, Adam J.; Tinney, C. G.; Parker, Stephen; Salter, Graeme</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 753, Issue 2, article id. 156, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;38&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...753..156K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...753...76W</bibcode>
			<title>The Coronal Abundance Anomalies of M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Wood, Brian E.; Laming, J. Martin; Karovska, Margarita</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 753, Issue 1, article id. 76, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...753...76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...543A..84R</bibcode>
			<title>Coronal activity cycles in nearby G and K stars. XMM-Newton monitoring of 61 Cygni and alpha Centauri</title>
			<authors>Robrade, J.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Favata, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 543, id.A84, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...543A..84R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...542A..84D</bibcode>
			<title>Accurate and homogeneous abundance patterns in solar-type stars of the solar neighbourhood: a chemo-chronological analysis</title>
			<authors>da Silva, R.; Porto de Mello, G. F.; Milone, A. C.; da Silva, L.; Ribeiro, L. S.; Rocha-Pinto, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 542, id.A84, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;26&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...542A..84D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.1241F</bibcode>
			<title>Oscillations in the habitable zone around alpha Centauri B</title>
			<authors>Forgan, Duncan</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 2, pp. 1241-1249.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.1241F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJS..199....8G</bibcode>
			<title>A Compilation of Interstellar Column Densities</title>
			<authors>Gudennavar, S. B.; Bubbly, S. G.; Preethi, K.; Murthy, Jayant</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 199, Issue 1, article id. 8, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJS..199....8G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..63R</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating stellar mean density through seismic inversions</title>
			<authors>Reese, D. R.; Marques, J. P.; Goupil, M. J.; Thompson, M. J.; Deheuvels, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A63, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;18&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..63R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.419L..34M</bibcode>
			<title>Assessing the accuracy of the surface gravity determination in late-type stars with solar-like pulsators</title>
			<authors>Morel, Thierry; Miglio, Andrea</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 419, Issue 1, pp. L34-L38.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.419L..34M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.147H</bibcode>
			<title>Optimizing exoplanet transit searches around low-mass stars with inclination constraints</title>
			<authors>Herrero, E.; Ribas, I.; Jordi, C.; Guinan, E. F.; Engle, S. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A147, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...537A.147H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.491..207D</bibcode>
			<title>An Earth-mass planet orbiting {alf} Centauri B.</title>
			<authors>Dumusque, X.; Pepe, F.; Lovis, C.; Segransan, D.; Sahlmann, J.; Benz, W.; Bouchy, F.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, 491, 207-211 (2012)</journal>
			<date>0/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.491..207D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.491..200H</bibcode>
			<title>Meet our closest neighbour.</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, A. P.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, 491, 200-201 (2012)</journal>
			<date>0/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.491..200H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011SerAJ.183....1J</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomical Optical Interferometry. II. Astrophysical Results</title>
			<authors>Jankov, S.</authors>
			<journal>Serbian Astronomical Journal, vol. 183, pp. 1-35</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011SerAJ.183....1J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418.1272J</bibcode>
			<title>Effect of different stellar galactic environments on planetary discs - I. The solar neighbourhood and the birth cloud of the Sun</title>
			<authors>Jimnez-Torres, Juan J.; Pichardo, Barbara; Lake, George; Throop, Henry</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 418, Issue 2, pp. 1272-1284.</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418.1272J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..161W</bibcode>
			<title>Calculating Asteroseismic Diagrams for Solar-like Oscillations</title>
			<authors>White, Timothy R.; Bedding, Timothy R.; Stello, Dennis; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Huber, Daniel; Kjeldsen, Hans</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 161, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..161W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...48W</bibcode>
			<title>The Stellar-activity-Rotation Relationship and the Evolution of Stellar Dynamos</title>
			<authors>Wright, Nicholas J.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 48, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...48W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742L...3W</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismic Diagrams from a Survey of Solar-like Oscillations with Kepler</title>
			<authors>White, Timothy R.; Bedding, Timothy R.; Stello, Dennis; Appourchaux, Thierry; Ballot, Jrme; Benomar, Othman; Bonanno, Alfio; Broomhall, Anne-Marie; Campante, Tiago L.; Chaplin, William J.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Corsaro, Enrico; Dogan, Glnur; Elsworth, Yvonne P.; Fletcher, Stephen T.; Garca, Rafael A.; Gaulme, Patrick; Handberg, Rasmus; Hekker, Saskia; Huber, Daniel; Karoff, Christoffer; Kjeldsen, Hans; Mathur, Savita; Mosser, Benoit; Monteiro, Mario J. P. F. G.; Rgulo, Clara; Salabert, David; Silva Aguirre, Victor; Thompson, Michael J.; Verner, Graham; Morris, Robert L.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Seader, Shawn E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. L3, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742L...3W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...741...54C</bibcode>
			<title>Testing a Predictive Theoretical Model for the Mass Loss Rates of Cool Stars</title>
			<authors>Cranmer, Steven R.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 741, Issue 1, article id. 54, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;23&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...741...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A..17B</bibcode>
			<title>Bisectors of the HARPS cross-correlation function. The dependence on stellar atmospheric parameters</title>
			<authors>Bastrk, .; Dall, T. H.; Collet, R.; Lo Curto, G.; Selam, S. O.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A17, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A..17B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740L...2S</bibcode>
			<title>Constructing a One-solar-mass Evolutionary Sequence Using Asteroseismic Data from Kepler</title>
			<authors>Silva Aguirre, V.; Chaplin, W. J.; Ballot, J.; Basu, S.; Bedding, T. R.; Serenelli, A. M.; Verner, G. A.; Miglio, A.; Monteiro, M. J. P. F. G.; Weiss, A.; Appourchaux, T.; Bonanno, A.; Broomhall, A. M.; Bruntt, H.; Campante, T. L.; Casagrande, L.; Corsaro, E.; Elsworth, Y.; Garca, R. A.; Gaulme, P.; Handberg, R.; Hekker, S.; Huber, D.; Karoff, C.; Mathur, S.; Mosser, B.; Salabert, D.; Schnrich, R.; Sousa, S. G.; Stello, D.; White, T. R.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Gilliland, R. L.; Kawaler, S. D.; Kjeldsen, H.; Houdek, G.; Metcalfe, T. S.; Molenda-Z akowicz, J.; Thompson, M. J.; Caldwell, D. A.; Christiansen, J. L.; Wohler, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. L2, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740L...2S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534L...3B</bibcode>
			<title>The diameter of the CoRoT target HD 49933. Combining the 3D limb darkening, asteroseismology, and interferometry</title>
			<authors>Bigot, L.; Mourard, D.; Berio, P.; Thvenin, F.; Ligi, R.; Tallon-Bosc, I.; Chesneau, O.; Delaa, O.; Nardetto, N.; Perraut, K.; Stee, Ph.; Boyajian, T.; Morel, P.; Pichon, B.; Kervella, P.; Schmider, F. X.; McAlister, H.; Ten Brummelaar, T.; Ridgway, S. T.; Sturmann, J.; Sturmann, L.; Turner, N.; Farrington, C.; Goldfinger, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.L3, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;4&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534L...3B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534A..58P</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for Earth-like planets in the habitable zone. I. Very low-mass planets around HD 20794, HD 85512, and HD 192310</title>
			<authors>Pepe, F.; Lovis, C.; Sgransan, D.; Benz, W.; Bouchy, F.; Dumusque, X.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.A58, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534A..58P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...81W</bibcode>
			<title>The Frequency of Low-mass Exoplanets. III. Toward eta&amp;oplus; at Short Periods</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. P.; O'Toole, Simon J.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Bailey, J.; Horner, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 81, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...81W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A...6S</bibcode>
			<title>Estimation of the XUV radiation onto close planets and their evaporation</title>
			<authors>Sanz-Forcada, J.; Micela, G.; Ribas, I.; Pollock, A. M. T.; Eiroa, C.; Velasco, A.; Solano, E.; Garca-lvarez, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A6, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;18&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A...6S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A...7G</bibcode>
			<title>Time evolution of high-energy emissions of low-mass stars. I. Age determination using stellar chronology with white dwarfs in wide binaries</title>
			<authors>Garcs, A.; Cataln, S.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A7, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A...7G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413.2218D</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar rotation in the Hyades and Praesepe: gyrochronology and braking time-scale</title>
			<authors>Delorme, P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Rostron, J.; Lister, T. A.; Norton, A. J.; Pollacco, D.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 413, Issue 3, pp. 2218-2234.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.413.2218D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Sci...332..213C</bibcode>
			<title>Ensemble Asteroseismology of Solar-Type Stars with the NASA Kepler Mission</title>
			<authors>Chaplin, W. J.; Kjeldsen, H.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Basu, S.; Miglio, A.; Appourchaux, T.; Bedding, T. R.; Elsworth, Y.; Garca, R. A.; Gilliland, R. L.; Girardi, L.; Houdek, G.; Karoff, C.; Kawaler, S. D.; Metcalfe, T. S.; Molenda-Zakowicz, J.; Monteiro, M. J. P. F. G.; Thompson, M. J.; Verner, G. A.; Ballot, J.; Bonanno, A.; Brando, I. M.; Broomhall, A.-M.; Bruntt, H.; Campante, T. L.; Corsaro, E.; Creevey, O. L.; Dogan, G.; Esch, L.; Gai, N.; Gaulme, P.; Hale, S. J.; Handberg, R.; Hekker, S.; Huber, D.; Jimnez, A.; Mathur, S.; Mazumdar, A.; Mosser, B.; New, R.; Pinsonneault, M. H.; Pricopi, D.; Quirion, P.-O.; R gulo, C.; Salabert, D.; Serenelli, A. M.; Silva Aguirre, V.; Sousa, S. G.; Stello, D.; Stevens, I. R.; Suran, M. D.; Uytterhoeven, K.; White, T. R.; Borucki, W. J.; Brown, T. M.; Jenkins, J. M.; Kinemuchi, K.; Van Cleve, J.; Klaus, T. C.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 332, Issue 6026, pp. 213- (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Sci...332..213C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.2311F</bibcode>
			<title>BESO chelle spectroscopy of solar-type stars at Cerro Armazones</title>
			<authors>Fuhrmann, K.; Chini, R.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Lemke, R.; Murphy, M.; Seifert, W.; Stahl, O.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 4, pp. 2311-2318.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.2311F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..82D</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary detection limits taking into account stellar noise. II. Effect of stellar spot groups on radial-velocities</title>
			<authors>Dumusque, X.; Santos, N. C.; Udry, S.; Lovis, C.; Bonfils, X.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A82, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..82D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..138H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-26b: A Low-density Neptune-mass Planet Transiting a K Star</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Kipping, D. M.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Quinn, S. N.; Buchhave, L. A.; Bky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 138, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727..102W</bibcode>
			<title>On the Frequency of Jupiter Analogs</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Tinney, C. G.; O'Toole, Simon J.; Jones, H. R. A.; Butler, R. P.; Carter, B. D.; Bailey, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 102, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727..102W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A..91F</bibcode>
			<title>Generation of longitudinal flux tube waves in theoretical main-sequence stars: effects of model parameters</title>
			<authors>Fawzy, D. E.; Cuntz, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A91, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A..91F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A..35T</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismic modelling of the metal-poor star tau Ceti</title>
			<authors>Tang, Y. K.; Gai, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A35, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A..35T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A.140D</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary detection limits taking into account stellar noise. I. Observational strategies to reduce stellar oscillation and granulation effects</title>
			<authors>Dumusque, X.; Udry, S.; Lovis, C.; Santos, N. C.; Monteiro, M. J. P. F. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A140, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A.140D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.409..873Y</bibcode>
			<title>The effects of stellar population synthesis on the distributions of the asteroseismic observables numax and Deltanu of red-clump stars</title>
			<authors>Yang, Wuming; Meng, Xiangcun; Li, Zhongmu</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 409, Issue 2, pp. 873-879.</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.409..873Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.2176Q</bibcode>
			<title>Automatic Determination of Stellar Parameters Via Asteroseismology of Stochastically Oscillating Stars: Comparison with Direct Measurements</title>
			<authors>Quirion, Pierre-Olivier; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Arentoft, Torben</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 2176-2189 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.2176Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...524A..47G</bibcode>
			<title>HD 46375: seismic and spectropolarimetric analysis of a young Sun hosting a Saturn-like planet</title>
			<authors>Gaulme, P.; Deheuvels, S.; Weiss, W. W.; Mosser, B.; Moutou, C.; Bruntt, H.; Donati, J.-F.; Vannier, M.; Guillot, T.; Appourchaux, T.; Michel, E.; Auvergne, M.; Samadi, R.; Baudin, F.; Catala, C.; Baglin, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 524, id.A47, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...524A..47G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723.1607H</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of Red Giants from the First Four Months of Kepler Data: Global Oscillation Parameters for 800 Stars</title>
			<authors>Huber, D.; Bedding, T. R.; Stello, D.; Mosser, B.; Mathur, S.; Kallinger, T.; Hekker, S.; Elsworth, Y. P.; Buzasi, D. L.; De Ridder, J.; Gilliland, R. L.; Kjeldsen, H.; Chaplin, W. J.; Garca, R. A.; Hale, S. J.; Preston, H. L.; White, T. R.; Borucki, W. J.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Clarke, B. D.; Jenkins, J. M.; Koch, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 2, pp. 1607-1617 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723.1607H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..54D</bibcode>
			<title>Core properties of alpha Centauri A using asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>de Meulenaer, P.; Carrier, F.; Miglio, A.; Bedding, T. R.; Campante, T. L.; Eggenberger, P.; Kjeldsen, H.; Montalbn, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A54, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..54D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722.1854W</bibcode>
			<title>The Frequency of Low-mass Exoplanets. II. The "Period Valley"</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; O'Toole, Simon J.; Jones, H. R. A.; Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. P.; Carter, B. D.; Bailey, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 2, pp. 1854-1863 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722.1854W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722..343D</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray, FUV, and UV Observations of alpha Centauri B: Determination of Long-term Magnetic Activity Cycle and Rotation Period</title>
			<authors>DeWarf, L. E.; Datin, K. M.; Guinan, E. F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. 343-357 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722..343D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..12M</bibcode>
			<title>A spectroscopy study of nearby late-type stars, possible members of stellar kinematic groups</title>
			<authors>Maldonado, J.; Martnez-Arniz, R. M.; Eiroa, C.; Montes, D.; Montesinos, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A12, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;40&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..12M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720..357S</bibcode>
			<title>The Synergy of Direct Imaging and Astrometry for Orbit Determination of Exo-Earths</title>
			<authors>Shao, Michael; Catanzarite, Joseph; Pan, Xiaopei</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 1, pp. 357-367 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720..357S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..79M</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric activity and rotation of FGK stars in the solar vicinity. An estimation of the radial velocity jitter</title>
			<authors>Martnez-Arniz, R.; Maldonado, J.; Montes, D.; Eiroa, C.; Montesinos, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A79, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..79M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A..51B</bibcode>
			<title>Improved stellar parameters of CoRoT-7. A star hosting two super Earths</title>
			<authors>Bruntt, H.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; Alonso, R.; Bouchy, F.; Hatzes, A.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A51, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A..51B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62.1117A</bibcode>
			<title>Oscillations in G-Type Giants</title>
			<authors>Ando, Hiroyasu; Tsuboi, Yusuke; Kambe, Eiji; Sato, Bun'ei</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.4, pp.1117--1126</journal>
			<date>8/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62.1117A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.1907B</bibcode>
			<title>Accurate fundamental parameters for 23 bright solar-type stars</title>
			<authors>Bruntt, H.; Bedding, T. R.; Quirion, P.-O.; Lo Curto, G.; Carrier, F.; Smalley, B.; Dall, T. H.; Arentoft, T.; Bazot, M.; Butler, R. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 1907-1923.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.1907B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ChA&amp;A..34..277X</bibcode>
			<title>The V-band Empirical Mass-luminosity Relation for Main Sequence Stars</title>
			<authors>Xia, Fang; Fu, Yan-Ning</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 34, Issue 3, p. 277-287.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ChA%26A..34..277X</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...517A..88W</bibcode>
			<title>Rotational velocities of nearby young stars</title>
			<authors>Weise, P.; Launhardt, R.; Setiawan, J.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 517, id.A88, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;17&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...517A..88W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..28V</bibcode>
			<title>Three editions of the star catalogue of Tycho Brahe. Machine-readable versions and comparison with the modern Hipparcos Catalogue&lt;xref ref-type="fn" rid="FN1"&gt;</title>
			<authors>Verbunt, F.; van Gent, R. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A28, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;24&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..28V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...515A.111S</bibcode>
			<title>The PASTEL catalogue of stellar parameters</title>
			<authors>Soubiran, C.; Le Campion, J.-F.; Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Caillo, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 515, id.A111, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...515A.111S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..122B</bibcode>
			<title>New Completeness Methods for Estimating Exoplanet Discoveries by Direct Detection</title>
			<authors>Brown, Robert A.; Soummer, Rmi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 122-131 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..122B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010NewA...15..367Y</bibcode>
			<title>Models of mu Her with asteroseismic constraints</title>
			<authors>Yang, Wuming; Meng, Xiangcun</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 15, Issue 4, p. 367-372.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010NewA...15..367Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.1089P</bibcode>
			<title>Target selection for the SUNS and DEBRIS surveys for debris discs in the solar neighbourhood</title>
			<authors>Phillips, N. M.; Greaves, J. S.; Dent, W. R. F.; Matthews, B. C.; Holland, W. S.; Wyatt, M. C.; Sibthorpe, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 3, pp. 1089-1101.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.1089P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.176B</bibcode>
			<title>Solar-like Oscillations in Low-luminosity Red Giants: First Results from Kepler</title>
			<authors>Bedding, T. R.; Huber, D.; Stello, D.; Elsworth, Y. P.; Hekker, S.; Kallinger, T.; Mathur, S.; Mosser, B.; Preston, H. L.; Ballot, J.; Barban, C.; Broomhall, A. M.; Buzasi, D. L.; Chaplin, W. J.; Garca, R. A.; Gruberbauer, M.; Hale, S. J.; De Ridder, J.; Frandsen, S.; Borucki, W. J.; Brown, T.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Gilliland, R. L.; Jenkins, J. M.; Kjeldsen, H.; Koch, D.; Belkacem, K.; Bildsten, L.; Bruntt, H.; Campante, T. L.; Deheuvels, S.; Derekas, A.; Dupret, M.-A.; Goupil, M.-J.; Hatzes, A.; Houdek, G.; Ireland, M. J.; Jiang, C.; Karoff, C.; Kiss, L. L.; Lebreton, Y.; Miglio, A.; Montalbn, J.; Noels, A.; Roxburgh, I. W.; Sangaralingam, V.; Stevens, I. R.; Suran, M. D.; Tarrant, N. J.; Weiss, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L176-L181 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.176B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..935B</bibcode>
			<title>A Multi-Site Campaign to Measure Solar-Like Oscillations in Procyon. II. Mode Frequencies</title>
			<authors>Bedding, Timothy R.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Campante, Tiago L.; Appourchaux, Thierry; Bonanno, Alfio; Chaplin, William J.; Garcia, Rafael A.; Martic, Milena; Mosser, Benoit; Butler, R. Paul; Bruntt, Hans; Kiss, Lszl L.; O'Toole, Simon J.; Kambe, Eiji; Ando, Hiroyasu; Izumiura, Hideyuki; Sato, Bun'ei; Hartmann, Michael; Hatzes, Artie; Barban, Caroline; Berthomieu, Gabrielle; Michel, Eric; Provost, Janine; Turck-Chize, Sylvaine; Lebrun, Jean-Claude; Schmitt, Jerome; Bertaux, Jean-Loup; Benatti, Serena; Claudi, Riccardo U.; Cosentino, Rosario; Leccia, Silvio; Frandsen, Sren; Brogaard, Karsten; Glowienka, Lars; Grundahl, Frank; Stempels, Eric; Arentoft, Torben; Bazot, Michal; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Dall, Thomas H.; Karoff, Christoffer; Lundgreen-Nielsen, Jens; Carrier, Fabien; Eggenberger, Patrick; Sosnowska, Danuta; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Endl, Michael; Metcalfe, Travis S.; Hekker, Saskia; Reffert, Sabine</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 935-949 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..935B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403L..64P</bibcode>
			<title>Planetesimal collisions in binary systems</title>
			<authors>Paardekooper, S.-J.; Leinhardt, Z. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 403, Issue 1, pp. L64-L68.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403L..64P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..54C</bibcode>
			<title>An absolutely calibrated Teff scale from the infrared flux method. Dwarfs and subgiants</title>
			<authors>Casagrande, L.; Ramrez, I.; Melndez, J.; Bessell, M.; Asplund, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A54, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;22&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L..21C</bibcode>
			<title>Weak microlensing</title>
			<authors>Coles, Jonathan; Saha, Prasenjit; Schmid, Hans Martin</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L21-L24.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L..21C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....139..743T</bibcode>
			<title>Speckle Interferometry at the Blanco and SOAR Telescopes in 2008 and 2009</title>
			<authors>Tokovinin, Andrei; Mason, Brian D.; Hartkopf, William I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 139, Issue 2, pp. 743-756 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....139..743T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010CoAst.161....3B</bibcode>
			<title>Scaled oscillation frequencies and chelle diagrams as a tool for comparative asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>Bedding, T. R.; Kjeldsen, H.</authors>
			<journal>Communications in Asteroseismology, Vol.161, p. 3-15</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010CoAst.161....3B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..535B</bibcode>
			<title>Radii of Rapidly Rotating Stars, with Application to Transiting-Planet Hosts</title>
			<authors>Brown, Timothy M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 535-545 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..535B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708.1566X</bibcode>
			<title>Planetesimal Accretion in Binary Systems: Could Planets Form Around alpha Centauri B?</title>
			<authors>Xie, Ji-Wei; Zhou, Ji-Lin; Ge, Jian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 2, pp. 1566-1578 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708.1566X</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A..77K</bibcode>
			<title>Oscillating red giants in the CoRoT exofield: asteroseismic mass and radius determination</title>
			<authors>Kallinger, T.; Weiss, W. W.; Barban, C.; Baudin, F.; Cameron, C.; Carrier, F.; De Ridder, J.; Goupil, M.-J.; Gruberbauer, M.; Hatzes, A.; Hekker, S.; Samadi, R.; Deleuil, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A77</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A..77K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.400.1936P</bibcode>
			<title>Outward migration of terrestrial embryos in binary systems</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Wyatt, Mark C.; Thbault, Philippe</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 400, Issue 4, pp. 1936-1944.</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.400.1936P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.400L..80S</bibcode>
			<title>The relation between Deltanu and numax for solar-like oscillations</title>
			<authors>Stello, D.; Chaplin, W. J.; Basu, S.; Elsworth, Y.; Bedding, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 400, Issue 1, pp. L80-L84.</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.400L..80S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.399..914K</bibcode>
			<title>Sounding stellar cycles with Kepler - I. Strategy for selecting targets</title>
			<authors>Karoff, C.; Metcalfe, T. S.; Chaplin, W. J.; Elsworth, Y.; Kjeldsen, H.; Arentoft, T.; Buzasi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 399, Issue 2, pp. 914-923.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.399..914K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.399..888M</bibcode>
			<title>The chromospheric emission of solar-type stars in the young open clusters IC 2391 and IC 2602</title>
			<authors>Marsden, S. C.; Carter, B. D.; Donati, J.-F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 399, Issue 2, pp. 888-905.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.399..888M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1495V</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric changes in K stars with activity</title>
			<authors>Vieytes, Mariela C.; Mauas, Pablo J. D.; Daz, Rodrigo F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 3, pp. 1495-1504.</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1495V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..184..138H</bibcode>
			<title>XID II: Statistical Cross-Association of ROSAT Bright Source Catalog X-ray Sources with 2MASS Point Source Catalog Near-Infrared Sources</title>
			<authors>Haakonsen, Christian Bernt; Rutledge, Robert E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 184, Issue 1, pp. 138-151 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..184..138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702..672C</bibcode>
			<title>Direct Detection of Planets Orbiting Large Angular Diameter Stars: Sensitivity of an Internally Occulting Space-based Coronagraph</title>
			<authors>Crepp, Justin R.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Ge, Jian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 1, pp. 672-679 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702..672C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.1732O</bibcode>
			<title>The Frequency of Low-Mass Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>O'Toole, S. J.; Jones, H. R. A.; Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. P.; Marcy, G. W.; Carter, B.; Bailey, J.; Wittenmyer, R. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 1732-1741 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.1732O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..373M</bibcode>
			<title>A Stellar Model-fitting Pipeline for Asteroseismic Data from the Kepler Mission</title>
			<authors>Metcalfe, T. S.; Creevey, O. L.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 373-382 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..373M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501.1087R</bibcode>
			<title>Granulation in K-type dwarf stars. II. Hydrodynamic simulations and 3D spectrum synthesis</title>
			<authors>Ramrez, I.; Allende Prieto, C.; Koesterke, L.; Lambert, D. L.; Asplund, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1087-1101</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501.1087R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.2066X</bibcode>
			<title>Planetesimal Accretion in Binary Systems: Role of the Companion's Orbital Inclination</title>
			<authors>Xie, Ji-Wei; Zhou, Ji-Lin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 2066-2074 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.2066X</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500L..21C</bibcode>
			<title>Mode lifetimes of stellar oscillations. Implications for asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>Chaplin, W. J.; Houdek, G.; Karoff, C.; Elsworth, Y.; New, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 2, 2009, pp.L21-L24</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500L..21C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1931A</bibcode>
			<title>The Cycles of alpha Centauri</title>
			<authors>Ayres, Thomas R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1931-1949 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1931A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.393L..21T</bibcode>
			<title>Planet formation in the habitable zone of alpha Centauri B</title>
			<authors>Thbault, P.; Marzari, F.; Scholl, H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 393, Issue 1, pp. L21-L25.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.393L..21T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.393..245N</bibcode>
			<title>The radius and other fundamental parameters of the F9V star beta Virginis</title>
			<authors>North, J. R.; Davis, J.; Robertson, J. G.; Bedding, T. R.; Bruntt, H.; Ireland, M. J.; Jacob, A. P.; Lacour, S.; O'Byrne, J. W.; Owens, S. M.; Stello, D.; Tango, W. J.; Tuthill, P. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 393, Issue 1, pp. 245-252.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.393..245N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692..531C</bibcode>
			<title>Excitation and Damping of p-Mode Oscillations of alpha Cen B</title>
			<authors>Chaplin, W. J.; Houdek, G.; Elsworth, Y.; New, R.; Bedding, T. R.; Kjeldsen, H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. 531-537 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692..531C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...495..287B</bibcode>
			<title>Long-term chromospheric activity of non-eclipsing RS CVn-type stars</title>
			<authors>Buccino, A. P.; Mauas, P. J. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 495, Issue 1, 2009, pp.287-295</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...495..287B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...494..237T</bibcode>
			<title>Solar-like oscillations in the G8 V star tau Ceti</title>
			<authors>Teixeira, T. C.; Kjeldsen, H.; Bedding, T. R.; Bouchy, F.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Cunha, M. S.; Dall, T.; Frandsen, S.; Karoff, C.; Monteiro, M. J. P. F. G.; Pijpers, F. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 494, Issue 1, 2009, pp.237-242</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...494..237T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493.1099S</bibcode>
			<title>Ca II HK emission in rapidly rotating stars. Evidence for an onset of the solar-type dynamo</title>
			<authors>Schrder, C.; Reiners, A.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1099-1107</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493.1099S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MmSAI..80..180C</bibcode>
			<title>Hints from chromospheric activity to constrain stellar modelling</title>
			<authors>Cardini, D.; Di Mauro, M. P.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v.80, p.180 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MmSAI..80..180C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008RMxAC..34...91A</bibcode>
			<title>Circumstellar and Circumbinary Disks in Eccentric Stellar Binaries</title>
			<authors>Aguilar, L. A.; Pichardo, B. S.; Sparke, L. S.</authors>
			<journal>IV Reunin sobre Astronoma Dinmica en Latino Amrica (Eds. C. Allen, A. Ruelas, &amp; R. Teixeira) Revista Mexicana de Astronoma y Astrofsica (Serie de Conferencias) Vol. 34, pp. 91-97 (2008) (http://www.astroscu.unam.mx/~rmaa/)</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008RMxAC..34...91A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...491..855K</bibcode>
			<title>The angular sizes of dwarf stars and subgiants. Non-linear surface brightness relations in BVR_cIc from interferometry</title>
			<authors>Kervella, P.; Fouqu, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 491, Issue 3, 2008, pp.855-858</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...491..855K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008NewA...13..541T</bibcode>
			<title>Seismic analysis of 70 Ophiuchi A: A new quantity proposed</title>
			<authors>Tang, Y. K.; Bi, S. L.; Gai, N.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 13, Issue 8, p. 541-548.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008NewA...13..541T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1264M</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Age Estimation for Solar-Type Dwarfs Using Activity-Rotation Diagnostics</title>
			<authors>Mamajek, Eric E.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1264-1293.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1264M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AJ....136.1810A</bibcode>
			<title>Chandra's Darkest Bright Star: not so Dark after All?</title>
			<authors>Ayres, Thomas R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 136, Issue 5, pp. 1810-1814 (2008).</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AJ....136.1810A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008Sci...322..558M</bibcode>
			<title>CoRoT Measures Solar-Like Oscillations and Granulation in Stars Hotter Than the Sun</title>
			<authors>Michel, Eric; Baglin, Annie; Auvergne, Michel; Catala, Claude; Samadi, Reza; Baudin, Frdric; Appourchaux, Thierry; Barban, Caroline; Weiss, Werner W.; Berthomieu, Gabrielle; Boumier, Patrick; Dupret, Marc-Antoine; Garcia, Rafael A.; Fridlund, Malcolm; Garrido, Rafael; Goupil, Marie-Jo; Kjeldsen, Hans; Lebreton, Yveline; Mosser, Benot; Grotsch-Noels, Arlette; Janot-Pacheco, Eduardo; Provost, Janine; Roxburgh, Ian W.; Thoul, Anne; Toutain, Thierry; Tiphne, Didier; Turck-Chieze, Sylvaine; Vauclair, Sylvie D.; Vauclair, Grard P.; Aerts, Conny; Alecian, Georges; Ballot, Jrme; Charpinet, Stphane; Hubert, Anne-Marie; Lignires, Franois; Mathias, Philippe; Monteiro, Mario J. P. F. G.; Neiner, Coralie; Poretti, Ennio; Renan de Medeiros, Jos; Ribas, Ignasi; Rieutord, Michel L.; Corts, Teodoro Roca; Zwintz, Konstanze</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 322, Issue 5901, pp. 558- (2008).</journal>
			<date>10/2008 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008Sci...322..558M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1162D</bibcode>
			<title>Recent FUSE Observations of Diffuse O VI Emission from the Interstellar Medium</title>
			<authors>Dixon, W. Van Dyke; Sankrit, Ravi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1162-1173.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1162D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AN....329..790J</bibcode>
			<title>The main sequence from F to K stars of the solar neighbourhood in SDSS colours</title>
			<authors>Just, A.; Jahrei, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.329, Issue 8, p.790</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AN....329..790J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...489..291S</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling the excitation of acoustic modes in alpha Centauri A</title>
			<authors>Samadi, R.; Belkacem, K.; Goupil, M. J.; Dupret, M.-A.; Kupka, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 489, Issue 1, 2008, pp.291-299</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...489..291S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..925T</bibcode>
			<title>Comparative statistics and origin of triple and quadruple stars</title>
			<authors>Tokovinin, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 2, pp. 925-938.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..925T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..869E</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of multiplicity among bright stellar systems</title>
			<authors>Eggleton, P. P.; Tokovinin, A. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 2, pp. 869-879.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..869E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488.1149E</bibcode>
			<title>Toward detection of terrestrial planets in the habitable zone of our closest neighbor: proxima Centauri</title>
			<authors>Endl, M.; Krster, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 3, 2008, pp.1149-1153</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488.1149E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..653P</bibcode>
			<title>The Alpha Centauri binary system. Atmospheric parameters and element abundances</title>
			<authors>Porto de Mello, G. F.; Lyra, W.; Keller, G. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.653-666</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..653P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.388.1528T</bibcode>
			<title>Planet formation in alpha Centauri A revisited: not so accretion friendly after all</title>
			<authors>Thbault, P.; Marzari, F.; Scholl, H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 388, Issue 4, pp. 1528-1536.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.388.1528T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.388.1143Y</bibcode>
			<title>On the structure of the Sun and alpha Centauri A and B in the light of seismic and non-seismic constraints</title>
			<authors>Yildiz, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 388, Issue 3, pp. 1143-1151.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.388.1143Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ChJAA...8..421T</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismic Analysis of alpha Cen B: Preliminary Tests of Effects of Rotation and Interior Magnetic Field in the Solar-like Star</title>
			<authors>Tang, Yan-Ke; Bi, Shao-Lan; Gai, Ning; Xu, Hua-Yin</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Journal of Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 8, Issue 4, pp. 421-432 (2008).</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ChJAA...8..421T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...683L.175K</bibcode>
			<title>Correcting Stellar Oscillation Frequencies for Near-Surface Effects</title>
			<authors>Kjeldsen, Hans; Bedding, Timothy R.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 683, Issue 2, pp. L175-L178.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...683L.175K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1370K</bibcode>
			<title>The Amplitude of Solar Oscillations Using Stellar Techniques</title>
			<authors>Kjeldsen, Hans; Bedding, Timothy R.; Arentoft, Torben; Butler, R. Paul; Dall, Thomas H.; Karoff, Christoffer; Kiss, Lszl L.; Tinney, C. G.; Chaplin, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1370-1375.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1370K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...487..595S</bibcode>
			<title>An extremely wide and very low-mass pair with common proper motion. Is it representative of a nearby halo stream?</title>
			<authors>Scholz, R.-D.; Kharchenko, N. V.; Lodieu, N.; McCaughrean, M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 487, Issue 2, 2008, pp.595-599</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...487..595S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...486..995R</bibcode>
			<title>Neon and oxygen in low activity stars: towards a coronal unification with the Sun</title>
			<authors>Robrade, J.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Favata, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 486, Issue 3, 2008, pp.995-1002</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...486..995R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...679.1582G</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and Detectability of Terrestrial Planets around alpha Centauri B</title>
			<authors>Guedes, J. M.; Rivera, E. J.; Davis, E.; Laughlin, G.; Quintana, E. V.; Fischer, D. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 679, Issue 2, pp. 1582-1587.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...679.1582G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AJ....135.2291L</bibcode>
			<title>Electron Density Diagnostic for Hot Plasmas in the Coronal Regime by Using B-Like Ions</title>
			<authors>Liang, G. Y.; Zhao, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 135, Issue 6, pp. 2291-2297 (2008).</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AJ....135.2291L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...483..903B</bibcode>
			<title>Mg II h+k emission lines as stellar activity indicators of main sequence F-K stars</title>
			<authors>Buccino, A. P.; Mauas, P. J. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 483, Issue 3, 2008, pp.903-910</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...483..903B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386..516O</bibcode>
			<title>The impact of stellar oscillations on doppler velocity planet searches</title>
			<authors>O'Toole, S. J.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 1, pp. 516-520.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386..516O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678L.121A</bibcode>
			<title>The Fainting of alpha Centauri A, Resolved</title>
			<authors>Ayres, Thomas R.; Judge, Philip G.; Saar, Steven H.; Schmitt, J rgen H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. L121-L124.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678L.121A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678L..73K</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence That Solar Flares Drive Global Oscillations in the Sun</title>
			<authors>Karoff, C.; Kjeldsen, H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 1, pp. L73-L76.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678L..73K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482..631E</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of 70 Ophiuchi AB including seismic constraints</title>
			<authors>Eggenberger, P.; Miglio, A.; Carrier, F.; Fernandes, J.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 2, 2008, pp.631-638</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482..631E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.385.1691N</bibcode>
			<title>The corona and upper transition region of &amp;epsilEridani</title>
			<authors>Ness, J.-U.; Jordan, C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 385, Issue 4, pp. 1691-1708.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.385.1691N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008JRASC.102...69G</bibcode>
			<title>Through My Eyepiece: Southward Bound</title>
			<authors>Gaherty, Geoff</authors>
			<journal>Journal of the Royal Astronomical Society of Canada, Vol. 102, Number 2, p.69</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008JRASC.102...69G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AN....329..206S</bibcode>
			<title>XMM-Newton: The next decade for cool star research</title>
			<authors>Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.329, Issue 2, p.206-209</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AN....329..206S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...478..497K</bibcode>
			<title>Nonradial p-modes in the G9.5 giant &amp;epsil Ophiuchi? Pulsation model fits to MOST photometry</title>
			<authors>Kallinger, T.; Guenther, D. B.; Matthews, J. M.; Weiss, W. W.; Huber, D.; Kuschnig, R.; Moffat, A. F. J.; Rucinski, S. M.; Sasselov, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 478, Issue 2, February I 2008, pp.497-505</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...478..497K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASP..120...38U</bibcode>
			<title>Taking the Measure of the Universe: Precision Astrometry with SIM PlanetQuest</title>
			<authors>Unwin, Stephen C.; Shao, Michael; Tanner, Angelle M.; Allen, Ronald J.; Beichman, Charles A.; Boboltz, David; Catanzarite, Joseph H.; Chaboyer, Brian C.; Ciardi, David R.; Edberg, Stephen J.; Fey, Alan L.; Fischer, Debra A.; Gelino, Christopher R.; Gould, Andrew P.; Grillmair, Carl; Henry, Todd J.; Johnston, Kathryn V.; Johnston, Kenneth J.; Jones, Dayton L.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Law, Nicholas M.; Majewski, Steven R.; Makarov, Valeri V.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Meier, David L.; Olling, Rob P.; Pan, Xiaopei; Patterson, Richard J.; Pitesky, Jo Eliza; Quirrenbach, Andreas; Shaklan, Stuart B.; Shaya, Edward J.; Strigari, Louis E.; Tomsick, John A.; Wehrle, Ann E.; Worthey, Guy</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 120, issue 863, pp.38-88</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASP..120...38U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008CoAst.152..131K</bibcode>
			<title>Exploring solar-type pulsation with BRITE</title>
			<authors>Kallinger, T.</authors>
			<journal>Communications in Asteroseismology, Vol.152, p. 131-139</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008CoAst.152..131K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..283R</bibcode>
			<title>The Structure of the Local Interstellar Medium. IV. Dynamics, Morphology, Physical Properties, and Implications of Cloud-Cloud Interactions</title>
			<authors>Redfield, Seth; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 283-314.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..283R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MmSAI..79..670B</bibcode>
			<title>Abundance analysis of alpha  Cen A: the 3D hydrodynamical approach.</title>
			<authors>Bigot, L.; Thvenin, F.; Kervella, P.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v.79, p.670 (2008)</journal>
			<date>0/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MmSAI..79..670B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.382.1516C</bibcode>
			<title>The helium abundance and DeltaY/DeltaZ in lower main-sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Casagrande, Luca; Flynn, Chris; Portinari, Laura; Girardi, Leo; Jimenez, Raul</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 382, Issue 4, pp. 1516-1540.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.382.1516C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.381.1001K</bibcode>
			<title>High-frequency modes in solar-like stars</title>
			<authors>Karoff, C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 381, Issue 3, pp. 1001-1008.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.381.1001K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1167B</bibcode>
			<title>Ages for Illustrative Field Stars Using Gyrochronology: Viability, Limitations, and Errors</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Sydney A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1167-1189.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1167B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;ARv..14..217C</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology and interferometry</title>
			<authors>Cunha, M. S.; Aerts, C.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Baglin, A.; Bigot, L.; Brown, T. M.; Catala, C.; Creevey, O. L.; Domiciano de Souza, A.; Eggenberger, P.; Garcia, P. J. V.; Grundahl, F.; Kervella, P.; Kurtz, D. W.; Mathias, P.; Miglio, A.; Monteiro, M. J. P. F. G.; Perrin, G.; Pijpers, F. P.; Pourbaix, D.; Quirrenbach, A.; Rousselet-Perraut, K.; Teixeira, T. C.; Thvenin, F.; Thompson, M. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomy and Astrophysics Review, Volume 14, Issue 3-4, pp. 217-360</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26ARv..14..217C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..243D</bibcode>
			<title>A near-infrared interferometric survey of debris disk stars. I. Probing the hot dust content around &amp;epsil Eridani and tau Ceti with CHARA/FLUOR</title>
			<authors>di Folco, E.; Absil, O.; Augereau, J.-C.; Mrand, A.; Coud du Foresto, V.; Thvenin, F.; Defrre, D.; Kervella, P.; ten Brummelaar, T. A.; McAlister, H. A.; Ridgway, S. T.; Sturmann, J.; Sturmann, L.; Turner, N. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 1, November III 2007, pp.243-250</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..243D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.381..669W</bibcode>
			<title>Elemental abundances of Galactic bulge planetary nebulae from optical recombination lines</title>
			<authors>Wang, W.; Liu, X.-W.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 381, Issue 2, pp. 669-701.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.381..669W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AJ....134.1089S</bibcode>
			<title>H-R Diagrams Based on the HD Stars in the Michigan Spectral Catalogue and the Hipparcos Catalog</title>
			<authors>Sowell, J. R.; Trippe, M.; Caballero-Nieves, S. M.; Houk, N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 134, Issue 3, pp. 1089-1102 (2007).</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AJ....134.1089S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...472..571Y</bibcode>
			<title>The frequency separations of stellar p-modes</title>
			<authors>Yang, W. M.; Bi, S. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 472, Issue 2, September III 2007, pp.571-576</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...472..571Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007NewA...12..435L</bibcode>
			<title>Soft X-ray emissions of Si IX in Procyon</title>
			<authors>Liang, Guiyun; Zhao, Gang</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 12, Issue 6, p. 435-440.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007NewA...12..435L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379L..16M</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismic signatures of stellar magnetic activity cycles</title>
			<authors>Metcalfe, T. S.; Dziembowski, W. A.; Judge, P. G.; Snow, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 379, Issue 1, pp. L16-L20.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379L..16M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.378.1007D</bibcode>
			<title>The NaI D resonance lines in main-sequence late-type stars</title>
			<authors>Daz, Rodrigo F.; Cincunegui, Carolina; Mauas, Pablo J. D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 378, Issue 3, pp. 1007-1018.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.378.1007D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...663.1315B</bibcode>
			<title>Solar-like Oscillations in the G2 Subgiant beta Hydri from Dual-Site Observations</title>
			<authors>Bedding, Timothy R.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Arentoft, Torben; Bouchy, Francois; Brandbyge, Jacob; Brewer, Brendon J.; Butler, R. Paul; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Dall, Thomas; Frandsen, Sren; Karoff, Christoffer; Kiss, Lszl L.; Monteiro, Mario J. P. F. G.; Pijpers, Frank P.; Teixeira, Teresa C.; Tinney, C. G.; Baldry, Ivan K.; Carrier, Fabien; O'Toole, Simon J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 663, Issue 2, pp. 1315-1324.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...663.1315B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...470..295B</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of alpha Centauri A. Evidence of rotational splitting</title>
			<authors>Bazot, M.; Bouchy, F.; Kjeldsen, H.; Charpinet, S.; Laymand, M.; Vauclair, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 470, Issue 1, July IV 2007, pp.295-302</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...470..295B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...469..309C</bibcode>
			<title>Halpha and the Ca II H and K lines as activity proxies for late-type stars</title>
			<authors>Cincunegui, C.; Daz, R. F.; Mauas, P. J. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 469, Issue 1, July I 2007, pp.309-317</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...469..309C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...468.1033B</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of solar-like oscillations in the red giant star &amp;epsil Ophiuchi by MOST spacebased photometry</title>
			<authors>Barban, C.; Matthews, J. M.; De Ridder, J.; Baudin, F.; Kuschnig, R.; Mazumdar, A.; Samadi, R.; Guenther, D. B.; Moffat, A. F. J.; Rucinski, S. M.; Sasselov, D.; Walker, G. A. H.; Weiss, W. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 468, Issue 3, 2007, pp.1033-1038</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...468.1033B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...468..721B</bibcode>
			<title>The frequency of planets in multiple systems</title>
			<authors>Bonavita, M.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 468, Issue 2, June III 2007, pp.721-729</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...468..721B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.377...17C</bibcode>
			<title>On prospects for sounding activity cycles of Sun-like stars with acoustic modes</title>
			<authors>Chaplin, W. J.; Elsworth, Y.; Houdek, G.; New, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 377, Issue 1, pp. 17-29.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.377...17C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..807Q</bibcode>
			<title>Terrestrial Planet Formation around Individual Stars within Binary Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Quintana, Elisa V.; Adams, Fred C.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Chambers, John E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 807-822.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..807Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007JRASC.101...68H</bibcode>
			<title>Deep-Sky Contemplations: The Great Rift and the Coal Sack</title>
			<authors>Hube, Doug; Finlay, Warren</authors>
			<journal>Journal of the Royal Astronomical Society of Canada, Vol. 101, Issue 2, p.68</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007JRASC.101...68H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...465..271R</bibcode>
			<title>Oxygen abundances in nearby stars. Clues to the formation and evolution of the Galactic disk</title>
			<authors>Ramrez, I.; Allende Prieto, C.; Lambert, D. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 465, Issue 1, April I 2007, pp.271-289</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...465..271R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...464..373K</bibcode>
			<title>Deep imaging survey of the environment of alpha Centauri. II. CCD imaging with the NTT-SUSI2 camera</title>
			<authors>Kervella, P.; Thvenin, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 464, Issue 1, March II 2007, pp.373-375</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...464..373K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.374.1264Y</bibcode>
			<title>Models of alpha Centauri A and B with and without seismic constraints: time dependence of the mixing-length parameter</title>
			<authors>Yildiz, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 374, Issue 4, pp. 1264-1270.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.374.1264Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJS..168..297T</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and Evolution of Nearby Stars with Planets. II. Physical Properties of ~1000 Cool Stars from the SPOCS Catalog</title>
			<authors>Takeda, Genya; Ford, Eric B.; Sills, Alison; Rasio, Frederic A.; Fischer, Debra A.; Valenti, Jeff A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 168, Issue 2, pp. 297-318.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJS..168..297T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...463..297S</bibcode>
			<title>Excitation of solar-like oscillations across the HR diagram</title>
			<authors>Samadi, R.; Georgobiani, D.; Trampedach, R.; Goupil, M. J.; Stein, R. F.; Nordlund, .</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 463, Issue 1, February III 2007, pp.297-308</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...463..297S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASP..119..127M</bibcode>
			<title>Duty Cycle of Doppler Ground-based Asteroseismic Observations</title>
			<authors>Mosser, Benot; Aristidi, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 119, Issue 851, pp. 127-133.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASP..119..127M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNSSA..66..244G</bibcode>
			<title>The discovery of the nearest star.</title>
			<authors>Glass, I. S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notes of the Astronomical Society of South Africa, Vol. 66, p. 244-262 (2007)</journal>
			<date>0/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNSSA..66..244G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..695T</bibcode>
			<title>Search for associations containing young stars (SACY). I. Sample and searching method</title>
			<authors>Torres, C. A. O.; Quast, G. R.; da Silva, L.; de La Reza, R.; Melo, C. H. F.; Sterzik, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 3, December IV 2006, pp.695-708</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..695T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...651.1126A</bibcode>
			<title>The Coronae of gamma Draconis</title>
			<authors>Ayres, Thomas R.; Brown, Alexander; Harper, Graham M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 651, Issue 2, pp. 1126-1129.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...651.1126A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132.1995W</bibcode>
			<title>Are Proxima and alpha Centauri Gravitationally Bound?</title>
			<authors>Wertheimer, Jeremy G.; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 5, pp. 1995-1997.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132.1995W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...459..669K</bibcode>
			<title>Deep imaging survey of the environment of alpha Centauri. I. Adaptive optics imaging of alpha Cen B with VLT-NACO</title>
			<authors>Kervella, P.; Thvenin, F.; Coud du Foresto, V.; Mignard, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 459, Issue 2, November IV 2006, pp.669-678</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...459..669K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132.1547L</bibcode>
			<title>Determinations of Temperature and Density for Solar-like Stars Using Si XI Soft X-Ray Emission Lines</title>
			<authors>Liang, G. Y.; Zhao, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 4, pp. 1547-1554.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132.1547L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...458L...1L</bibcode>
			<title>The coronal Ne/O abundance of alpha Centauri</title>
			<authors>Liefke, C.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 458, Issue 1, October IV 2006, pp.L1-L4</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...458L...1L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...647..558B</bibcode>
			<title>Solar-like Oscillations in the Metal-poor Subgiant nu Indi: Constraining the Mass and Age Using Asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>Bedding, Timothy R.; Butler, R. Paul; Carrier, Fabien; Bouchy, Francois; Brewer, Brendon J.; Eggenberger, Patrick; Grundahl, Frank; Kjeldsen, Hans; McCarthy, Chris; Nielsen, Tine Bjrn; Retter, Alon; Tinney, Christopher G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 647, Issue 1, pp. 558-563.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...647..558B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...647..328D</bibcode>
			<title>An Extended FUSE Survey of Diffuse O VI Emission in the Interstellar Medium</title>
			<authors>Dixon, W. Van Dyke; Sankrit, Ravi; Otte, Birgit</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 647, Issue 1, pp. 328-349.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...647..328D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132..371L</bibcode>
			<title>Coronal Density Diagnostics with Si X: Chandra LETGS Observations of Procyon, alpha Centauri A and B, Capella, and &amp;epsil Eridani</title>
			<authors>Liang, G. Y.; Zhao, G.; Shi, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 1, pp. 371-377.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132..371L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132..161G</bibcode>
			<title>Contributions to the Nearby Stars (NStars) Project: Spectroscopy of Stars Earlier than M0 within 40 pc-The Southern Sample</title>
			<authors>Gray, R. O.; Corbally, C. J.; Garrison, R. F.; McFadden, M. T.; Bubar, E. J.; McGahee, C. E.; O'Donoghue, A. A.; Knox, E. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 1, pp. 161-170.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132..161G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...449.1233D</bibcode>
			<title>Simulating observable comets. III. Real stellar perturbers of the Oort cloud and their output</title>
			<authors>Dybczynski, P. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 449, Issue 3, April III 2006, pp.1233-1242</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...449.1233D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...449..723G</bibcode>
			<title>Abundances of refractory elements in the atmospheres of stars with extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Gilli, G.; Israelian, G.; Ecuvillon, A.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 449, Issue 2, April II 2006, pp.723-736</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...449..723G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...449..293E</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling beta Virginis using seismological data</title>
			<authors>Eggenberger, P.; Carrier, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 449, Issue 1, April I 2006, pp.293-303</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...449..293E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...448..709S</bibcode>
			<title>Oscillation mode lifetimes in xi Hydrae: will strong mode damping limit asteroseismology of red giant stars?</title>
			<authors>Stello, D.; Kjeldsen, H.; Bedding, T. R.; Buzasi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 448, Issue 2, March III 2006, pp.709-715</journal>
			<date>3/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...448..709S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...446..635B</bibcode>
			<title>The limb darkening of alpha Centauri B. Matching 3D hydrodynamical models with interferometric measurements</title>
			<authors>Bigot, L.; Kervella, P.; Thvenin, F.; Sgransan, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 446, Issue 2, February I 2006, pp.635-641</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...446..635B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...445..633E</bibcode>
			<title>Oxygen abundances in planet-harbouring stars. Comparison of different abundance indicators</title>
			<authors>Ecuvillon, A.; Israelian, G.; Santos, N. C.; Shchukina, N. G.; Mayor, M.; Rebolo, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 445, Issue 2, January II 2006, pp.633-645</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...445..633E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MmSAI..77..472M</bibcode>
			<title>Evolution and seismology of alpha  Centauri.</title>
			<authors>Montalbn, J.; Miglio, A.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v.77, p.472 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MmSAI..77..472M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MmSAI..77..458G</bibcode>
			<title>SONG: Stellar Oscillations Network Group .  A global network of small telescopes for asteroseismology and planet searches.</title>
			<authors>Grundahl, F.; Kjeldsen, H.; Frandsen, S.; Andersen, M.; Bedding, T.; Arentoft, T.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v.77, p.458 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MmSAI..77..458G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MmSAI..77..451E</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of solar-type stars with CORALIE and HARPS . II: Observations and modelling of binary stars</title>
			<authors>Eggenberger, P.; Carrier, F.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v. 77, p.451 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MmSAI..77..451E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MmSAI..77..411T</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology and interferometry .</title>
			<authors>Thvenin, F.; Bigot, L.; Kervella, P.; Lopez, B.; Pichon, B.; Schmider, F.-X.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v.77, p.411 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MmSAI..77..411T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MmSAI..77..384B</bibcode>
			<title>Observing solar-like oscillations: recent results.</title>
			<authors>Bedding, Timothy R.; Kjeldsen, Hans</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v.77, p.384 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MmSAI..77..384B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MmSAI..77..326C</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of solar-type stars with CORALIE and HARPS . I: Observations and modelling of single stars</title>
			<authors>Carrier, F.; Eggenberger, P.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v.77, p.326 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MmSAI..77..326C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MmSAI..77..309E</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of solar-like oscillations and asteroseismic models including rotation .</title>
			<authors>Eggenberger, P.; Carrier, F.; Maeder, A.; Meynet, G.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v.77, p.309 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MmSAI..77..309E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...635.1281K</bibcode>
			<title>Solar-like Oscillations in alpha Centauri B</title>
			<authors>Kjeldsen, Hans; Bedding, Timothy R.; Butler, R. Paul; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Kiss, Laszlo L.; McCarthy, Chris; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Tinney, Christopher G.; Wright, Jason T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 635, Issue 2, pp. 1281-1290.</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...635.1281K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...634.1319F</bibcode>
			<title>Synthetic Lick Indices and Detection of alpha-enhanced Stars. III. F, G, and K Stars with [Fe/H] &gt; 0.00</title>
			<authors>Franchini, M.; Morossi, C.; Di Marcantonio, P.; Castelli, F.; Malagnini, M. L.; Chavez, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 634, Issue 2, pp. 1319-1335.</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...634.1319F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...444..549F</bibcode>
			<title>Fundamental parameters and granulation properties of Alpha Centauri A and B obtained from inversions of their spectra</title>
			<authors>Frutiger, C.; Solanki, S. K.; Mathys, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 444, Issue 2, December III 2005, pp.549-559</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...444..549F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...442..315R</bibcode>
			<title>X-rays from alpha Centauri - The darkening of the solar twin</title>
			<authors>Robrade, J.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Favata, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 442, Issue 1, October IV 2005, pp.315-321</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...442..315R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...441..615M</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining fundamental stellar parameters using seismology. Application to alpha Centauri AB</title>
			<authors>Miglio, A.; Montalbn, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 441, Issue 2, October II 2005, pp.615-629</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...441..615M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...440..727H</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of X-ray emission from beta Pictoris with XMM-Newton: a cool corona, a boundary layer or what?</title>
			<authors>Hempel, M.; Robrade, J.; Ness, J.-U.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 440, Issue 2, September III 2005, pp.727-734</journal>
			<date>9/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...440..727H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.361.1375B</bibcode>
			<title>The light curve of the semiregular variable L2 Puppis - II. Evidence for solar-like excitation of the oscillations</title>
			<authors>Bedding, T. R.; Kiss, L. L.; Kjeldsen, H.; Brewer, B. J.; Dind, Z. E.; Kawaler, S. D.; Zijlstra, A. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 361, Issue 4, pp. 1375-1381.</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.361.1375B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJS..159..141V</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic Properties of Cool Stars (SPOCS). I. 1040 F, G, and K Dwarfs from Keck, Lick, and AAT Planet Search Programs</title>
			<authors>Valenti, Jeff A.; Fischer, Debra A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 159, Issue 1, pp. 141-166.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJS..159..141V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJS..159..118W</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Lyalpha Emission Lines in the Hubble Space Telescope Archive: Intrinsic Line Fluxes and Absorption from the Heliosphere and Astrospheres</title>
			<authors>Wood, Brian E.; Redfield, Seth; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Mller, Hans-Reinhard; Zank, Gary P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 159, Issue 1, pp. 118-140.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJS..159..118W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...438..139S</bibcode>
			<title>Abundance trends in kinematical groups of the Milky Way's disk</title>
			<authors>Soubiran, C.; Girard, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 438, Issue 1, July IV 2005, pp.139-151</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...438..139S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...437.1127S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic metallicities for planet-host stars: Extending the samples</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Bento, J. P.; Almeida, P. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Ecuvillon, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 437, Issue 3, July III 2005, pp.1127-1133</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...437.1127S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005JApA...26..171S</bibcode>
			<title>Excitation of Solar-like Oscillations: From PMS to MS Stellar Models</title>
			<authors>Samadi, R.; Goupil, M.-J.; Alecian, E.; Baudin, F.; Georgobiani, D.; Trampedach, R.; Stein, R.; Nordlund, .</authors>
			<journal>Journal of Astrophysics and Astronomy, Vol. 26, Issue 2-3, p. 171</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005JApA...26..171S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...626..465R</bibcode>
			<title>The Effective Temperature Scale of FGK Stars. II. Teff:Color:[Fe/H] Calibrations</title>
			<authors>Ramrez, Ivn; Melndez, Jorge</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 626, Issue 1, pp. 465-485.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...626..465R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...626..446R</bibcode>
			<title>The Effective Temperature Scale of FGK Stars. I. Determination of Temperatures and Angular Diameters with the Infrared Flux Method</title>
			<authors>Ramrez, Ivn; Melndez, Jorge</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 626, Issue 1, pp. 446-464.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...626..446R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.359..521P</bibcode>
			<title>Circumstellar and circumbinary discs in eccentric stellar binaries</title>
			<authors>Pichardo, Barbara; Sparke, Linda S.; Aguilar, Luis A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 359, Issue 2, pp. 521-530.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.359..521P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...624.1010B</bibcode>
			<title>Single-Visit Photometric and Obscurational Completeness</title>
			<authors>Brown, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 624, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1024.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...624.1010B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...434..707W</bibcode>
			<title>Line identification in soft X-ray spectra of stellar coronae by comparison with the hottest white dwarf's photosphere: Procyon, alpha Cen A+B, and H 1504+65</title>
			<authors>Werner, K.; Drake, J. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 434, Issue 2, May I 2005, pp.707-712</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...434..707W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...623.1171T</bibcode>
			<title>Three Low-Mass Planets from the Anglo-Australian Planet Search</title>
			<authors>Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Jones, Hugh R. A.; Penny, Alan J.; McCarthy, Chris; Carter, Brad D.; Fischer, Debra A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 623, Issue 2, pp. 1171-1179.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...623.1171T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1102F</bibcode>
			<title>The Planet-Metallicity Correlation</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Valenti, Jeff</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1102-1117.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1102F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005AN....326..269S</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar activity cycles: observing the dynamo?</title>
			<authors>Strassmeier, K. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.326, Issue 3, p.269-277</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005AN....326..269S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Msngr.119...36W</bibcode>
			<title>Recent Astrophysical Results from the VLTI</title>
			<authors>Wittkowski, M.; Paresce, F.; Chesneau, O.; Kervella, P.; Meilland, A.; Meisenheimer, K.; Ohnaka, K.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger (ISSN0722-6691), No.119, p. 36-42 (March 2005)</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Msngr.119...36W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...432L..43B</bibcode>
			<title>The non-detection of oscillations in Procyon by MOST: Is it really a surprise?</title>
			<authors>Bedding, T. R.; Kjeldsen, H.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Butler, R. P.; Buzasi, D. L.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Frandsen, S.; Lebrun, J.-C.; Martic, M.; Schou, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 432, Issue 2, March III 2005, pp.L43-L48</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...432L..43B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.357..174D</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting accurate stellar angular diameters by the near-infrared surface brightness technique</title>
			<authors>Di Benedetto, G. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 357, Issue 1, pp. 174-190.</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.357..174D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...619L.187G</bibcode>
			<title>Structure in the &amp;epsil Eridani Debris Disk</title>
			<authors>Greaves, J. S.; Holland, W. S.; Wyatt, M. C.; Dent, W. R. F.; Robson, E. I.; Coulson, I. M.; Jenness, T.; Moriarty-Schieven, G. H.; Davis, G. R.; Butner, H. M.; Gear, W. K.; Dominik, C.; Walker, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 619, Issue 2, pp. L187-L190.</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...619L.187G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...431..773R</bibcode>
			<title>CHARM2: An updated Catalog of High Angular Resolution Measurements</title>
			<authors>Richichi, A.; Percheron, I.; Khristoforova, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.431, p.773-777 (2005)</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...431..773R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.356..671O</bibcode>
			<title>The use of frequency-separation ratios for asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>Ot Floranes, H.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Thompson, M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 356, Issue 2, pp. 671-679.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.356..671O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005PASA...22...29W</bibcode>
			<title>High-Resolution Spectroscopy of some Active Southern Stars</title>
			<authors>Waite, Ian A.; Carter, Brad D.; Marsden, Stephen C.; Mengel, Matthew W.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Volume 22, Issue 1, pp. 29-35.</journal>
			<date>0/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005PASA...22...29W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005LAstr.119..136M</bibcode>
			<title>Asterosismologie.</title>
			<authors>Mosser, B.</authors>
			<journal>L'astronomie, Vol. 119, p. 136-140 (2005)</journal>
			<date>0/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005LAstr.119..136M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004RMxAC..22...99L</bibcode>
			<title>Terrestrial Planet Formation in Binary Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, J. J.; Quintana, E. V.; Chambers, J. E.; Duncan, M. J.; Adams, F. C.</authors>
			<journal>Gravitational Collapse: From Massive Stars to Planets. / First Astrophysics meeting of the Observatorio Astronomico Nacional. / A meeting to celebrate Peter Bodenheimer for his outstanding contributions to Astrophysics. (Eds. G. Garca-Segura, G. Tenorio-Tagle, J. Franco, &amp; H. W. Yorke) Revista Mexicana de Astronoma y Astrofsica (Serie de Conferencias) Vol. 22, pp. 99-103 (2004) (http://www.astroscu.unam.mx/~rmaa/)</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004RMxAC..22...99L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...616L.167S</bibcode>
			<title>High-Resolution Spectroscopy of the Transiting Planet Host Star TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Yong, David; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Latham, David W.; Allende Prieto, Carlos; Brown, Timothy M.; Carney, Bruce W.; Laird, John B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 616, Issue 2, pp. L167-L170.</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...616L.167S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...427..667N</bibcode>
			<title>On the sizes of stellar X-ray coronae</title>
			<authors>Ness, J.-U.; Gdel, M.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Audard, M.; Telleschi, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.427, p.667-683 (2004)</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...427..667N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...614.1063L</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Picture of the First Ionization Potential and Inverse First Ionization Potential Effects</title>
			<authors>Laming, J. Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 614, Issue 2, pp. 1063-1072.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...614.1063L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...613L.153A</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-1: The Transiting Planet of a Bright K0 V Star</title>
			<authors>Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Torres, Guillermo; Latham, David W.; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Mandushev, Georgi; Belmonte, Juan A.; Charbonneau, David; Deeg, Hans J.; Dunham, Edward W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 613, Issue 2, pp. L153-L156.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...613L.153A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...613.1004R</bibcode>
			<title>The Structure of the Local Interstellar Medium. III. Temperature and Turbulence</title>
			<authors>Redfield, Seth; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 613, Issue 2, pp. 1004-1022.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...613.1004R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;G....45e..14E</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology: Asteroseismology of Sun-like stars</title>
			<authors>Elsworth, Yvonne P.; Thompson, Michael J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Geophysics, Volume 45, Issue 5, pp. 5.14-5.19.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26G....45e..14E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.353..903G</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Baade-Wesselink surface brightness relations</title>
			<authors>Groenewegen, M. A. T.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 353, Issue 3, pp. 903-916.</journal>
			<date>9/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.353..903G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...609..417R</bibcode>
			<title>Cooler and Bigger than Previously Thought? Planetary Host Stellar Parameters from the Infrared Flux Method</title>
			<authors>Ramrez, Ivn; Melndez, Jorge</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 609, Issue 1, pp. 417-422.</journal>
			<date>7/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...609..417R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...420..183A</bibcode>
			<title>S4N: A spectroscopic survey of stars in the solar neighborhood.  The Nearest 15 pc</title>
			<authors>Allende Prieto, C.; Barklem, P. S.; Lambert, D. L.; Cunha, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.420, p.183-205 (2004)</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...420..183A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004S&amp;T...107d..44S</bibcode>
			<title>Imaging exoplanets.</title>
			<authors>Shiga, D.</authors>
			<journal>Sky Telesc., 107, part no 4, 44-52 (2004)</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004S%26T...107d..44S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...605..472M</bibcode>
			<title>A Preliminary Seismic Analysis of 51 Pegasi: Large and Small Spacings from Standard Models</title>
			<authors>Murphy, Eric J.; Demarque, Pierre; Guenther, D. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 605, Issue 1, pp. 472-479.</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...605..472M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...604..741H</bibcode>
			<title>An Assessment of Dynamical Mass Constraints on Pre-Main-Sequence Evolutionary Tracks</title>
			<authors>Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; White, Russel J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 604, Issue 2, pp. 741-757.</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...604..741H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...417..651S</bibcode>
			<title>NEXXUS: A comprehensive ROSAT survey of coronal X-ray emission among nearby solar-like stars</title>
			<authors>Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Liefke, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.417, p.651-665 (2004)</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...417..651S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004PASP..116..187T</bibcode>
			<title>Astrophysics in 2003</title>
			<authors>Trimble, Virginia; Aschwanden, Markus J.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 116, Issue 817, pp. 187-265.</journal>
			<date>3/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004PASP..116..187T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...602..776R</bibcode>
			<title>The Structure of the Local Interstellar Medium. II. Observations of D I, C II, N I, O I, Al II, and Si II toward Stars within 100 Parsecs</title>
			<authors>Redfield, Seth; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 602, Issue 2, pp. 776-802.</journal>
			<date>2/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...602..776R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...415..331P</bibcode>
			<title>HST/STIS high resolution echelle spectra of alpha Centauri A (G2 V)</title>
			<authors>Pagano, I.; Linsky, J. L.; Valenti, J.; Duncan, D. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.415, p.331-348 (2004)</journal>
			<date>2/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...415..331P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...414..699C</bibcode>
			<title>Library of flux-calibrated echelle spectra of southern late-type dwarfs with different activity levels</title>
			<authors>Cincunegui, C.; Mauas, P. J. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.414, p.699-706 (2004)</journal>
			<date>2/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...414..699C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...600L..75B</bibcode>
			<title>Ultra-High-Precision Velocity Measurements of Oscillations in alpha Centauri A</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. Paul; Bedding, Timothy R.; Kjeldsen, Hans; McCarthy, Chris; O'Toole, Simon J.; Tinney, Christopher G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Wright, Jason T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 600, Issue 1, pp. L75-L78.</journal>
			<date>1/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...600L..75B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...600..419G</bibcode>
			<title>Matching Stellar Models to Oscillation Data</title>
			<authors>Guenther, D. B.; Brown, Kevin I. T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 600, Issue 1, pp. 419-434.</journal>
			<date>1/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...600..419G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003Msngr.114...26R</bibcode>
			<title>Harvesting Scientific Results with the VLTI</title>
			<authors>Richichi, Andrea; Paresce, Francesco</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger (ISSN0722-6691), No.114, p. 26-34 (December 2003)</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003Msngr.114...26R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003Msngr.114...20M</bibcode>
			<title>Setting New Standards with HARPS</title>
			<authors>Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Bouchy, F.; Rupprecht, G.; Lo Curto, G.; Avila, G.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bonfils, X.; Dall, Th.; Dekker, H.; Delabre, B.; Eckert, W.; Fleury, M.; Gilliotte, A.; Gojak, D.; Guzman, J. C.; Kohler, D.; Lizon, J.-L.; Longinotti, A.; Lovis, C.; Megevand, D.; Pasquini, L.; Reyes, J.; Sivan, J.-P.; Sosnowska, D.; Soto, R.; Udry, S.; van Kesteren, A.; Weber, L.; Weilenmann, U.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger (ISSN0722-6691), No.114, p. 20-24 (December 2003)</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003Msngr.114...20M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJS..149..423T</bibcode>
			<title>Target Selection for SETI. II. Tycho-2 Dwarfs, Old Open Clusters, and the Nearest 100 Stars</title>
			<authors>Turnbull, Margaret C.; Tarter, Jill C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 149, Issue 2, pp. 423-436.</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJS..149..423T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...409..611L</bibcode>
			<title>Disentangling discrepancies between stellar evolution  theory and sub-solar mass stars. The influence of the mixing length parameter for the UV Psc binary</title>
			<authors>Lastennet, E.; Fernandes, J.; Valls-Gabaud, D.; Oblak, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.409, p.611-618 (2003)</journal>
			<date>10/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...409..611L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...408..681K</bibcode>
			<title>The interferometric diameter and internal structure of Sirius A</title>
			<authors>Kervella, P.; Thvenin, F.; Morel, P.; Bord, P.; Di Folco, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.408, p.681-688 (2003)</journal>
			<date>9/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...408..681K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...593..868F</bibcode>
			<title>Local Interstellar Matter: The Apex Cloud</title>
			<authors>Frisch, Priscilla C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 593, Issue 2, pp. 868-873.</journal>
			<date>8/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...593..868F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...593..534J</bibcode>
			<title>An Estimate of the Sun's ROSAT-PSPC X-Ray Luminosities Using SNOE-SXP Measurements</title>
			<authors>Judge, Philip G.; Solomon, Stanley C.; Ayres, Thomas R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 593, Issue 1, pp. 534-548.</journal>
			<date>8/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...593..534J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003AJ....126..778V</bibcode>
			<title>Empirically Constrained Color-Temperature Relations. I. BV(RI)C</title>
			<authors>VandenBerg, Don A.; Clem, James L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 126, Issue 2, pp. 778-802.</journal>
			<date>8/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003AJ....126..778V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...407..347N</bibcode>
			<title>Are stellar coronae optically thin in X-rays?. A systematic investigation of opacity effects</title>
			<authors>Ness, J.-U.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Audard, M.; Gdel, M.; Mewe, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.407, p.347-358 (2003)</journal>
			<date>8/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...407..347N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...406L..23C</bibcode>
			<title>Solar-like oscillations in the K1 dwarf star alpha Cen B</title>
			<authors>Carrier, F.; Bourban, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.406, p.L23-L26 (2003)</journal>
			<date>7/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...406L..23C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...404.1087K</bibcode>
			<title>The diameters of alpha  Centauri A and B. A comparison of the asteroseismic and VINCI/VLTI views</title>
			<authors>Kervella, P.; Thvenin, F.; Sgransan, D.; Berthomieu, G.; Lopez, B.; Morel, P.; Provost, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.404, p.1087-1097 (2003)</journal>
			<date>6/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...404.1087K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003SSRv..106...49L</bibcode>
			<title>Atomic Deuterium/Hydrogen in the Galaxy</title>
			<authors>Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>Space Science Reviews, v. 106, Issue 1, p. 49-60 (2003).</journal>
			<date>4/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003SSRv..106...49L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...402..293T</bibcode>
			<title>A new seismic analysis of Alpha Centauri</title>
			<authors>Thoul, A.; Scuflaire, R.; Noels, A.; Vatovez, B.; Briquet, M.; Dupret, M.-A.; Montalban, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.402, p.293-297 (2003)</journal>
			<date>4/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...402..293T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJS..145..147S</bibcode>
			<title>The Structure of Stellar Coronae in Active Binary Systems</title>
			<authors>Sanz-Forcada, J.; Brickhouse, N. S.; Dupree, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 145, Issue 1, pp. 147-179.</journal>
			<date>3/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJS..145..147S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...585..993R</bibcode>
			<title>A Far Ultraviolet Spectroscopic Explorer Survey of Coronal Forbidden Lines in Late-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Redfield, Seth; Ayres, Thomas R.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Ake, Thomas B.; Dupree, A. K.; Robinson, Richard D.; Young, Peter R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 585, Issue 2, pp. 993-1006.</journal>
			<date>3/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...585..993R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...400.1103B</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary orbits in the elliptic restricted problem. V.. The ADS 11060 system</title>
			<authors>Benest, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.400, p.1103-1111 (2003)</journal>
			<date>3/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...400.1103B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...400..671R</bibcode>
			<title>Chandra-LETGS X-ray observation of alpha  Centauri: A nearby (G2V + K1V) binary system</title>
			<authors>Raassen, A. J. J.; Ness, J.-U.; Mewe, R.; van der Meer, R. L. J.; Burwitz, V.; Kaastra, J. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.400, p.671-678 (2003)</journal>
			<date>3/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...400..671R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...400..241P</bibcode>
			<title>Selection criteria for targets of asteroseismic campaigns</title>
			<authors>Pijpers, F. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.400, p.241-248 (2003)</journal>
			<date>3/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...400..241P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...583..963A</bibcode>
			<title>Space Telescope Imaging Spectrograph Survey of Far-Ultraviolet Coronal Forbidden Lines in Late-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Ayres, Thomas R.; Brown, Alexander; Harper, Graham M.; Osten, Rachel A.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Wood, Brian E.; Redfield, Seth</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 583, Issue 2, pp. 963-984.</journal>
			<date>2/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...583..963A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...398..731T</bibcode>
			<title>Statistical cataloging of archival data for luminosity class IV-V stars. II. The epoch 2001 [Fe/H] catalog</title>
			<authors>Taylor, B. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.398, p.731-738 (2003)</journal>
			<date>2/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...398..731T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...398..721T</bibcode>
			<title>Statistical cataloging of archival data for luminosity class IV-V stars. I. The epoch 2001 temperature catalog</title>
			<authors>Taylor, B. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.398, p.721-729 (2003)</journal>
			<date>2/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...398..721T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...582.1011S</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Astrometry and Photometry for the Luyten Catalog. II. Faint Stars and the Revised Catalog</title>
			<authors>Salim, Samir; Gould, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 582, Issue 2, pp. 1011-1031.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...582.1011S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...397..147P</bibcode>
			<title>The stellar activity-rotation relationship revisited: Dependence of saturated and non-saturated X-ray emission regimes on stellar mass for late-type dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Pizzolato, N.; Maggio, A.; Micela, G.; Sciortino, S.; Ventura, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.397, p.147-157 (2003)</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...397..147P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003PASA...20..203B</bibcode>
			<title>Solar-like Oscillations</title>
			<authors>Bedding, Timothy R.; Kjeldsen, Hans</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Volume 20, Issue 2, pp. 203-212.</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003PASA...20..203B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003PASA...20..165K</bibcode>
			<title>New Metallicity Calibration Down to [Fe/H] = -2.75 dex</title>
			<authors>Karaali, S.; Bilir, S.; Karatas, Y.; Ak, S. G.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Volume 20, Issue 2, pp. 165-172.</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003PASA...20..165K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003MSAIS...2..194S</bibcode>
			<title>Optical interferometry -- A brief introduction</title>
			<authors>Schller, Markus</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana Supplement, v.2, p.194 (2003)</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003MSAIS...2..194S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003MSAIS...2..162G</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of  alpha  Centauri from Concordia</title>
			<authors>Grec, G.; Renaud, C.; Berthomieu, G.; Provost, J.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana Supplement, v.2, p.162 (2003)</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003MSAIS...2..162G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ASPC..294..319Q</bibcode>
			<title>Terrestrial Planet Formation Around Alpha Centauri B</title>
			<authors>Quintana, E. V.</authors>
			<journal>Scientific Frontiers in Research on Extrasolar Planets, ASP Conference Series, Vol 294, Edited by Drake Deming and Sara Seager. (San Francisco: ASP) ISBN: 1-58381-141-9, 2003, pp. 319-322</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ASPC..294..319Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.337.1170J</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planets around HD 196050, HD 216437 and HD 160691</title>
			<authors>Jones, Hugh R. A.; Paul Butler, R.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Tinney, Chris G.; Penny, Alan J.; McCarthy, Chris; Carter, Brad D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notice of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 337, Issue 4, pp. 1170-1178.</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.337.1170J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002KFNT...18..535Z</bibcode>
			<title>The radii and spectra of the nearest stars</title>
			<authors>Zakhozhaj, V. A.</authors>
			<journal>Kinematika I Fizika Nebesnykh Tel, v. 18, no. 6, p. 535-552</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002KFNT...18..535Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...581..626R</bibcode>
			<title>A Far Ultraviolet Spectroscopic Explorer Survey of Late-Type Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Redfield, Seth; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Ake, Thomas B.; Ayres, Thomas R.; Dupree, A. K.; Robinson, Richard D.; Wood, Brian E.; Young, Peter R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 581, Issue 1, pp. 626-653.</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...581..626R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...396..219B</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of terrestrial planets in close binary systems: The case of alpha Centauri A</title>
			<authors>Barbieri, M.; Marzari, F.; Scholl, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.396, p.219-224 (2002)</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...396..219B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002PASP..114.1173S</bibcode>
			<title>Narrow-Angle Astrometry with the Space Interferometry Mission: The Search for Extrasolar Planets. I. Detection and Characterization of Single Planets</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Casertano, S.; Brown, R. A.; Lattanzi, M. G.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 114, Issue 801, pp. 1173-1196.</journal>
			<date>11/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002PASP..114.1173S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...579..800S</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on Chromospheres and Convection among the Main-Sequence A Stars</title>
			<authors>Simon, Theodore; Ayres, Thomas R.; Redfield, Seth; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 579, Issue 2, pp. 800-809.</journal>
			<date>11/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...579..800S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...578..543S</bibcode>
			<title>Imaging Spectroscopy for Extrasolar Planet Detection</title>
			<authors>Sparks, William B.; Ford, Holland C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 578, Issue 1, pp. 543-564.</journal>
			<date>10/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...578..543S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...576..982Q</bibcode>
			<title>Terrestrial Planet Formation in the alpha Centauri System</title>
			<authors>Quintana, Elisa V.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Chambers, John E.; Duncan, Martin J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 576, Issue 2, pp. 982-996.</journal>
			<date>9/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...576..982Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...392L...9T</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology and calibration of alpha Cen binary system</title>
			<authors>Thvenin, F.; Provost, J.; Morel, P.; Berthomieu, G.; Bouchy, F.; Carrier, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.392, p.L9-L12 (2002)</journal>
			<date>9/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...392L...9T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...392..671E</bibcode>
			<title>The planet search program at the ESO Coud Echelle spectrometer. III. The complete Long Camera survey results</title>
			<authors>Endl, M.; Krster, M.; Els, S.; Hatzes, A. P.; Cochran, W. D.; Dennerl, K.; Dbereiner, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.392, p.671-690 (2002)</journal>
			<date>9/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...392..671E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...574..834F</bibcode>
			<title>The Velocity Distribution of the Nearest Interstellar Gas</title>
			<authors>Frisch, Priscilla C.; Grodnicki, Lauren; Welty, Daniel E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 574, Issue 2, pp. 834-846.</journal>
			<date>8/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...574..834F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...391..647G</bibcode>
			<title>Photocentric orbits from a direct combination of ground-based astrometry with Hipparcos. I. Comparison with known orbits</title>
			<authors>Gontcharov, G. A.; Kiyaeva, O. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.391, p.647-657 (2002)</journal>
			<date>8/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...391..647G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJS..141..187B</bibcode>
			<title>Revised Coordinates and Proper Motions of the Stars in the Luyten Half-Second Catalog</title>
			<authors>Bakos, Gspr .; Sahu, Kailash C.; Nmeth, Pter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 141, Issue 1, pp. 187-193.</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJS..141..187B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...574..412W</bibcode>
			<title>Measured Mass-Loss Rates of Solar-like Stars as a Function of Age and Activity</title>
			<authors>Wood, Brian E.; Mller, Hans-Reinhard; Zank, Gary P.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 574, Issue 1, pp. 412-425.</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...574..412W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...388L..13S</bibcode>
			<title>Carbon and nitrogen abundances in the coronae of Algol B and other evolved stars: Evidence for CNO-cycle processed material</title>
			<authors>Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Ness, J.-U.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.388, p.L13-L16 (2002)</journal>
			<date>6/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...388L..13S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002PASJ...54..275T</bibcode>
			<title>On the Abundance of Potassium in Metal-Poor Stars</title>
			<authors>Takeda, Yoichi; Zhao, Gang; Chen, Yu-Qin; Qiu, Hong-Mei; Takada-Hidai, Masahide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.54, No.2, pp.275-284</journal>
			<date>4/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002PASJ...54..275T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJS..139..439R</bibcode>
			<title>The Structure of the Local Interstellar Medium. I. High-Resolution Observations of Fe II, Mg II, and Ca II toward Stars within 100 Parsecs</title>
			<authors>Redfield, Seth; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 139, Issue 2, pp. 439-465.</journal>
			<date>4/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJS..139..439R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...567..544A</bibcode>
			<title>Signatures of Convection in the Spectrum of Procyon: Fundamental Parameters and Iron Abundance</title>
			<authors>Allende Prieto, Carlos; Asplund, Martin; Garca Lpez, Ramn J.; Lambert, David L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 567, Issue 1, pp. 544-565.</journal>
			<date>3/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...567..544A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AN....323...37S</bibcode>
			<title>On stellar encounters and their effect on cometary orbits in the Oort cloud</title>
			<authors>Serafin, R. A.; Grothues, H.-G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, vol. 323, no. 1, p. 37-48.</journal>
			<date>3/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AN....323...37S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...383..210M</bibcode>
			<title>On X-ray variability in ROSAT-PSPC observations of F7-K2 stars</title>
			<authors>Marino, A.; Micela, G.; Peres, G.; Sciortino, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.383, p.210-217 (2002)</journal>
			<date>1/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...383..210M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...381..500K</bibcode>
			<title>Europium abundances in F and G disk dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Koch, A.; Edvardsson, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.381, p.500-506 (2002)</journal>
			<date>1/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...381..500K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001MNRAS.328...45M</bibcode>
			<title>Late-type members of young stellar kinematic groups - I. Single stars</title>
			<authors>Montes, D.; Lpez-Santiago, J.; Glvez, M. C.; Fernndez-Figueroa, M. J.; De Castro, E.; Cornide, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 328, Issue 1, pp. 45-63.</journal>
			<date>11/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001MNRAS.328...45M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...379..634G</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar encounters with the solar system</title>
			<authors>Garca-Snchez, J.; Weissman, P. R.; Preston, R. A.; Jones, D. L.; Lestrade, J.-F.; Latham, D. W.; Stefanik, R. P.; Paredes, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.379, p.634-659 (2001)</journal>
			<date>11/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...379..634G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001RMxAA..37..179L</bibcode>
			<title>Perturbations by Mass Loss in the Orbital Elements of gamma Persei and alpha Centauri</title>
			<authors>Ling, J. F.; Magdalena, P.; Prieto, C.</authors>
			<journal>Revista Mexicana de Astronomia y Astrofisica, Vol. 37, pp. 179-186 (2001)</journal>
			<date>10/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001RMxAA..37..179L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...558..830A</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical Abundances from Inversions of Stellar Spectra: Analysis of Solar-Type Stars with Homogeneous and Static Model Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Allende Prieto, Carlos; Barklem, Paul S.; Asplund, Martin; Ruiz Cobo, Basilio</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 558, Issue 2, pp. 830-851.</journal>
			<date>9/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...558..830A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...374.1085C</bibcode>
			<title>On the Wilson-Bappu relationship in the Mg II k line</title>
			<authors>Cassatella, A.; Altamore, A.; Badiali, M.; Cardini, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.374, p.1085-1091 (2001)</journal>
			<date>8/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...374.1085C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...374..675E</bibcode>
			<title>The planet search program at the ESO Coud Echelle spectrometer. II. The alpha Centauri system: Limits for planetary companions</title>
			<authors>Endl, M.; Krster, M.; Els, S.; Hatzes, A. P.; Cochran, W. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.374, p.675-681 (2001)</journal>
			<date>8/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...374..675E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...373..159C</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of [Fe/H] determinations for FGK stars: 2001 edition</title>
			<authors>Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Soubiran, C.; Ralite, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.373, p.159-163 (2001)</journal>
			<date>7/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...373..159C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001AJ....121.3254T</bibcode>
			<title>Search for Faint Companions to Nearby Solar-like Stars using the Adaptive Optics System at Mount Wilson Observatory</title>
			<authors>Turner, Nils H.; ten Brummelaar, Theo A.; McAlister, Harold A.; Mason, Brian D.; Hartkopf, William I.; Roberts, Lewis C., Jr.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 121, Issue 6, pp. 3254-3258.</journal>
			<date>6/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001AJ....121.3254T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...551..413R</bibcode>
			<title>Microstructure of the Local Interstellar Cloud and the Identification of the Hyades Cloud</title>
			<authors>Redfield, Seth; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 551, Issue 1, pp. 413-428.</journal>
			<date>4/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...551..413R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...367..521P</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of Apparent Diameters and Absolute Radii of Stars (CADARS) - Third edition - Comments and statistics</title>
			<authors>Pasinetti Fracassini, L. E.; Pastori, L.; Covino, S.; Pozzi, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.367, p.521-524 (2001)</journal>
			<date>2/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...367..521P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...547L..49W</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Estimates for the Mass-Loss Rates of alpha Centauri and Proxima Centauri Using Hubble Space Telescope Lyalpha Spectra</title>
			<authors>Wood, Brian E.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Mller, Hans-Reinhard; Zank, Gary P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 547, Issue 1, pp. L49-L52.</journal>
			<date>1/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...547L..49W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001AJ....121..489R</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for L Dwarf Binary Systems</title>
			<authors>Reid, I. Neill; Gizis, John E.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Koerner, D. W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 121, Issue 1, pp. 489-502.</journal>
			<date>1/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001AJ....121..489R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001PASA...18..281D</bibcode>
			<title>Binary Star Observations in Selected Instants of Good Seeing</title>
			<authors>Davis, John; North, Julian R.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Volume 18, Issue 3, pp. 281-286.</journal>
			<date>0/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001PASA...18..281D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001BaltA..10..481B</bibcode>
			<title>Kinematics of Hipparcos Visual Binaries. I. Stars with Orbital Solutions</title>
			<authors>Bartkevicius, A.; Gudas, A.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.10, p.481-587.</journal>
			<date>0/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001BaltA..10..481B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...363..947J</bibcode>
			<title>The G dwarf problem. Analysis of a new data set</title>
			<authors>Jrgensen, Bjarne Rosenkilde</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.363, p.947-957 (2000)</journal>
			<date>11/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...363..947J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...363..675M</bibcode>
			<title>Calibrations of alpha Centauri A &amp; B</title>
			<authors>Morel, P.; Provost, J.; Lebreton, Y.; Thvenin, F.; Berthomieu, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.363, p.675-691 (2000)</journal>
			<date>11/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...363..675M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJ...542..493W</bibcode>
			<title>Hydrogen Lyalpha Absorption Predictions by Boltzmann Models of the Heliosphere</title>
			<authors>Wood, Brian E.; Mller, Hans-Reinhard; Zank, Gary P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 542, Issue 1, pp. 493-503.</journal>
			<date>10/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJ...542..493W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJ...542..411W</bibcode>
			<title>The Mg II and Lyalpha Lines of Nearby K Dwarfs: Interstellar Medium Components and Flux Measurements</title>
			<authors>Wood, Brian E.; Ambruster, Carol W.; Brown, Alexander; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 542, Issue 1, pp. 411-420.</journal>
			<date>10/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJ...542..411W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJ...539..815J</bibcode>
			<title>An IUE Atlas of Pre-Main-Sequence Stars. II. Far-Ultraviolet Accretion Diagnostics in T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 539, Issue 2, pp. 815-833.</journal>
			<date>8/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJ...539..815J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJ...532..497P</bibcode>
			<title>HST/STIS Echelle Spectra of the dM1e Star AU Microscopii Outside of Flares</title>
			<authors>Pagano, Isabella; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Carkner, Lee; Robinson, Richard D.; Woodgate, Bruce; Timothy, Gethyn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 532, Issue 1, pp. 497-513.</journal>
			<date>3/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJ...532..497P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJ...531..503G</bibcode>
			<title>alpha Centauri AB</title>
			<authors>Guenther, D. B.; Demarque, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 531, Issue 1, pp. 503-520.</journal>
			<date>3/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJ...531..503G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000AJ....119..906S</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Faint Companions to Nearby Stars Using the Wide Field Planetary Camera 2</title>
			<authors>Schroeder, Daniel J.; Golimowski, David A.; Brukardt, Ryan A.; Burrows, Christopher J.; Caldwell, John J.; Fastie, William G.; Ford, Holland C.; Hesman, Brigette; Kletskin, Ilona; Krist, John E.; Royle, Patricia; Zubrowski, Richard. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 119, Issue 2, pp. 906-922.</journal>
			<date>2/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000AJ....119..906S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJ...528..756L</bibcode>
			<title>The Three-dimensional Structure of the Warm Local Interstellar Medium. I. Methodology</title>
			<authors>Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Redfield, Seth; Wood, Brian E.; Piskunov, Nikolai</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 528, Issue 2, pp. 756-766.</journal>
			<date>1/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJ...528..756L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...353..666C</bibcode>
			<title>The infrared triplet lines of ionized calcium as a diagnostic tool for F, G, K-type stellar atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Chmielewski, Yves</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.353, p.666-690 (2000)</journal>
			<date>1/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...353..666C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999ApJ...525..492F</bibcode>
			<title>Dust in the Local Interstellar Wind</title>
			<authors>Frisch, Priscilla C.; Dorschner, Johann M.; Geiss, Johannes; Greenberg, J. Mayo; Grn, Eberhard; Landgraf, Markus; Hoppe, Peter; Jones, Anthony P.; Kr tschmer, Wolfgang; Linde, Timur J.; Morfill, Gregor E.; Reach, William; Slavin, Jonathan D.; Svestka, Jiri; Witt, Adolf N.; Zank, Gary P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 525, Issue 1, pp. 492-516.</journal>
			<date>11/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999ApJ...525..492F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999PASP..111.1009G</bibcode>
			<title>Linearity and High Signal-to-Noise Performance of the STIS CCD</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; Goudfrooij, Paul; Kimble, Randy A.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 111, Issue 762, pp. 1009-1020.</journal>
			<date>8/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999PASP..111.1009G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999ARep...43..521G</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical L-M, R-M, and M-Teff relations for main-sequence stars: Components of close binary systems and low-mass stars</title>
			<authors>Gorda, S. Yu.; Svechnikov, M. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Reports, Volume 43, Issue 8, August 1999, pp.521-525</journal>
			<date>8/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999ARep...43..521G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...348.1040D</bibcode>
			<title>Astrometric radial velocities. I. Non-spectroscopic methods for measuring stellar radial velocity</title>
			<authors>Dravins, Dainis; Lindegren, Lennart; Madsen, Sren</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.348, p.1040-1051 (1999)</journal>
			<date>8/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...348.1040D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999NewA....4..231L</bibcode>
			<title>Deuterium abundances</title>
			<authors>Lemoine, Martin; Audouze, Jean; Ben Jaffel, Lotfi; Feldman, Paul; Ferlet, Roger; Hebrard, Guillaume; Jenkins, Edward B.; Mallouris, Christoforos; Moos, Warren; Sembach, Kenneth; Sonneborn, George; Vidal-Madjar, Alfred; York, Donald G.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, vol. 4, no. 4, p. 231-243.</journal>
			<date>7/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999NewA....4..231L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999Ap&amp;SS.265..345C</bibcode>
			<title>Old, Low-Mass, Metal-Rich (SMR) Stars</title>
			<authors>Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Lebreton, Y.; Soubiran, C.; Friel, E. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, v. 265, Issue 1/4, p. 345-352 (1999).</journal>
			<date>7/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999Ap%26SS.265..345C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999Ap&amp;SS.265...57B</bibcode>
			<title>Light Element Abundances in Field Stars</title>
			<authors>Balachandran, Suchitra C.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, v. 265, Issue 1/4, p. 57-65 (1999).</journal>
			<date>7/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999Ap%26SS.265...57B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...345..249C</bibcode>
			<title>Beryllium abundance in lithium-rich giants</title>
			<authors>Castilho, B. V.; Spite, F.; Barbuy, B.; Spite, M.; de Medeiros, J. R.; Gregorio-Hetem, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.345, p.249-255 (1999)</journal>
			<date>5/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...345..249C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;AS..136..419P</bibcode>
			<title>Evolution of the ``efficiency'' when different data sets are combined into a unified adjustment</title>
			<authors>Pourbaix, D.; Eichhorn, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.136, p.419-420</journal>
			<date>4/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26AS..136..419P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...344..172P</bibcode>
			<title>Revised masses of alpha Centauri</title>
			<authors>Pourbaix, D.; Neuforge-Verheecke, C.; Noels, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.344, p.172-176 (1999)</journal>
			<date>4/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...344..172P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999MNRAS.303..579K</bibcode>
			<title>A search for solar-like oscillations and granulation in alpha CEN A</title>
			<authors>Kjeldsen, H.; Bedding, T. R.; Frandsen, S.; dall, T. H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 303, Issue 3, pp. 579-587.</journal>
			<date>3/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999MNRAS.303..579K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;AS..135..319H</bibcode>
			<title>The ROSAT all-sky survey catalogue of the nearby stars</title>
			<authors>Hnsch, M.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Sterzik, M. F.; Voges, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.135, p.319-338</journal>
			<date>3/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26AS..135..319H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999AJ....117.1042G</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Encounters with the Oort Cloud Based on HIPPARCOS Data</title>
			<authors>Garca-Snchez, Joan; Preston, Robert A.; Jones, Dayton L.; Weissman, Paul R.; Lestrade, Jean-Franois; Latham, David W.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 117, Issue 2, pp. 1042-1055.</journal>
			<date>2/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999AJ....117.1042G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...341..857L</bibcode>
			<title>Metallicity-dependent effective temperature determination for eclipsing binaries from synthetic UVBY Strmgren photometry</title>
			<authors>Lastennet, E.; Lejeune, T.; Westera, P.; Buser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.341, p.857-866 (1999)</journal>
			<date>1/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...341..857L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...339L..29G</bibcode>
			<title>Parent stars of extrasolar planets III: rho^1 CANCRI Revisited</title>
			<authors>Gonzalez, Guillermo; Vanture, Andrew D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.339, p.L29-L32 (1998)</journal>
			<date>11/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...339L..29G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...339..545M</bibcode>
			<title>Alpha Centauri: coronal temperature structure and abundances from ASCA observations</title>
			<authors>Mewe, R.; Drake, S. A.; Kaastra, J. S.; Schrijver, C. J.; Drake, J. J.; Guedel, M.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Singh, K. P.; White, N. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.339, p.545-552 (1998)</journal>
			<date>11/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...339..545M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...338..455F</bibcode>
			<title>Fundamental stellar parameters for nearby visual binary stars: eta Cas, XI Boo, 70 OPH and 85 Peg. Helium abundance, age and mixing length parameter for low mass stars</title>
			<authors>Fernandes, J.; Lebreton, Y.; Baglin, A.; Morel, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.338, p.455-464 (1998)</journal>
			<date>10/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...338..455F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998PASP..110..794S</bibcode>
			<title>Recalibration of the Wilson-Bappu Effect Using the Singly Ionized Magnesium K Line</title>
			<authors>Scoville, Frederick; Mena-Werth, Jose</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 110, Issue 749, pp. 794-803.</journal>
			<date>7/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998PASP..110..794S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...334..599G</bibcode>
			<title>Beryllium abundances in parent stars of extrasolar planets: 16 Cygni A &amp; B and rho (1) CANCRI</title>
			<authors>Garcia Lopez, R. J.; Perez de Taoro, M. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.334, p.599-605 (1998)</journal>
			<date>6/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...334..599G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...334..221G</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic analyses of the parent stars of extrasolar planetary system candidates</title>
			<authors>Gonzalez, Guillermo</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.334, p.221-238 (1998)</journal>
			<date>6/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...334..221G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998ApJ...499..871D</bibcode>
			<title>Boron Abundances and Internal Mixing in Stars. I. The Hyades Giants</title>
			<authors>Duncan, Douglas K.; Peterson, Ruth C.; Thorburn, Julie A.; Pinsonneault, Marc H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.499, p.871</journal>
			<date>5/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998ApJ...499..871D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998SSRv...84..297V</bibcode>
			<title>Deuterium Observations in the Galaxy</title>
			<authors>Vidal-Madjar, A.; Ferlet, R.; Lemoine, M.</authors>
			<journal>Space Science Reviews, v. 84, Issue 1/2, p. 297-308 (1998).</journal>
			<date>4/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998SSRv...84..297V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998SSRv...84..285L</bibcode>
			<title>Deuterium Abundance in the Local ISM and Possible Spatial Variations</title>
			<authors>Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>Space Science Reviews, vol. 84, p. 285</journal>
			<date>4/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998SSRv...84..285L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...332.1147B</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary orbits in the elliptic restricted problem. IV. The ADS 12033 system</title>
			<authors>Benest, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.332, p.1147-1153 (1998)</journal>
			<date>4/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...332.1147B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998ApJ...495..905B</bibcode>
			<title>Implications of a Subthreshold Resonance for Stellar Beryllium Depletion</title>
			<authors>Brown, Edward F.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.495, p.905</journal>
			<date>3/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998ApJ...495..905B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998ApJ...492..788W</bibcode>
			<title>The Local ISM and Its Interaction with the Winds of Nearby Late-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Wood, Brian E.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.492, p.788</journal>
			<date>1/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998ApJ...492..788W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998AJ....115..316C</bibcode>
			<title>Extreme Ultraviolet Explorer Right Angle Program observations of cool stars</title>
			<authors>Christian, D. J.; Drake, J. J.; Mathioudakis, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, vol. 115, p. 316</journal>
			<date>1/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998AJ....115..316C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998SerAJ.157...13P</bibcode>
			<title>Inclination of the Orbital Planes of Visual Binaries</title>
			<authors>Popovic, G. M.</authors>
			<journal>Serbian Astronomical Journal, Vol. 157, page 13 ()</journal>
			<date>0/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998SerAJ.157...13P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;A...328..261N</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic analysis of the Alpha Centauri system</title>
			<authors>Neuforge-Verheecke, C.; Magain, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.328, p.261-268 (1997)</journal>
			<date>12/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26A...328..261N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...487L.151F</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared Space Observatory Mapping of 60 MU M Dust Emission Around Vega-type Systems</title>
			<authors>Fajardo-Acosta, S. B.; Stencel, R. E.; Backman, D. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Letters v.487, p.L151</journal>
			<date>10/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...487L.151F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;A...326..741S</bibcode>
			<title>HeI D3 absorption and its relation to rotation and activity in G and K dwarfs.</title>
			<authors>Saar, S. H.; Huovelin, J.; Osten, R. A.; Shcherbakov, A. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.326, p.741-750</journal>
			<date>10/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26A...326..741S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...487..259G</bibcode>
			<title>One- versus Two-Shock Heliosphere: Constraining Models with Goddard High Resolution Spectrograph Ly alpha Spectra toward alpha Centauri</title>
			<authors>Gayley, K. G.; Zank, G. P.; Pauls, H. L.; Frisch, P. C.; Welty, D. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.487, p.259</journal>
			<date>9/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...487..259G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;AS..124..299C</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of [Fe/H] determinations: 1996 edition</title>
			<authors>Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Soubiran, C.; Friel, E. D.; Ralite, N.; Francois, P.</authors>
			<journal>A &amp; A Supplement series, Vol. 124, August 1997, 299-305.</journal>
			<date>8/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26AS..124..299C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...483..435S</bibcode>
			<title>High Chromospheres of Late A Stars</title>
			<authors>Simon, Theodore; Landsman, Wayne B.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.483, p.435</journal>
			<date>7/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...483..435S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997AJ....114..388H</bibcode>
			<title>The solar neighborhood IV: discovery of the twentieth nearest star</title>
			<authors>Henry, Todd J.; Ianna, Philip A.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Jahreiss, Hartmut</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal 114, 388-395</journal>
			<date>7/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997AJ....114..388H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;A...323..809F</bibcode>
			<title>The [Fe/H] distribution of a volume limited sample of solar-type stars and its implications for galactic chemical evolution.</title>
			<authors>Favata, F.; Micela, G.; Sciortino, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.323, p.809-818</journal>
			<date>7/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26A...323..809F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;A...322..131F</bibcode>
			<title>The relationship between lithium and activity in disk population main sequence G and K stars.</title>
			<authors>Favata, F.; Micela, G.; Sciortino, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.322, p.131-138</journal>
			<date>6/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26A...322..131F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...480..784P</bibcode>
			<title>Hubble Space Telescope Beryllium Abundances in the alpha Centauri System</title>
			<authors>Primas, F.; Duncan, D. K.; Pinsonneault, M. H.; Deliyannis, Constantine P.; Thorburn, J. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.480, p.784</journal>
			<date>5/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...480..784P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997AJ....113.1871K</bibcode>
			<title>Lithium Abundances in the Solar Twins 16 CYG A and B and the Solar Analog alpha CEN A, Calibration of the 6707 Angstrom Li Region Linelist, and Implications</title>
			<authors>King, Jeremy R.; Deliyannis, Constantine P.; Hiltgen, Daniel D.; Stephens, Alex; Cunha, Katia; Boesgaard, Ann Merchant</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.113, p.1871</journal>
			<date>5/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997AJ....113.1871K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997MNRAS.286..500M</bibcode>
			<title>Quantitative spectral classification of galactic disc K-M stars from spectrophotometric measurements</title>
			<authors>Malyuto, V.; Oestreicher, M. O.; Schmidt-Kaler, Th.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 286, Issue 2, pp. 500-512.</journal>
			<date>4/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997MNRAS.286..500M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...478L.103S</bibcode>
			<title>The Mixing Length in Convective Stellar Envelopes Is Proportional to Distance from the Convective Boundary</title>
			<authors>Stothers, Richard B.; Chin, Chao-Wen</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Letters v.478, p.L103</journal>
			<date>4/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...478L.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997AJ....113.1445W</bibcode>
			<title>The Stability of Planets in the Alpha Centauri System</title>
			<authors>Wiegert, Paul A.; Holman, Matt J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.113, p. 1445-1450 (1997)</journal>
			<date>4/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997AJ....113.1445W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...478..778K</bibcode>
			<title>The 9Be Abundances of alpha Centauri A and B and the Sun: Implications for Stellar Evolution and Mixing</title>
			<authors>King, Jeremy R.; Deliyannis, Constantine P.; Boesgaard, Ann Merchant</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.478, p.778</journal>
			<date>3/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...478..778K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...478..745W</bibcode>
			<title>Evaluating Possible Heating Mechanisms Using the Transition Region Line Profiles of Late-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Wood, Brian E.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Ayres, Thomas R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.478, p.745</journal>
			<date>3/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...478..745W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997MNRAS.284..803S</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation, turbulence and evidence for magnetic fields in southern dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Saar, S. H.; Osten, R. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 284, Issue 4, pp. 803-810.</journal>
			<date>2/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997MNRAS.284..803S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;A...318..429R</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic field measurements on moderately active cool dwarfs.</title>
			<authors>Rueedi, I.; Solanki, S. K.; Mathys, G.; Saar, S. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.318, p.429-442</journal>
			<date>2/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26A...318..429R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...474..315P</bibcode>
			<title>Local Interstellar Medium Properties and Deuterium Abundances for the Lines of Sight toward HR 1099, 31 Comae, beta Ceti, and beta Cassiopeiae</title>
			<authors>Piskunov, Nikolai; Wood, Brian E.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Dempsey, Robert C.; Ayres, Thomas R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.474, p.315</journal>
			<date>1/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...474..315P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ARA&amp;A..35..557P</bibcode>
			<title>Mixing in Stars</title>
			<authors>Pinsonneault, M.</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 35, 1997, pp. 557-605.</journal>
			<date>0/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ARA%26A..35..557P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996A&amp;AS..120..423S</bibcode>
			<title>Temperature and luminosity effects in photoelectric spectrum scanner measurements of F0-K5 stars.</title>
			<authors>Schmidt-Kaler, T.; Malyuto, V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.120, p.423-427</journal>
			<date>12/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996A%26AS..120..423S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996S&amp;T....92R..32R</bibcode>
			<title>Our Nearest Celestial Neighbors</title>
			<authors>Roth, Joshua; Sinnott, Roger W.</authors>
			<journal>Sky and Telescope, volume 92, number 4, page 32.</journal>
			<date>10/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996S%26T....92R..32R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996ApJ...470.1157W</bibcode>
			<title>The Properties of the Local Interstellar Medium and the Interaction of the Stellar Winds of epsilon INDI and lambda Andromedae with the Interstellar Environment</title>
			<authors>Wood, Brian E.; Alexander, William R.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.470, p.1157</journal>
			<date>10/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996ApJ...470.1157W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996A&amp;A...314..983B</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary orbits in the elliptic restricted problem. III. The eta Coronae Borealis system.</title>
			<authors>Benest, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.314, p.983-988</journal>
			<date>10/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996A%26A...314..983B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996A&amp;A...313..909G</bibcode>
			<title>Constraints on the use of Be I lines for deriving beryllium abundances in late-type dwarf stars.</title>
			<authors>Garcia Lopez, R. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.313, p.909-912</journal>
			<date>9/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996A%26A...313..909G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996PASP..108..724P</bibcode>
			<title>The Challenge of Beryllium Observations</title>
			<authors>Primas, Francesca</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, v.108, p.724</journal>
			<date>8/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996PASP..108..724P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....112..276M</bibcode>
			<title>Binary Star Orbits From Speckle Interferometry. IX. The Nearby Solar-Type Speckle-Spectroscopic Binary Fin 347 AA</title>
			<authors>Mason, Brian D.; McAlister, Harold A.; Hartkopf, William I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.112, p.276</journal>
			<date>7/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....112..276M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996A&amp;A...311..951F</bibcode>
			<title>Lithium abundance in a volume-limited sample of nearby main sequence G and K stars.</title>
			<authors>Favata, F.; Micela, G.; Sciortino, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.311, p.951-960</journal>
			<date>7/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996A%26A...311..951F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996PASP..108..510S</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for Faint Companions to Nearby Stars with the Hubble Space Telescope</title>
			<authors>Schroeder, Daniel J.; Golimowski, David A.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, v.108, p.510</journal>
			<date>6/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996PASP..108..510S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996MNRAS.280.1155B</bibcode>
			<title>Measuring stellar oscillations using equivalent widths of absorption lines</title>
			<authors>Bedding, T. R.; Kjeldsen, H.; Reetz, J.; Barbuy, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 280, Issue 4, pp. 1155-1161.</journal>
			<date>6/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996MNRAS.280.1155B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AAS...188.5808K</bibcode>
			<title>The (9) Be Abundances of alpha CEN A and B and the Sun</title>
			<authors>King, J. R.; Deliyannis, C. P.; Boesgaard, A. M.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 188th AAS Meeting, #58.08; &lt;ALTJOURNAL&gt;Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 28, p.916&lt;/ALTJOURNAL&gt;</journal>
			<date>5/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AAS...188.5808K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996IAUC.6338....2G</bibcode>
			<title>Alpha Centauri C</title>
			<authors>Guinan, E.; Morgan, N.</authors>
			<journal>IAU Circ., 6338, 2 (1996).  Edited by Green, D. W. E.</journal>
			<date>3/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996IAUC.6338....2G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996Ap&amp;SS.237...13J</bibcode>
			<title>The Chromosphere-Corona Transition Region in Late-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Jordan, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, Volume 237, Issue 1-2, pp. 13-32</journal>
			<date>3/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996Ap%26SS.237...13J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996ApJ...457..382B</bibcode>
			<title>Determinations of Metal Abundances from ROSAT Observations</title>
			<authors>Bauer, Franz; Bregman, Joel N.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.457, p.382</journal>
			<date>1/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996ApJ...457..382B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....111..439H</bibcode>
			<title>A Survey of Ca II H and K Chromospheric Emission in Southern Solar-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Henry, Todd J.; Soderblom, David R.; Donahue, Robert A.; Baliunas, Sallie L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, 111, 439</journal>
			<date>1/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....111..439H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996BaltA...5..603A</bibcode>
			<title>The Pulkovo Spectrophotometric Catalog of Bright Stars in the Range from 320 TO 1080 NM</title>
			<authors>Alekseeva, G. A.; Arkharov, A. A.; Galkin, V. D.; Hagen-Thorn, E. I.; Nikanorova, I. N.; Novikov, V. V.; Novopashenny, V. B.; Pakhomov, V. P.; Ruban, E. V.; Shchegolev, D. E.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.5, p.603-838.</journal>
			<date>0/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996BaltA...5..603A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995MNRAS.277.1507K</bibcode>
			<title>The dynamical properties of stellar systems in the Galactic disc</title>
			<authors>Kroupa, Pavel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 277, 1507</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995MNRAS.277.1507K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;AS..114..487J</bibcode>
			<title>Photographic observations of visual double stars.</title>
			<authors>Jasinta, D. M. D.; Raharto, M.; Soegiartini, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.114, p.487</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26AS..114..487J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995IAUC.6259....2G</bibcode>
			<title>Alpha Centauri B</title>
			<authors>Guinan, E.; Messina, S.</authors>
			<journal>IAU Circ., 6259, 2 (1995).  Edited by Green, D. W. E.</journal>
			<date>11/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995IAUC.6259....2G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJ...450..401F</bibcode>
			<title>Correlations of Coronal X-Ray Emission with Activity, Mass, and Age of the Nearby K and M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Fleming, Thomas A.; Schmitt, Juergen H. M. M.; Giampapa, Mark S.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.450, p.401</journal>
			<date>9/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJ...450..401F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995PASA...12..266E</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology.</title>
			<authors>Edmonds, P. D.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Vol. 12, No. 2, p. 266 - 267</journal>
			<date>8/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995PASA...12..266E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;A...300..775M</bibcode>
			<title>Activity versus rotation in the extreme ultraviolet.</title>
			<authors>Mathioudakis, M.; Fruscione, A.; Drake, J. J.; McDonald, K.; Bowyer, S.; Malina, R. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.300, p.775</journal>
			<date>8/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26A...300..775M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995MNRAS.274.1165P</bibcode>
			<title>The ROSAT Wide Field Camera all-sky survey of extreme-ultraviolet sources - II. The 2RE Source Catalogue</title>
			<authors>Pye, J. P.; McGale, P. A.; Allan, D. J.; Barber, C. R.; Bertram, D.; Denby, M.; Page, C. G.; Ricketts, M. J.; Stewart, B. C.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 274, Issue 4, pp. 1165-1193.</journal>
			<date>6/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995MNRAS.274.1165P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995SSRv...72..499F</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Nearby Interstellar Matter</title>
			<authors>Frisch, Priscilla C.</authors>
			<journal>Space Science Reviews, Volume 72, Issue 3-4, pp. 499-592</journal>
			<date>5/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995SSRv...72..499F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995IBVS.4185....1P</bibcode>
			<title>Narrowing the Main Sequence Mass Gap</title>
			<authors>Popper, Daniel M.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4185, 1.</journal>
			<date>4/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995IBVS.4185....1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;A...296..477M</bibcode>
			<title>EUV spectroscopy of cool stars. I. The corona of alpha Centauri observed with EUVE. R</title>
			<authors>Mewe, R.; Kaastra, J. S.; Schrijver, C. J.; van den Oord, G. H. J.; Alkemade, F. J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.296, p.477</journal>
			<date>4/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26A...296..477M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995AJ....109.1327E</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric discriminate for GK dwarfs of disk populations</title>
			<authors>Eggen, Olin J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 109, no. 3, p. 1327-1345</journal>
			<date>3/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995AJ....109.1327E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;A...295..736B</bibcode>
			<title>Opacity sampling model photospheres for M dwarfs. I. Computations, sensitivities and comparisons.</title>
			<authors>Brett, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.295, p.736</journal>
			<date>3/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26A...295..736B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;A...295..678F</bibcode>
			<title>alpha Centauri and convection theories.</title>
			<authors>Fernandes, J.; Neuforge, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.295, p.678</journal>
			<date>3/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26A...295..678F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;A...294..515H</bibcode>
			<title>Coronal X-ray emission and rotation of cool main-sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Hempelmann, A.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Schultz, M.; Ruediger, G.; Stepien, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 294, no. 2, p. 515-524</journal>
			<date>2/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26A...294..515H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJS...96..223A</bibcode>
			<title>The RIASS coronathon: Joint X-ray and ultraviolet observations of normal F-K stars</title>
			<authors>Ayres, Thomas R.; Fleming, T. A.; Simon, T.; Haisch, B. M.; Brown, A.; Lenz, D.; Wamsteker, W.; de Martino, D.; Gonzalez, C.; Bonnell, J.; Mas-Hesse, J. M.; Rosso, C.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Truemper, J.; Voges, W.; Pye, J.; Dempsey, R. C.; Linsky, J. L.; Guinan, E. F.; Harper, G. M.; Jordan, C.; Montesinos, B. M.; Pagano, I.; Rodono, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 96, no. 1, p. 223-259</journal>
			<date>1/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJS...96..223A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994Obs...114..288C</bibcode>
			<title>An ultar-high-resolution search for interstellar Ca+ towards alpha Centauri A</title>
			<authors>Crawford, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Observatory, vol. 114, p. 288-293 (1994)</journal>
			<date>12/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994Obs...114..288C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994AAS...185.4503D</bibcode>
			<title>In Pursuit of the FIP Effect and Element Abundance Anomalies in Late-Type Stellar Coronae with EUVE</title>
			<authors>Drake, J. J.; Laming, J. M.; Widing, K. G.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 185th AAS Meeting, #45.03; &lt;ALTJOURNAL&gt;Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 26, p.1379&lt;/ALTJOURNAL&gt;</journal>
			<date>12/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994AAS...185.4503D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994A&amp;A...292..115A</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamics of nearby multiple stars. The alpha Centauri system</title>
			<authors>Anosova, J.; Orlov, V. V.; Pavlova, N. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 292, no. 1, p. 115-118</journal>
			<date>12/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994A%26A...292..115A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994A&amp;ARv...6...19G</bibcode>
			<title>Models of late-type stellar photospheres</title>
			<authors>Gustafsson, Bengt; Jorgensen, Uffe Grae</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Review (ISSN 0935-4956), vol. 6 no. 1-2, p. 19-65</journal>
			<date>11/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994A%26ARv...6...19G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994A&amp;A...289..899K</bibcode>
			<title>Doppler imaging with a CLEAN -- like approach. 2: A photospheric image of AB Doradus (=HD 36705)</title>
			<authors>Kuerster, M.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Cutispoto, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 289, no. 3, p. 899-921</journal>
			<date>9/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994A%26A...289..899K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994ApJS...94..127F</bibcode>
			<title>The distribution of neutral hydrogen in the interstellar medium. 1: The data</title>
			<authors>Fruscione, Antonella; Hawkins, Isabel; Jelinsky, Patrick; Wiercigroch, Alexandria</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, vol. 94, no. 1, p. 127-146</journal>
			<date>8/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994ApJS...94..127F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994Msngr..76...51K</bibcode>
			<title>A radial velocity search for extra-solar planets using an iodine gas absorption cell at the CAT+CES.</title>
			<authors>Krster, M.; Hatzes, A. P.; Cochran, W. D.; Pulliam, C. E.; Dennerl, K.; Dbereiner, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 76, p. 51-55</journal>
			<date>6/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994Msngr..76...51K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994ApJ...427.1013B</bibcode>
			<title>The effectiveness of oscillation frequencies in constraining stellar model parameters</title>
			<authors>Brown, Timothy M.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Weibel-Mihalas, Barbara; Gilliland, Ronald L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 427, no. 2, p. 1013-1034</journal>
			<date>6/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994ApJ...427.1013B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994PASP..106..452T</bibcode>
			<title>Analyses of archival data for cool dwarfs. 2: A catalog of temperatures</title>
			<authors>Taylor, Benjamin J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 106, no. 699, p. 452-461</journal>
			<date>5/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994PASP..106..452T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994A&amp;AS..104..429O</bibcode>
			<title>A large, complete, volume-limited sample of G-type dwarfs. I. Completion of Stroemgren UVBY photometry</title>
			<authors>Olsen, E. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Suppl. 104, 429-472 (1994)</journal>
			<date>5/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994A%26AS..104..429O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994MNRAS.267..840H</bibcode>
			<title>ROSAT Extreme Ultraviolet / EUV Luminosity Functions of Nearby Late Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Hodgkin, S. T.; Pye, J. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 267, NO. 4/APR15, P. 840, 1994</journal>
			<date>4/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994MNRAS.267..840H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994QJRAS..35....1M</bibcode>
			<title>The Close Approach of Stars in the Solar Neighborhood</title>
			<authors>Matthews, R. A. J.</authors>
			<journal>Quarterly Journal of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 35, NO. 1, P. 1, 1994</journal>
			<date>3/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994QJRAS..35....1M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994Ap&amp;SS.212..335H</bibcode>
			<title>The photometric method of extrasolar planet detection revisited</title>
			<authors>Hale, Alan; Doyle, Laurance R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, vol. 212, nos. 1-2, p. 335-348</journal>
			<date>2/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994Ap%26SS.212..335H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994PASP..106....1T</bibcode>
			<title>Astrophysics in 1993</title>
			<authors>Trimble, Virginia; Leonard, Peter J. T.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, vol. 106, no. 695, p. 1-24</journal>
			<date>1/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994PASP..106....1T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994KFNT...10b..68Z</bibcode>
			<title>The masses of the nearest stars.</title>
			<authors>Zakhozhaj, V. A.</authors>
			<journal>Kinematika Fiz. Nebesn. Tel., 10, part no 2, 68-73 (1994)</journal>
			<date>0/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994KFNT...10b..68Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994ARA&amp;A..32...37B</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>Brown, Timothy M.; Gilliland, Ronald L.</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 32, 1994, pp. 37-82.</journal>
			<date>0/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994ARA%26A..32...37B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993MNRAS.264..106J</bibcode>
			<title>The Kinematics of Active Late Type Stars Observed by the ROSAT Wide-Field Camera</title>
			<authors>Jeffries, R. D.; Jewell, S. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 264, NO. 1/SEP1, P. 106, 1993</journal>
			<date>9/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993MNRAS.264..106J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;A...276...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric Rotational Modulation in Solar-Like Stars - Part Two - Multicomponent Modelling and Rotational Period of Alpha-Centauri from CAII H Spectroscopic Variability</title>
			<authors>Char, S.; Foing, B. H.; Beckman, J.; Garcia-Lopez, R. J.; Rebolo, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Vol.276, NO. 1/SEPI, P. 78, 1993</journal>
			<date>9/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26A...276...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993ApJ...413..390L</bibcode>
			<title>A formulation of convection for stellar structure and evolution calculations without the mixing-length theory approximations. II - Application to Alpha Centauri A and B</title>
			<authors>Lydon, Thomas J.; Fox, Peter A.; Sofia, Sabatino</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 413, no. 1, p. 390-400.</journal>
			<date>8/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993ApJ...413..390L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993ApJ...413..349M</bibcode>
			<title>A search for substellar companions to southern solar-type stars</title>
			<authors>Murdoch, Kaylene A.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Clark, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 413, no. 1, p. 349-363.</journal>
			<date>8/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993ApJ...413..349M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993ApJ...412..797D</bibcode>
			<title>The fundamental parameters of the chromospherically active K2 dwarf Epsilon Eridani</title>
			<authors>Drake, Jeremy J.; Smith, Geoffrey</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 412, no. 2, p. 797-809.</journal>
			<date>8/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993ApJ...412..797D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993AJ....106..773H</bibcode>
			<title>The mass-luminosity relation for stars of mass 1.0 to 0.08 solar mass</title>
			<authors>Henry, Todd J.; McCarthy, Donald W., Jr.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 106, no. 2, p. 773-789.</journal>
			<date>8/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993AJ....106..773H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;AS..100..343P</bibcode>
			<title>The importance of surface inhomogeneities for K and M dwarf chromospheric fluxes</title>
			<authors>Panagi, P. M.; Mathioudakis, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 100, no. 2, p. 343-369.</journal>
			<date>8/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26AS..100..343P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993ApJ...412..312M</bibcode>
			<title>MG II and Ly-alpha fluxes in M dwarfs - Evaluation of an acoustic model</title>
			<authors>Mullan, D. J.; Cheng, Q. Q.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 412, no. 1, p. 312-323.</journal>
			<date>7/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993ApJ...412..312M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993MNRAS.262....1T</bibcode>
			<title>The chromospheres of late-type stars. II - an atlas of chromospheric lines for selected early-K stars</title>
			<authors>Thatcher, John D.; Robinson, Richard D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 262, no. 1, p. 1-19.</journal>
			<date>5/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993MNRAS.262....1T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993ApJ...408..305L</bibcode>
			<title>A catalog of stellar Lyman-alpha fluxes</title>
			<authors>Landsman, Wayne; Simon, Theodore</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 408, no. 1, p. 305-322.</journal>
			<date>5/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993ApJ...408..305L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993AAS...182.5605L</bibcode>
			<title>The Application of Numerical Simulations of Convection to Stellar Interiors</title>
			<authors>Lydon, T. J.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 182nd AAS Meeting, #56.05D; &lt;ALTJOURNAL&gt;Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 25, p.895&lt;/ALTJOURNAL&gt;</journal>
			<date>5/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993AAS...182.5605L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993Obs...113...79M</bibcode>
			<title>The spectroscopic mass ratio of the Alpha CEN system</title>
			<authors>Murdoch, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Observatory, vol. 113, p. 79-81 (1993)</journal>
			<date>4/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993Obs...113...79M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993MNRAS.261L...5M</bibcode>
			<title>Is Proxima really in orbit about Alpha CEN A/B?</title>
			<authors>Matthews, Robert; Gilmore, Gerard</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 261, no. 2, p. L5-L7.</journal>
			<date>3/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993MNRAS.261L...5M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;A...269..446S</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic activity in dwarf stars with shallow convective envelopes</title>
			<authors>Schrijver, C. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 269, no. 1-2, p. 446-456.</journal>
			<date>3/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26A...269..446S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993ApJ...403L..79L</bibcode>
			<title>Improved solar models constructed with a formulation of convection for stellar structure and evolution calculations without the mixing-length theory approximations</title>
			<authors>Lydon, Thomas J.; Fox, Peter A.; Sofia, Sabatino</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 2 - Letters (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 403, no. 2, p. L79-L82.</journal>
			<date>2/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993ApJ...403L..79L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993MNRAS.260...77P</bibcode>
			<title>The ROSAT Wide Field Camera all-sky survey of extreme-ultraviolet sources. I - The Bright Source Catalogue</title>
			<authors>Pounds, K. A.; Allan, D. J.; Barber, C.; Barstow, M. A.; Bertram, D.; Branduardi-Raymont, G.; Brebner, G. E. C.; Buckley, D.; Bromage, G. E.; Cole, R. E.; Courtier, M.; Cruise, A. M.; Culhane, J. L.; Denby, M.; Donoghue, D. O.; Dunford, E.; Georgantopoulos, I.; Goodall, C. V.; Gondhalekar, P. M.; Gourlay, J. A.; Harris, A. W.; Hassall, B. J. M.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S.; Jeffries, R. D.; Kellett, B. J.; Kent, B. J.; Lieu, R.; Lloyd, C.; McGale, P.; Mason, K. O.; Matthews, L.; Mittaz, J. P. D.; Page, C. G.; Pankiewicz, G. S.; Pike, C. D.; Ponman, T. J.; Puchnarewicz, E. M.; Pye, J. P.; Quenby, J. J.; Ricketts, M. J.; Rosen, S. R.; Sansom, A. E.; Sembay, S.; Sidher, S.; Sims, M. R.; Stewart, B. C.; Sumner, T. J.; Vallance, R. J.; Watson, M. G.; Warwick, R. S.; Wells, A. A.; Willingale, R.; Willmore, A. P.; Willoughby, G. A.; Wonnacott, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 260, no. 1, p. 77-102.</journal>
			<date>1/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993MNRAS.260...77P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993ApJ...402..694L</bibcode>
			<title>Goddard high-resolution spectrograph observations of the local interstellar medium and the deuterium/hydrogen ratio along the line of sight toward Capella</title>
			<authors>Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Brown, Alexander; Gayley, Ken; Diplas, Athanassios; Savage, Blair D.; Ayres, Thomas R.; Landsman, Wayne; Shore, Steven N.; Heap, Sara R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 402, no. 2, p. 694-709.</journal>
			<date>1/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993ApJ...402..694L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992Msngr..70...37C</bibcode>
			<title>The contribution of detailed analyses of F, G and K stars to the knowledge of the stellar populations of the galactic disk.</title>
			<authors>Cayrel de Strobel, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 70, p. 37-42</journal>
			<date>12/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992Msngr..70...37C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992Ap&amp;SS.197...35E</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray VS He II lambda 1640 A correlation of II Peg</title>
			<authors>Esendemir, A.; Alev, H. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science (ISSN 0004-640X), vol. 197, no. 1, p. 35-41.</journal>
			<date>11/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992Ap%26SS.197...35E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;AS...95..273C</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of Fe/H determinations - 1991 edition</title>
			<authors>Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Hauck, B.; Francois, P.; Thevenin, F.; Friel, E.; Mermilliod, M.; Borde, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 95, no. 2, p. 273-336.</journal>
			<date>10/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26AS...95..273C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992AJ....104.1248E</bibcode>
			<title>Analytic approximations to the 2-60 microns infrared continua for standard calibration stars - With application to the calibration of spectroscopy and photometry, and the determination of effective temperature and angular size from IR measurements</title>
			<authors>Engelke, C. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 104, no. 3, Sept. 1992, p. 1248-1259.</journal>
			<date>9/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992AJ....104.1248E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;A...263..219C</bibcode>
			<title>The 1992 detailed analyses of Alpha Centauri A and Alpha Centauri B</title>
			<authors>Chmielewski, Y.; Friel, E.; Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Bentolila, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 263, no. 1-2, p. 219-231.</journal>
			<date>9/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26A...263..219C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;A...262..195G</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheres of late-type active and quiescent dwarfs. III - Variability of CA II H emission profiles</title>
			<authors>Garcia Lopez, R. J.; Crivellari, L.; Beckman, J. E.; Rebolo, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 262, no. 1, p. 195-208.</journal>
			<date>8/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26A...262..195G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;A...261..499S</bibcode>
			<title>An optical search for Beta Pictoris-like disks around nearby stars</title>
			<authors>Smith, B. A.; Fountain, J. W.; Terrile, R. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 261, no. 2, p. 499-502.</journal>
			<date>8/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26A...261..499S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992MNRAS.257..105B</bibcode>
			<title>A narrow-band search for extraterrestrial intelligence (SETI) using the interstellar contact channel hypothesis</title>
			<authors>Blair, D. G.; Norris, R. P.; Troup, E. R.; Twardy, R.; Wellington, K. J.; Williams, A. J.; Wright, A. E.; Zadnik, M. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 257, no. 1, July 1, 1992, p. 105-109.</journal>
			<date>7/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992MNRAS.257..105B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJ...394..313E</bibcode>
			<title>Evolutionary models and the p-mode oscillation spectrum of Alpha Centauri A and B</title>
			<authors>Edmonds, Peter; Cram, Lawrence; Demarque, Pierre; Guenther, D. B.; Pinsonneault, Marc H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 394, no. 1, July 20, 1992, p. 313-319.</journal>
			<date>7/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJ...394..313E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;A...259..543M</bibcode>
			<title>The age of the Galaxy from thorium in G dwarfs, a re-analysis</title>
			<authors>Morell, O.; Kallander, D.; Butcher, H. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 259, no. 2, p. 543-548.</journal>
			<date>6/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26A...259..543M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992BICDS..40...71P</bibcode>
			<title>Some revisions to the Bright Star Catalogue and its supplement</title>
			<authors>Peters, A. R.; Hoffleit, D. E.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin d'Information du Centre de Donnees Stellaires, Vol. 40, p.71</journal>
			<date>1/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992BICDS..40...71P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;A...253..185P</bibcode>
			<title>Lithium in RS CVn binaries and related chromospherically active stars. I - Observational results</title>
			<authors>Pallavicini, R.; Randich, S.; Giampapa, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 253, no. 1, Jan. 1992, p. 185-198. Research supported by ASI and MURST.</journal>
			<date>1/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26A...253..185P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991Ap&amp;SS.186..169M</bibcode>
			<title>High precision radial velocities of southern solar-type stars by cross-correlation</title>
			<authors>Murdoch, Kaylene; Hearnshaw, J. B.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science (ISSN 0004-640X), vol. 186, no. 2, Dec. 1991, p. 169-177.</journal>
			<date>12/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991Ap%26SS.186..169M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991A&amp;A...252..203R</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic structure in cool stars. XVII - Minimum radiative losses from the outer atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Rutten, R. G. M.; Schrijver, C. J.; Lemmens, A. F. P.; Zwaan, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 252, no. 1, Dec. 1991, p. 203-219. Research supported by ASTRON and NWO.</journal>
			<date>12/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991A%26A...252..203R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991A&amp;A...252..123A</bibcode>
			<title>The dynamical evolution of the nearby multiple stellar systems ADS 48, ADS 6175 (Alpha Geminorum = Castor), Alpha Centauri, and ADS 9909 (Xi Scorpii)</title>
			<authors>Anosova, J. P.; Orlov, V. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 252, no. 1, Dec. 1991, p. 123-126.</journal>
			<date>12/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991A%26A...252..123A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991A&amp;A...251..199P</bibcode>
			<title>H-alpha absolute chromospheric fluxes in G and K dwarfs and subgiants</title>
			<authors>Pasquini, L.; Pallavicini, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 251, no. 1, Nov. 1991, p. 199-209.</journal>
			<date>11/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991A%26A...251..199P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991ApJ...380..200S</bibcode>
			<title>The onset of chromospheric activity among the A and F stars</title>
			<authors>Simon, Theodore; Landsman, Wayne</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 380, Oct. 10, 1991, p. 200-207.</journal>
			<date>10/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991ApJ...380..200S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991MNRAS.252P..21J</bibcode>
			<title>The dependence of coronal temperatures on Rossby numbers</title>
			<authors>Jordan, C.; Montesinos, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 252, Sept. 15, 1991, p. 21P-26P.</journal>
			<date>9/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991MNRAS.252P..21J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991ApJ...376L..45A</bibcode>
			<title>Digging in the coronal graveyard - A ROSAT observation of the red giant Arcturus</title>
			<authors>Ayres, Thomas R.; Fleming, Thomas A.; Schmitt, Juergen H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 2 - Letters (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 376, Aug. 1, 1991, p. L45-L48. Research supported by NASA.</journal>
			<date>8/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991ApJ...376L..45A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991ApJ...375..722S</bibcode>
			<title>The chromospheric emission-age relation for stars of the lower main sequence and its implications for the star formation rate</title>
			<authors>Soderblom, David R.; Duncan, Douglas K.; Johnson, Dean R. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 375, July 10, 1991, p. 722-739. Research supported by NSF and National Geographic Society.</journal>
			<date>7/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991ApJ...375..722S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991ApJ...375..716H</bibcode>
			<title>Absolute far-ultraviolet spectrophotometry of hot subluminous stars from Voyager</title>
			<authors>Holberg, J. B.; Ali, B.; Carone, T. E.; Polidan, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 375, July 10, 1991, p. 716-721.</journal>
			<date>7/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991ApJ...375..716H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991A&amp;A...247...91N</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of the Alpha Centauri system - Metallicity and age</title>
			<authors>Noels, A.; Grevesse, N.; Magain, P.; Neuforge, C.; Baglin, A.; Lebreton, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 247, no. 1, July 1991, p. 91-94.</journal>
			<date>7/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991A%26A...247...91N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991Ast....19d..28C</bibcode>
			<title>Does Alpha Centauri have intelligent life?</title>
			<authors>Croswell, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy, Vol. 19, No. 4, p. 28 - 37</journal>
			<date>0/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991Ast....19d..28C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990Ap&amp;SS.170..109G</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric variability in late-type dwarfs from high-resolution spectra of CA II H</title>
			<authors>Garcia Lopez, R. J.; Rebolo, R.; Beckman, J. E.; Crivellari, L.</authors>
			<journal>&lt;CONF_METADATA&gt;IAU, European Regional Astronomy Meeting, 11th, La Laguna, Spain, July 3-8, 1989&lt;/CONF_METADATA&gt; Astrophysics and Space Science (ISSN 0004-640X), vol. 170, no. 1-2, Aug. 1990, p. 109-111.</journal>
			<date>8/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990Ap%26SS.170..109G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990JRASC..84..175D</bibcode>
			<title>The local space density of thick disk stars</title>
			<authors>Dawson, P. C.</authors>
			<journal>Journal of the Royal Astronomical Society of Canada (ISSN 0035-872X), vol. 84, June 1990, p. 175-190.</journal>
			<date>6/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990JRASC..84..175D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990A&amp;AS...83..357B</bibcode>
			<title>BVRI photometry of the Gliese Catalogue stars</title>
			<authors>Bessel, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 83, no. 2, May 1990, p. 357-378.</journal>
			<date>5/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990A%26AS...83..357B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990ApJ...350..827F</bibcode>
			<title>An abundance analysis of Alpha Centauri A</title>
			<authors>Furenlid, Ingemar; Meylan, Tom</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 350, Feb. 20, 1990, p. 827-838.</journal>
			<date>2/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990ApJ...350..827F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990A&amp;A...228..218D</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar granulation. VI - Four-component models and non-solar-type stars</title>
			<authors>Dravins, Dainis</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 228, no. 1, Feb. 1990, p. 218-230. Research supported by NFR.</journal>
			<date>2/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990A%26A...228..218D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990A&amp;A...228..203D</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Granulation - Part Five - Synthetic Spectral Lines in Disk Integrated Starlight</title>
			<authors>Dravins, D.; Nordlund, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Vol. 228, NO. 1/FEB(I), P. 203, 1990</journal>
			<date>2/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990A%26A...228..203D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990A&amp;A...228..184D</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Granulation - Part Four - Line Formation in Inhomogeneous Stellar Photospheres</title>
			<authors>Dravins, D.; Nordlund, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Vol. 228, NO. 1/FEB(I), P. 184, 1990</journal>
			<date>2/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990A%26A...228..184D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990A&amp;A...228..155N</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar granulation. III - Hydrodynamic model atmospheres. IV - Line formation in inhomogeneous stellar photospheres. V - Synthetic spectral lines in disk-integrated starlight</title>
			<authors>Nordlund, A.; Dravins, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 228, no. 1, Feb. 1990, p. 155-217. Research supported by NFR, SNFO, and Danish Space Board.</journal>
			<date>2/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990A%26A...228..155N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990MmSAI..61..513D</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar granulation</title>
			<authors>Dravins, Dainis</authors>
			<journal>Societ Astronomica Italiana, Memorie (ISSN 0037-8720), vol. 61, no. 3, 1990, p. 513-526. NFR-supported research.</journal>
			<date>0/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990MmSAI..61..513D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989ApJ...347..998E</bibcode>
			<title>The distribution of visual binaries with two bright components</title>
			<authors>Eggleton, Peter P.; Fitchett, Michael J.; Tout, Christopher A.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 347, Dec. 15, 1989, p. 998-1011. Research supported by the Canadian Institute for Theoretical Astrophysics, Space Telescope Science Institute, and SERC.</journal>
			<date>12/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989ApJ...347..998E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989A&amp;AS...80..189F</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheres of late-type active and quiescent dwarfs. II - an activity index derived from profiles of the CA II 8498 A and 8542 A triplet lines</title>
			<authors>Foing, B. H.; Crivellari, L.; Vladilo, G.; Rebolo, R.; Beckman, J. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 80, no. 2, Oct. 1989, p. 189-200. Research supported by EEC.</journal>
			<date>10/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989A%26AS...80..189F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989A&amp;AS...80..135R</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheres of late-type active and quiescent dwarfs. I - an atlas of high resolution CA II H profiles</title>
			<authors>Rebolo, R.; Garcia Lopez, R.; Beckman, J. E.; Vladilo, G.; Foing, B. H.; Crivellari, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 80, no. 2, Oct. 1989, p. 135-148. Research supported by EEC.</journal>
			<date>10/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989A%26AS...80..135R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989A&amp;A...224..179M</bibcode>
			<title>Flux-flux relation - MG II H and K versus X-rays in dwarf M and K stars</title>
			<authors>Mathioudakis, M.; Doyle, J. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 224, no. 1-2, Oct. 1989, p. 179-186.</journal>
			<date>10/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989A%26A...224..179M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989A&amp;A...223..361B</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary orbits in the elliptic restricted problem. II - The Sirius system</title>
			<authors>Benest, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 223, no. 1-2, Oct. 1989, p. 361-364.</journal>
			<date>10/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989A%26A...223..361B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989ApJ...342..945S</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling Epsilon Eridani and its oscillations</title>
			<authors>Soderblom, David R.; Dappen, Werner</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 342, July 15, 1989, p. 945-950.</journal>
			<date>7/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989ApJ...342..945S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989A&amp;A...216..139S</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray emission from acoustically heated coronae</title>
			<authors>Stepien, K.; Ulmschneider, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 216, no. 1-2, June 1989, p. 139-142.</journal>
			<date>6/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989A%26A...216..139S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989A&amp;A...213..226C</bibcode>
			<title>A comparison of solar and stellar ultraviolet spectra obtained with SKYLAB and IUE</title>
			<authors>Cappelli, A.; Cerruti-Sola, M.; Pallavicini, R.; Cheng, C. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 213, no. 1-2, April 1989, p. 226-244. Research supported by CNR.</journal>
			<date>4/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989A%26A...213..226C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989Mercu..18....2T</bibcode>
			<title>Dark matter in our Galaxy.</title>
			<authors>Tucker, Wallace; Tucker, Karen</authors>
			<journal>Mercury (ISSN 0047-6773), vol. 18, Jan.-Feb. 1989, p. 2-11.</journal>
			<date>2/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989Mercu..18....2T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989ApJ...336..949M</bibcode>
			<title>IUE observations of the interstellar medium toward Beta Geminorum</title>
			<authors>Murthy, J.; Wofford, J. B.; Henry, R. C.; Moos, H. W.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Linsky, J. L.; Gry, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 336, Jan. 15, 1989, p. 949-953.</journal>
			<date>1/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989ApJ...336..949M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988A&amp;A...206..143B</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary orbits in the elliptic restricted problem. I - The Alpha Centauri system</title>
			<authors>Benest, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 206, no. 1, Nov. 1988, p. 143-146.</journal>
			<date>11/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988A%26A...206..143B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988A&amp;A...206..100A</bibcode>
			<title>Abundances of light metals and NI in a sample of disc stars</title>
			<authors>Abia, C.; Rebolo, R.; Beckman, J. E.; Crivellari, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 206, no. 1, Nov. 1988, p. 100-107. Research supported by the Consejo Superior de Investigaciones Cientificas and CNR.</journal>
			<date>11/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988A%26A...206..100A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988IrAJ...18..257F</bibcode>
			<title>Solar-like activity in late-type stars</title>
			<authors>Foing, Bernard H.</authors>
			<journal>&lt;CONF_METADATA&gt;Astronomocal Science Group of Ireland, Meeting, University College, Cork, Republic of Ireland, Mar. 31, 1988&lt;/CONF_METADATA&gt; Irish Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0021-1052), vol. 18, Sept. 1988, p. 257-265. Research supported by NBS and Lockheed Independent Research Program.</journal>
			<date>9/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988IrAJ...18..257F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988ApJ...329..253W</bibcode>
			<title>Search for wide binaries in the Yale Bright Star Catalogue</title>
			<authors>Weinberg, Martin D.; Wasserman, Ira</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 329, June 1, 1988, p. 253-275. Research supported by Siemens Corp.</journal>
			<date>6/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988ApJ...329..253W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988Msngr..51...12B</bibcode>
			<title>Galactic chronometry with the Coud Echelle Scanner.</title>
			<authors>Butcher, H.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 51, p. 12-15</journal>
			<date>3/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988Msngr..51...12B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988Ap&amp;SS.142...49G</bibcode>
			<title>The third catalogue of nearby stars with special emphasis on wide binaries</title>
			<authors>Gliese, W.; Jahreiss, H.</authors>
			<journal>&lt;CONF_METADATA&gt;IAU, Colloquium on Wide Components in Double and Multiple Stars, 97th, Brussels, Belgium, June 8-13, 1987&lt;/CONF_METADATA&gt; Astrophysics and Space Science (ISSN 0004-640X), vol. 142, no. 1-2, March 1988, p. 49-56; Discussion, p. 56.</journal>
			<date>3/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988Ap%26SS.142...49G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988MNRAS.230..573M</bibcode>
			<title>Isotopic magnesium abundances in stars</title>
			<authors>McWilliam, Andrew; Lambert, David L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 230, Feb. 15, 1988, p. 573-585. Research supported by the Robert A. Welch Foundation.</journal>
			<date>2/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988MNRAS.230..573M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988ApJS...66...51A</bibcode>
			<title>Redshifts of high-temperature emission lines in the far-ultraviolet spectra of late-type stars. II - New, precise measurements of dwarfs and giants</title>
			<authors>Ayres, Thomas R.; Jensen, Eberhard; Engvold, Oddbjorn</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 66, Feb. 1988, p. 51-68.</journal>
			<date>2/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988ApJS...66...51A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988A&amp;A...191..253P</bibcode>
			<title>CA II absolute line profiles of southern late-type stars</title>
			<authors>Pasquini, L.; Pallavicini, R.; Pakull, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 191, no. 2, Feb. 1988, p. 253-266.</journal>
			<date>2/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988A%26A...191..253P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988A&amp;A...190..148E</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic surface gravities and chemical compositions for 8 nearby single sub-giants</title>
			<authors>Edvardsson, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 190, no. 1-2, Jan. 1988, p. 148-166.</journal>
			<date>1/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988A%26A...190..148E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988RvPD...16...16P</bibcode>
			<title>L'activite d'origine magnetique dans les etoiles.</title>
			<authors>Praderie, F.</authors>
			<journal>Revue du Palais de la Decouverte, Vol. 16, p. 16-37 (1988)</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988RvPD...16...16P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988PASJ...40..475W</bibcode>
			<title>An indication of extended chromospheres in line width-luminosity relations</title>
			<authors>Watanabe, Tetsuya</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of Japan, Publications (ISSN 0004-6264), vol. 40, no. 4, 1988, p. 475-490.</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988PASJ...40..475W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988IUEEN..29...45.</bibcode>
			<title>Merged log of IUE observations.</title>
			<authors>:Anonymous</authors>
			<journal>IUE ESA Newsletter, Vol. 29, p. 45-98 (1988)</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988IUEEN..29...45.</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988IAUS..132..387E</bibcode>
			<title>Accurate Spectroscopic Surface Gravities for 8 Sub-Giants</title>
			<authors>Edvardsson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Impact of Very High S/N Spectroscopy on Stellar Physics: Proceedings of the 132nd Symposium of the International Astronomical Union held in Paris, France, June 29-July 3, 1987.   Edited by G. Cayrel de Strobel and Monique Spite.  International Astronomical Union. Symposium no. 132, Kluwer Academic Publishers, Dordrecht., p.387</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988IAUS..132..387E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988IAUS..132..355F</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Data Reduction Techniques for the ESO CES Plus RETICON Spectra</title>
			<authors>Foing, B. H.; Crivellari, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Impact of Very High S/N Spectroscopy on Stellar Physics: Proceedings of the 132nd Symposium of the International Astronomical Union held in Paris, France, June 29-July 3, 1987.   Edited by G. Cayrel de Strobel and Monique Spite.  International Astronomical Union. Symposium no. 132, Kluwer Academic Publishers, Dordrecht., p.355</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988IAUS..132..355F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988IAUS..132..287F</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic Variability in Late-Type Dwarfs Using High S/n Spectra</title>
			<authors>Foing, B. H.; Beckman, J. E.; Vladilo, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Impact of Very High S/N Spectroscopy on Stellar Physics: Proceedings of the 132nd Symposium of the International Astronomical Union held in Paris, France, June 29-July 3, 1987.   Edited by G. Cayrel de Strobel and Monique Spite.  International Astronomical Union. Symposium no. 132, Kluwer Academic Publishers, Dordrecht., p.287</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988IAUS..132..287F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988IAUS..132..279B</bibcode>
			<title>Light Elements as Probes of Stellar Interiors</title>
			<authors>Baglin, A.; Morel, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Impact of Very High S/N Spectroscopy on Stellar Physics: Proceedings of the 132nd Symposium of the International Astronomical Union held in Paris, France, June 29-July 3, 1987.   Edited by G. Cayrel de Strobel and Monique Spite.  International Astronomical Union. Symposium no. 132, Kluwer Academic Publishers, Dordrecht., p.279</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988IAUS..132..279B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988IAUS..132..239D</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Granulation and Photospheric Line Asymmetries</title>
			<authors>Dravins, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Impact of Very High S/N Spectroscopy on Stellar Physics: Proceedings of the 132nd Symposium of the International Astronomical Union held in Paris, France, June 29-July 3, 1987.   Edited by G. Cayrel de Strobel and Monique Spite.  International Astronomical Union. Symposium no. 132, Kluwer Academic Publishers, Dordrecht., p.239</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988IAUS..132..239D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988IAUS..132..153C</bibcode>
			<title>A Method for Calibrating, in Absolute Flux Units, CA II H Profiles of Late Type Stars Observed at ESO</title>
			<authors>Castelli, F.; Gouttebroze, P.; Beckman, J.; Crivellari, L.; Foing, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Impact of Very High S/N Spectroscopy on Stellar Physics: Proceedings of the 132nd Symposium of the International Astronomical Union held in Paris, France, June 29-July 3, 1987.   Edited by G. Cayrel de Strobel and Monique Spite.  International Astronomical Union. Symposium no. 132, Kluwer Academic Publishers, Dordrecht., p.153</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988IAUS..132..153C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987PASP...99.1344S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectral differential imaging detection of planets about nearby stars</title>
			<authors>Smith, W. Hayden</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 99, Dec. 1987, p. 1344-1353.</journal>
			<date>12/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987PASP...99.1344S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987MNRAS.229..627M</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of the connection between internal magnetic fields and chromospheric activity in late-type stars</title>
			<authors>Montesinos, B.; Fernandez-Figueroa, M. J.; de Castro, E.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 229, Dec. 15, 1987, p. 627-641. Research supported by the Ministerio de Educacion y Ciencia of Spain.</journal>
			<date>12/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987MNRAS.229..627M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987AZh....64.1243K</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray emission and structure of coronas of active late-type dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Katsova, M. M.; Badalyan, O. G.; Livshits, M. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomicheskii Zhurnal (ISSN 0004-6299), vol. 64, Nov.-Dec. 1987, p. 1243-1255. In Russian.</journal>
			<date>12/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987AZh....64.1243K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987JHA....18..233E</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origin of the Ptolemaic Star Catalogue - Part Two</title>
			<authors>Evans, J.</authors>
			<journal>Journal for the History of Astronomy, Vol.18, NO. 4/NOV, P.233, 1987</journal>
			<date>11/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987JHA....18..233E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987Natur.328..127B</bibcode>
			<title>Thorium in G-dwarf stars as a chronometer for the Galaxy</title>
			<authors>Butcher, H. R.</authors>
			<journal>Nature (ISSN 0028-0836), vol. 328, July 9, 1987, p. 127-131.</journal>
			<date>7/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987Natur.328..127B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987JApA....8..141C</bibcode>
			<title>On a possible metallicity gradient in SMR stars</title>
			<authors>Cayrel de Strobel, G.</authors>
			<journal>&lt;CONF_METADATA&gt;IAU, Meeting on Nucleosynthesis in the Galaxy from the Study of Low-mass Stars, New Delhi, India, Nov. 27, 1985&lt;/CONF_METADATA&gt; Journal of Astrophysics and Astronomy (ISSN 0250-6335), vol. 8, June 1987, p. 141-145.</journal>
			<date>6/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987JApA....8..141C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;AS...69..465K</bibcode>
			<title>Spectrophotometry of bright F-, G-, K- and M-type stars. I - Measurements of 60 southern and equatorial stars</title>
			<authors>Kiehling, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 69, no. 3, June 1987, p. 465-485.</journal>
			<date>6/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26AS...69..465K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;A...178..179G</bibcode>
			<title>Light element and NI abundance in field disk and halo stars</title>
			<authors>Gratton, R. G.; Sneden, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 178, no. 1-2, May 1987, p. 179-193. CNR-supported research.</journal>
			<date>5/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26A...178..179G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;A...177..155R</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic structure in cool stars. XIII - Appropriate units for the rotation-activity relation</title>
			<authors>Rutten, R. G. M.; Schrijver, C. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 177, no. 1-2, May 1987, p. 155-162. Research supported by the Stichting Astronomisch Onderzoek in Nederland and ZWO.</journal>
			<date>5/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26A...177..155R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987MNRAS.225..903J</bibcode>
			<title>The chromospheres and coronae of five G-K main-sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Jordan, C.; Ayres, T. R.; Brown, A.; Linsky, J. L.; Simon, T.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 225, April 15, 1987, p. 903-937. SERC-supported research.</journal>
			<date>4/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987MNRAS.225..903J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987ApJ...315..675M</bibcode>
			<title>IUE observations of hydrogen and deuterium in the local interstellar medium</title>
			<authors>Murthy, J.; Henry, R. C.; Moos, H. W.; Landsman, W. B.; Linsky, J. L.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Gry, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 315, April 15, 1987, p. 675-686.</journal>
			<date>4/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987ApJ...315..675M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;AS...68..259H</bibcode>
			<title>Narrow-band photometry of late-type stars. II</title>
			<authors>Haggkvist, L.; Oja, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 68, no. 2, March 1987, p. 259-282.</journal>
			<date>3/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26AS...68..259H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;AS...68..193G</bibcode>
			<title>Equivalent widths for field halo and disk stars</title>
			<authors>Gratton, R. G.; Sneden, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 68, no. 2, March 1987, p. 193-210.</journal>
			<date>3/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26AS...68..193G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;A...174..127C</bibcode>
			<title>CA II H emission line cores of late-type dwarfs - Variability measurements and velocity field diagnostics</title>
			<authors>Crivellari, L.; Vladilo, G.; Beckman, J. E.; Foing, B. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 174, no. 1-2, March 1987, p. 127-138.</journal>
			<date>3/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26A...174..127C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987AJ.....93..393E</bibcode>
			<title>Luminosities, abundances, and motions of stars brighter than visual magnitude 15.1 and annual proper motions larger than one-half arcsecond</title>
			<authors>Eggen, Olin J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 93, Feb. 1987, p. 393-420.</journal>
			<date>2/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987AJ.....93..393E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;A...172..251B</bibcode>
			<title>Magnesium isotopes in super-metal-rich stars</title>
			<authors>Barbuy, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 172, no. 1-2, Jan. 1987, p. 251-256. Research supported by the Fundacao de Amparo a Pesquisa do Estado de Sao Paulo.</journal>
			<date>1/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26A...172..251B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;A...172..211D</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Granulation - Part Two - Stellar Photospheric Line Asymmetries</title>
			<authors>Dravins, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Vol.172, NO. 1/2/JAN, P. 211, 1987</journal>
			<date>1/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26A...172..211D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;A...172..111S</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic structure in cool stars. XI - Relations between radiative fluxes measuring stellar activity, and evidence for two components in stellar chromospheres</title>
			<authors>Schrijver, C. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 172, no. 1-2, Jan. 1987, p. 111-123.</journal>
			<date>1/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26A...172..111S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987LNP...291..146J</bibcode>
			<title>Relations Between Chromospheric and Coronal Structure, Flux-Flux Correlations and Convective Zone Properties</title>
			<authors>Jordan, C.; Montesinos, B.</authors>
			<journal>Cool Stars, Stellar Systems and the Sun, Proceedings of the Fifth Cambridge Workshop held in Boulder, Colo., 8-11 Jul. 1987.  Lecture Notes in Physics, Vol. 291, edited by J. L. Linsky and R. E. Stencel. Springer-Verlag, Berlin, 1987., p.146</journal>
			<date>0/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987LNP...291..146J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987LNP...291...21M</bibcode>
			<title>Flux Tube Dynamics and Solar/Stellar Redshift Measurements (Invited review)</title>
			<authors>Mariska, J. T.</authors>
			<journal>Cool Stars, Stellar Systems and the Sun, Proceedings of the Fifth Cambridge Workshop held in Boulder, Colo., 8-11 Jul. 1987.  Lecture Notes in Physics, Vol. 291, edited by J. L. Linsky and R. E. Stencel. Springer-Verlag, Berlin, 1987., p.21</journal>
			<date>0/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987LNP...291...21M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986AJ.....92..910E</bibcode>
			<title>Large and kinematically unbiased samples of G and K type stars. I - The dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 92, Oct. 1986, p. 910-951.</journal>
			<date>10/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986AJ.....92..910E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986ESASP.263..669N</bibcode>
			<title>Correcting observed stellar Lyman alpha profiles for the effects of interstellar absorption and geocoronal emission</title>
			<authors>Neff, J. E.; Linsky, J. L.; Landsman, W. B.; Carpenter, K. G.</authors>
			<journal>In ESA Proceedings of an International Symposium on New Insights in Astrophysics. Eight Years of UV Astronomy with IUE  p 669-672 (SEE N87-19150 11-88)</journal>
			<date>9/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986ESASP.263..669N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986ESASP.263..555H</bibcode>
			<title>IUE study of the very local interstellar medium</title>
			<authors>Henry, R. C.; Murthy, J.; Moos, H. W.; Landsman, W. B.; Linsky, J. L.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Gry, C.</authors>
			<journal>In ESA Proceedings of an International Symposium on New Insights in Astrophysics. Eight Years of UV Astronomy with IUE  p 555-558 (SEE N87-19150 11-88)</journal>
			<date>9/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986ESASP.263..555H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986ESASP.263...17J</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheres of cool stars</title>
			<authors>Jordan, C.</authors>
			<journal>In ESA Proceedings of an International Symposium on New Insights in Astrophysics. Eight Years of UV Astronomy with IUE  p 17-13 (SEE N87-19150 11-88)</journal>
			<date>9/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986ESASP.263...17J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986A&amp;A...166..195R</bibcode>
			<title>Lithium abundances and Li-7/Li-6 ratios in late-type population I field dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Rebolo, R.; Beckman, J. E.; Crivellari, L.; Castelli, F.; Foing, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 166, no. 1-2, Sept. 1986, p. 195-203. Research supported by the Consejo Superior de Investigaciones Cientificas and CNR.</journal>
			<date>9/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986A%26A...166..195R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986A&amp;A...165..126S</bibcode>
			<title>Non-resonance lines of neutral calcium in the spectra of the Alpha Centauri binary system</title>
			<authors>Smith, G.; Edvardsson, B.; Frisk, U.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 165, no. 1-2, Sept. 1986, p. 126-134.</journal>
			<date>9/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986A%26A...165..126S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986S&amp;T....72..130K</bibcode>
			<title>The K stars - Orange giants and dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Kaler, J. B.</authors>
			<journal>Sky and Telescope (ISSN 0037-6604), vol. 72, Aug. 1986, p. 130-133.</journal>
			<date>8/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986S%26T....72..130K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986BAAS...18..810B</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Orbits in the alpha Centauri System</title>
			<authors>Benest, D.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 18, p.810</journal>
			<date>6/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986BAAS...18..810B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986ApJ...303..791L</bibcode>
			<title>IUE observations of interstellar hydrogen and deuterium toward Alpha Centauri B</title>
			<authors>Landsman, W. B.; Murthy, J.; Henry, R. C.; Moos, H. W.; Linsky, J. L.; Russell, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 303, April 15, 1986, p. 791-796.</journal>
			<date>4/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986ApJ...303..791L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986A&amp;A...158..273S</bibcode>
			<title>The temperatures of Alpha Centauri A and B</title>
			<authors>Soderblom, D. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 158, no. 1-2, April 1986, p. 273, 274.</journal>
			<date>4/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986A%26A...158..273S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986A&amp;A...157..278B</bibcode>
			<title>Rotational braking of late-type main sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Bohigas, J.; Carrasco, L.; Torres, C. A. O.; Quast, G. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 157, no. 2, March 1986, p. 278-292.</journal>
			<date>3/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986A%26A...157..278B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986ApJ...300..773D</bibcode>
			<title>The case of Alpha Centauri - Mass, age and p-mode oscillation spectrum</title>
			<authors>Demarque, P.; Guenther, D. B.; van Altena, W. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 300, Jan. 15, 1986, p. 773-778.</journal>
			<date>1/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986ApJ...300..773D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986A&amp;A...154..185O</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic structure in cool stars. IX - Ultraviolet emission lines from chromospheres and transition regions</title>
			<authors>Oranje, B. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 154, no. 1-2, Jan. 1986, p. 185-196. Research supported by the Stichting Astronomisch Onderzoek in Nederland and ZWO.</journal>
			<date>1/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986A%26A...154..185O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985Msngr..41...18F</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric modelling in late-type dwarfs. II - CES observations of active and quiescent stars</title>
			<authors>Foing, B. H.; Beckman, J.; Crivellari, L.; Galleguillos, D.</authors>
			<journal>ESO Messenger (ISSN 0722-6691), no. 41, Sept. 1985, p. 18-22.</journal>
			<date>9/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985Msngr..41...18F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985ApJS...57..389L</bibcode>
			<title>Abundances in field dwarf stars. I - Atmospheric parameters</title>
			<authors>Laird, J. B.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 57, Feb. 1985, p. 389-404.</journal>
			<date>2/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985ApJS...57..389L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985ApJ...289..556L</bibcode>
			<title>Abundances in field dwarf stars. II - Carbon and nitrogen abundances</title>
			<authors>Laird, J. B.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 289, Feb. 15, 1985, p. 556-569.</journal>
			<date>2/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985ApJ...289..556L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985ApJ...289..203G</bibcode>
			<title>Closed coronal structures. VI - Far-ultraviolet and X-ray emission from active late-type stars and the applicability of coronal loop models</title>
			<authors>Giampapa, M. S.; Golub, L.; Peres, G.; Serio, S.; Vaiana, G. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 289, Feb. 1, 1985, p. 203-212. Research supported by the Ministero della Pubblica Istruzione and Consiglio Nazionale delle Ricerche.</journal>
			<date>2/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985ApJ...289..203G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985MNRAS.212..211C</bibcode>
			<title>Narrow-band polarization measurements of late-type stars</title>
			<authors>Clarke, D.; Brooks, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 212, Jan. 1, 1985, p. 211-218. Research supported by the Science and Engineering Research Council.</journal>
			<date>1/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985MNRAS.212..211C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985A&amp;AS...59..145C</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of Fe/H determinations, 1984 edition</title>
			<authors>Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Bentolila, C.; Hauck, B.; Duquennoy, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 59, Jan. 1985, p. 145-186. Research supported by the Swiss National Science Foundation.</journal>
			<date>1/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985A%26AS...59..145C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985AbaOB..59...83B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of data on energy distribution in spectra of stars in a uniform spectrophotometric system.</title>
			<authors>Burnashev, V. I.</authors>
			<journal>Abastumanskaya Astrofiz. Obs., Byull., No. 59, p. 83 - 90</journal>
			<date>0/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985AbaOB..59...83B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984NASCP2349..468A</bibcode>
			<title>Precise measurements of radial velocities of emission lines in the far-ultraviolet spectra of late-type stars</title>
			<authors>Ayres, T. R.; Engvold, O.; Moe, D. K.; Simon, T.; Jordan, C.; Judge, P.; Brown, A.; Linsky, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>In NASA.  Goddard Space Flight Center  Future of Ultraviolet Astronomy Based on Six Years of IUE Res. p 468-471 (SEE N85-20961 11-89)</journal>
			<date>12/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984NASCP2349..468A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984NASCP2349..454G</bibcode>
			<title>Active late-type stars and the applicability of coronal loop models</title>
			<authors>Giampapa, M. S.; Golub, L.; Peres, G.; Serio, S.; Vaiana, G. S.</authors>
			<journal>In NASA.  Goddard Space Flight Center  Future of Ultraviolet Astronomy Based on Six Years of IUE Res. p 454-457 (SEE N85-20961 11-89)</journal>
			<date>12/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984NASCP2349..454G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984NASCP2349..445L</bibcode>
			<title>A progress report on the analysis of long exposure SWP high resolution spectra of cool stars</title>
			<authors>Linsky, J. L.; Ayres, T. R.; Brown, A.; Carpenter, K.; Jordan, C.; Judge, P.; Gustafsson, B.; Eriksson, K.; Saxner, M.; Engvold, O.; Jensen, E.; Moe, O. K.; Simon, T.</authors>
			<journal>In NASA.  Goddard Space Flight Center  Future of Ultraviolet Astronomy Based on Six Years of IUE Res. p 445-449 (SEE N85-20961 11-89)</journal>
			<date>12/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984NASCP2349..445L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984MNRAS.211..607B</bibcode>
			<title>Optical photometry and UV spectroscopy of the flare star GL 735 (= V1285 Aql)</title>
			<authors>Byrne, P. B.; Doyle, J. G.; Butler, C. J.; Andrews, A. D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 211, Dec. 1, 1984, p. 607-616.</journal>
			<date>12/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984MNRAS.211..607B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984ApJ...287L..43B</bibcode>
			<title>The temperature of C II emission-line formation regions in cool stars</title>
			<authors>Brown, A.; Carpenter, K. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 2 - Letters to the Editor (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 287, Dec. 1, 1984, p. L43-L46.</journal>
			<date>12/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984ApJ...287L..43B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984A&amp;A...140..427S</bibcode>
			<title>High resolution spectroscopy of Alpha Centauri. I - Lithium depletion near one solar mass</title>
			<authors>Soderblom, D. R.; Dravins, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 140, no. 2, Nov. 1984, p. 427-430. Research supported by the Smithsonian Institution and Naturvetenskapliga Forskningsradet of Sweden.</journal>
			<date>11/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984A%26A...140..427S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984BAAS...16..980M</bibcode>
			<title>IUE Observations of Interstellar Hydrogen and Deuterium toward Alpha Centauri B</title>
			<authors>Murthy, J.; Henry, R. C.; Moos, H. W.; Landsman, W.; Linsky, J. L.; Russell, J.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 16, p.980</journal>
			<date>9/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984BAAS...16..980M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984Sci...225..275P</bibcode>
			<title>Binary stars</title>
			<authors>Paczynski, B.</authors>
			<journal>Science (ISSN 0036-8075), vol. 225, July 20, 1984, p. 275-280.</journal>
			<date>7/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984Sci...225..275P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984A&amp;A...133..117V</bibcode>
			<title>The nature of magnetic activity in lower main sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Vilhu, O.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 133, no. 1, April 1984, p. 117-126.</journal>
			<date>4/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984A%26A...133..117V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984A&amp;A...133...57M</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric-coronal emission and rotation in cool MS stars Discordant correlations explained</title>
			<authors>Marilli, E.; Catalano, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 133, no. 1, April 1984, p. 57-62. Research supported by the Ministero della Pubblica Istruzione; Consiglio Nazionale delle Ricerche.</journal>
			<date>4/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984A%26A...133...57M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984Msngr..35....5P</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric emission, rotation and X-ray coronae of late-type stars</title>
			<authors>Pallavicini, R.</authors>
			<journal>ESO Messenger (ISSN 0722-6691), March 1984, p. 5-10.</journal>
			<date>3/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984Msngr..35....5P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984IzKry..69...71N</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of emission from certain stars at millimeter wavelengths</title>
			<authors>Nesterov, N. S.</authors>
			<journal>Krymskaia Astrofizicheskaia Observatoriia, Izvestiia, vol. 69, 1984, p. 71-78. In Russian.</journal>
			<date>0/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984IzKry..69...71N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984AcA....34...97E</bibcode>
			<title>A redetermination of the Barnes-Evans relation for surface flux in the V band</title>
			<authors>Eaton, J. A.; Poe, C. H.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica (ISSN 0001-5237), vol. 34, no. 1, 1984, p. 97-116.</journal>
			<date>0/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984AcA....34...97E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983ApJS...53..815Z</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar chromospheres - H-alpha and CA II K profiles</title>
			<authors>Zarro, D. M.; Rodgers, A. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 53, Dec. 1983, p. 815-868.</journal>
			<date>12/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983ApJS...53..815Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983ApJS...53..643J</bibcode>
			<title>Predicted infrared brightness of stars within 25 parsecs of the sun</title>
			<authors>Johnson, H. M.; Wright, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 53, Nov. 1983, p. 643-711. Research sponsored by the Lockheed Independent Research Program and Lockheed Independent Development Program.</journal>
			<date>11/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983ApJS...53..643J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983ApJ...274..784A</bibcode>
			<title>Outer atmospheres of cool stars. XV - High-dispersion ultraviolet studies of active chromosphere G-K dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Ayres, T. R.; Linsky, J. L.; Simon, T.; Jordan, C.; Brown, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 274, Nov. 15, 1983, p. 784-793.</journal>
			<date>11/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983ApJ...274..784A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983S&amp;W....22..479S</bibcode>
			<title>The masses of the main-sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Scheffler, H.</authors>
			<journal>Sterne und Weltraum (ISSN 0039-1263), vol. 22, Oct. 1983, p. 479-481. In German.</journal>
			<date>10/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983S%26W....22..479S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983PASP...95..480B</bibcode>
			<title>VRI photometry - an addendum</title>
			<authors>Bessell, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 95, Aug. 1983, p. 480-488.</journal>
			<date>8/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983PASP...95..480B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983A&amp;AS...51..489K</bibcode>
			<title>Near infrared photometry. I - Homogenization of near-infrared data from southern bright stars</title>
			<authors>Koornneef, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series, vol. 51, Mar. 1983, p. 489-503.</journal>
			<date>3/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983A%26AS...51..489K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983IzKry..67...13B</bibcode>
			<title>A determination of the effective temperatures, accelerations of gravity, and metallicity parameters of late-type stars from data on energy distribution in their spectra</title>
			<authors>Burnashev, V. I.</authors>
			<journal>Krymskaia Astrofizicheskaia Observatoriia, Izvestiia, vol. 67, 1983, p. 13-33. In Russian.</journal>
			<date>0/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983IzKry..67...13B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982ApJ...260..670L</bibcode>
			<title>Outer atmospheres of cool stars. XII - A survey of IUE ultraviolet emission line spectra of cool dwarf stars</title>
			<authors>Linsky, J. L.; Bornmann, P. L.; Carpenter, K. G.; Hege, E. K.; Wing, R. F.; Giampapa, M. S.; Worden, S. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1, vol. 260, Sept. 15, 1982, p. 670-694.</journal>
			<date>9/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982ApJ...260..670L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982ESASP.176....3L</bibcode>
			<title>The structure, energy balance, and winds of cool stars</title>
			<authors>Linsky, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>In ESA  3rd European IUE Conf.  p 3-14 (SEE N83-11889 02-88)</journal>
			<date>6/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982ESASP.176....3L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982A&amp;A...110...30O</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic structure in cool stars. V - Chromospheric and transition-region emission from giants</title>
			<authors>Oranje, B. J.; Zwaan, C.; Middelkoop, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 110, no. 1, June 1982, p. 30-36.  Research supported by the Nederlandse Organisatie voor Zuiver-Wetenschappelijk Onderzoek.</journal>
			<date>6/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982A%26A...110...30O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982A&amp;AS...47..341K</bibcode>
			<title>Picture gallery - A structured presentation of OAO-2 photometric data supported by OAO-2 spectrophotometric data and UBV, ANS and TD1 observations</title>
			<authors>Koornneef, J.; Meade, M. R.; Code, A. D.; Wesselius, P. R.; van Duinen, R. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series, vol. 47, Feb. 1982, p. 341-418.</journal>
			<date>2/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982A%26AS...47..341K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982A&amp;A...105...53T</bibcode>
			<title>Interstellar polarization in the immediate solar neighbourhood</title>
			<authors>Tinbergen, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 105, no. 1, Jan. 1982, p. 53-64.</journal>
			<date>1/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982A%26A...105...53T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982NASCP2338..281A</bibcode>
			<title>High dispersion IUE spectra of active chromosphere G and K dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Ayres, T. R.; Linsky, J. L.; Brown, A.; Jordan, C.; Simon, T.</authors>
			<journal>In NASA.  Goddard Space Flight Center  Advan. in Ultraviolet Astron.  p 281-284 (SEE N82-31163 21-89)</journal>
			<date>0/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982NASCP2338..281A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982NASCP2338...17L</bibcode>
			<title>The structure and energy balance of cool star atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Linsky, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>In NASA.  Goddard Space Flight Center  Advan. in Ultraviolet Astron.  p 17-32 (SEE N82-31163 21-89)</journal>
			<date>0/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982NASCP2338...17L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981A&amp;A...104..240S</bibcode>
			<title>Transition region structure in F dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Saxner, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 104, no. 2, Dec. 1981, p. 240-248. Research sponsored by the Swedish Board for Space Activities.</journal>
			<date>12/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981A%26A...104..240S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981ApJ...250..293A</bibcode>
			<title>The cool half of the H-R diagram in soft X-rays</title>
			<authors>Ayres, T. R.; Linsky, J. L.; Vaiana, G. S.; Golub, L.; Rosner, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1, vol. 250, Nov. 1, 1981, p. 293-299. NASA-supported research.</journal>
			<date>11/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981ApJ...250..293A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981A&amp;AS...46..193H</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical bolometric corrections for the main-sequence</title>
			<authors>Habets, G. M. H. J.; Heintze, J. R. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series, vol. 46, Nov. 1981, p. 193-237.</journal>
			<date>11/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981A%26AS...46..193H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981ApJ...248L..73H</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation of dwarf star chromospheres in the ultraviolet</title>
			<authors>Hallam, K. L.; Wolff, C. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 2 - Letters to the Editor, vol. 248, Sept. 1, 1981, p. L73-L76.</journal>
			<date>9/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981ApJ...248L..73H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981ApJ...247..545A</bibcode>
			<title>Outer atmospheres of cool stars. IX - A survey of ultraviolet emission from F-K dwarfs and giants with IUE</title>
			<authors>Ayres, T. R.; Marstad, N. C.; Linsky, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1, vol. 247, July 15, 1981, p. 545-559.</journal>
			<date>7/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981ApJ...247..545A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981A&amp;AS...45....5E</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared Observations of Southern Bright Stars</title>
			<authors>Engels, D.; Sherwood, W. A.; Wamsteker, W.; Schultz, G. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, Vol. 45, P. 5, 1981</journal>
			<date>7/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981A%26AS...45....5E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981A&amp;A...100..116H</bibcode>
			<title>Distribution of near infrared sources in the galactic disk</title>
			<authors>Hayakawa, S.; Matsumoto, T.; Murakami, H.; Uyama, K.; Thomas, J. A.; Yamagami, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 100, no. 1, July 1981, p. 116-123. Research supported by the Japan Society for the Promotion of Science and Yamada Science Foundation.</journal>
			<date>7/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981A%26A...100..116H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981ApJ...245..163V</bibcode>
			<title>Results from an extensive Einstein stellar survey</title>
			<authors>Vaiana, G. S.; Cassinelli, J. P.; Fabbiano, G.; Giacconi, R.; Golub, L.; Gorenstein, P.; Haisch, B. M.; Harnden, F. R., Jr.; Johnson, H. M.; Linsky, J. L.; Maxson, C. W.; Mewe, R.; Rosner, R.; Seward, F.; Topka, K.; Zwaan, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1, vol. 244, Apr. 1, 1981, p. 163-182.  Research supported by the Consiglio Nazionale delle Ricerche;</journal>
			<date>4/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981ApJ...245..163V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981BICDS..20...28C</bibcode>
			<title>Age et mtallicit d'toiles plus proches que 10 parsecs et ayant une temprature effective suprieure  4000 K</title>
			<authors>Cayrel de Strobel, G.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin d'Information du Centre de Donnees Stellaires, Vol. 20, p.28</journal>
			<date>2/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981BICDS..20...28C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981SAAOC...6...10D</bibcode>
			<title>DDO Observations of Southern Stars</title>
			<authors>Dean, J. F.</authors>
			<journal>South African Astronomical Observatory Circulars, Vol. 6, P. 10, 1981</journal>
			<date>0/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981SAAOC...6...10D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981ATsir1154....1K</bibcode>
			<title>Identification of X-Ray Source H0850+13 with Eclipsing Binary Ac-Cancri</title>
			<authors>Kurochkin, N. E.; Shugarov, S. Y.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomicheskii Tsirkulyar NO.1154, 1981</journal>
			<date>0/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981ATsir1154....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1980A&amp;AS...41..405C</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of /Fe/H/ determinations</title>
			<authors>Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Bentolila, C.; Hauck, B.; Curchod, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series, vol. 41, Sept. 1980, p. 405-419.</journal>
			<date>9/1980</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1980A%26AS...41..405C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1980ApJS...43..501C</bibcode>
			<title>Ultraviolet photometry from the Orbiting Astronomical Observatory. XXXIV - Filter photometry of 531 stars of diverse types</title>
			<authors>Code, A. D.; Holm, A. V.; Bottemiller, R. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, vol. 43, Aug. 1980, p. 501-545.</journal>
			<date>8/1980</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1980ApJS...43..501C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1980BICDS..19...41H</bibcode>
			<title>Erratum - Discordances Between SAO and HD Numbers for Bright Stars</title>
			<authors>Hoffleit, D.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin d'Information du Centre de Donnees Stellaires, Vol. 19, P. 41, 1980</journal>
			<date>7/1980</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1980BICDS..19...41H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1980MNRAS.191...23E</bibcode>
			<title>A spectroscopic analysis of the Alpha Centauri system</title>
			<authors>England, M. N.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, vol. 191, Apr. 1980, p. 23-35.</journal>
			<date>4/1980</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1980MNRAS.191...23E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1980Ap&amp;SS..68..433D</bibcode>
			<title>Close binary systems before and after mass transfer - A comparison of observations and theory</title>
			<authors>De Greve, J. P.; Vanbeveren, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, vol. 68, no. 2, Apr. 1980, p. 433-457. Fonds de la Recherche Fondamentale Collective</journal>
			<date>4/1980</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1980Ap%26SS..68..433D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1980SAAOC...1..166C</bibcode>
			<title>VRI photometry of nearby stars.</title>
			<authors>Cousins, A. W. J.</authors>
			<journal>South African Astronomical Observatory Circular, Vol. 1, p. 166 - 171</journal>
			<date>0/1980</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1980SAAOC...1..166C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979ApJ...230..786E</bibcode>
			<title>Luminosity and motion of large proper-motion stars. I - Stars with annual proper motion larger than 1 arcsec</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1, vol. 230, June 15, 1979, p. 786-801.</journal>
			<date>6/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979ApJ...230..786E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979ApJS...39..195C</bibcode>
			<title>Ultraviolet photometry from the Orbiting Astronomical Observatory. XXXII - an atlas of ultraviolet stellar spectra</title>
			<authors>Code, A. D.; Meade, M. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, vol. 39, Feb. 1979, p. 195-289.</journal>
			<date>2/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979ApJS...39..195C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979VKha..190...52Z</bibcode>
			<title>Nearest stars.</title>
			<authors>Zakhozhaj, V. A.</authors>
			<journal>Vestnik Khar'kovskogo Universiteta, Vol. 190, p. 52-77 (1979)</journal>
			<date>0/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979VKha..190...52Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1978A&amp;A....70..431A</bibcode>
			<title>Upper limits on extreme ultraviolet radiation from nearby main sequence and subgiant stars</title>
			<authors>Ayres, T. R.; Linsky, J. L.; Margon, B.; Bowyer, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 70, no. 3, Nov. 1978, p. 431-434.</journal>
			<date>11/1978</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1978A%26A....70..431A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1978ApJ...222..191E</bibcode>
			<title>Intermediate-band photometry of late-type stars. VI - Main-sequence stars near the sun. VII - The HR 1614 group of overabundant stars</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1, vol. 222, May 15, 1978, p. 191-208.</journal>
			<date>5/1978</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1978ApJ...222..191E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1978A&amp;A....66..175R</bibcode>
			<title>Flare active binary systems - EQ Peg and its brighter companion BD plus 19 5116 A</title>
			<authors>Rodon, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 66, no. 1-2, May 1978, p. 175-185.</journal>
			<date>5/1978</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1978A%26A....66..175R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1977PASP...89..588H</bibcode>
			<title>Measures of southern visual double stars.</title>
			<authors>Holden, F.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Vol. 89, p. 588 - 595</journal>
			<date>8/1977</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1977PASP...89..588H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1977PASP...89..582H</bibcode>
			<title>Visual double stars measured at Las Campanas Observatory, Chile.</title>
			<authors>Holden, F.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Vol. 89, p. 582 - 587</journal>
			<date>8/1977</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1977PASP...89..582H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1977ApJS...34..479L</bibcode>
			<title>Radii of nearby stars: an application of the Barnes-Evans relation.</title>
			<authors>Lacy, C. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Suppl. Ser., Vol. 34, p. 479 - 492</journal>
			<date>8/1977</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1977ApJS...34..479L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1977MNRAS.180..177B</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar angular diameters from infrared photometry - Application to Arcturus and other stars; with effective temperatures</title>
			<authors>Blackwell, D. E.; Shallis, M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, vol. 180, July 1977, p. 177-191.</journal>
			<date>7/1977</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1977MNRAS.180..177B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1977A&amp;A....54..779P</bibcode>
			<title>Fine structure of the H-R diagram for 138 stars in the solar neighbourhood</title>
			<authors>Perrin, M.-N.; Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Cayrel, R.; Hejlesen, P. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 54, no. 3, Feb. 1977, p. 779-795.</journal>
			<date>2/1977</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1977A%26A....54..779P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1976PASP...88...52H</bibcode>
			<title>Measures of southern visual double stars.</title>
			<authors>Holden, F.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Vol. 88, p. 52 - 57</journal>
			<date>2/1976</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1976PASP...88...52H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1975PASP...87..945H</bibcode>
			<title>Visual double stars measured at Las Campanas Observatory, Chile.</title>
			<authors>Holden, F.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Vol. 87, p. 945 - 948</journal>
			<date>12/1975</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1975PASP...87..945H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1975ApJ...202L..67M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of X-ray emission from stellar coronae with ANS</title>
			<authors>Mewe, R.; Heise, J.; Gronenschild, E. H. B. M.; Brinkman, A. C.; Schrijver, J.; den Boggende, A. J. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 202, Dec. 1, 1975, pt. 2, p. L67-L71.</journal>
			<date>12/1975</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1975ApJ...202L..67M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1975ApJ...200...42P</bibcode>
			<title>A new upper limit to the mass loss from the central region of the Galaxy</title>
			<authors>Poveda, A.; Allen, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 200, Aug. 15, 1975, pt. 1, p. 42-47.</journal>
			<date>8/1975</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1975ApJ...200...42P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1975ApJ...199..710B</bibcode>
			<title>Studies of heavy-element synthesis in the Galaxy. II - A survey of e-, r-, and s-process abundances</title>
			<authors>Butcher, H. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 199, Aug. 1, 1975, pt. 1, p. 710-717.</journal>
			<date>8/1975</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1975ApJ...199..710B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1975ApJ...197L..19V</bibcode>
			<title>A search for stellar soft X-ray sources</title>
			<authors>Vanderhill, M. J.; Borken, R. J.; Bunner, A. N.; Burstein, P. H.; Kraushaar, W. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 197, Apr. 1, 1975, pt. 2, p. L19-L22.</journal>
			<date>4/1975</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1975ApJ...197L..19V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1975ApJ...195L.121A</bibcode>
			<title>A possible width-luminosity correlation of the CA II K1 and MG II k1 features</title>
			<authors>Ayres, T. R.; Shine, R. A.; Linsky, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 195, Feb. 1, 1975, pt. 2, p. L121-L124.</journal>
			<date>2/1975</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1975ApJ...195L.121A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1974PASP...86..907H</bibcode>
			<title>Measures of Southern Visual Double Stars</title>
			<authors>Holden, Frank</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Vol. 86, No. 514, p.907</journal>
			<date>12/1974</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1974PASP...86..907H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1974ApJ...189L..17B</bibcode>
			<title>Multiple Star Systems and X-Ray Sources</title>
			<authors>Bahcall, J. N.; Dyson, F. J.; Katz, J. I.; Paczynski, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 189, p.L17</journal>
			<date>4/1974</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1974ApJ...189L..17B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1974ApJ...189...85B</bibcode>
			<title>The age of alpha Centauri.</title>
			<authors>Boesgaard, A. M.; Hagen, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Vol. 189, p. 85 - 87</journal>
			<date>4/1974</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1974ApJ...189...85B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1973ApJ...182..821E</bibcode>
			<title>On the existence of subdwarfs in the (Mbol, log Te)-plane. III.</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Vol. 182, p. 821 - 837</journal>
			<date>6/1973</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1973ApJ...182..821E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1973MNRAS.165..201T</bibcode>
			<title>Southern infra-red standards and the absolute calibration of infra-red photometry.</title>
			<authors>Thomas, J. A.; Hyland, A. R.; Robinson, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. Vol. 165, p. 201 - 211</journal>
			<date>0/1973</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1973MNRAS.165..201T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1973MNRAS.164P..19A</bibcode>
			<title>Problems with strong-line G and K dwarfs.</title>
			<authors>Alexander, J. B.; Branch, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. Vol. 164, p. 19P - 25P</journal>
			<date>0/1973</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1973MNRAS.164P..19A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1972ApJ...178..495D</bibcode>
			<title>Ultraviolet photometry from the Orbiting Astronomical Observatory. VI. Magnesium II 2800  emission in cool stars.</title>
			<authors>Doherty, L. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Vol. 178, p. 495 - 501</journal>
			<date>12/1972</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1972ApJ...178..495D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1972PASP...84..465M</bibcode>
			<title>The Structure of Chemically Homogeneous Main-Sequence Stars</title>
			<authors>Motz, Lloyd</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Vol. 84, No. 500, p.465</journal>
			<date>8/1972</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1972PASP...84..465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1970AJ.....75..624C</bibcode>
			<title>Four-color and Hbeta photometry for bright stars in the southern hemisphere.</title>
			<authors>Crawford, D. L.; Barnes, J. V.; Golson, J. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, Vol. 75, p. 624 - 635 = Contrib. Cerro Tololo Inter-American Obs., No. 109</journal>
			<date>6/1970</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1970AJ.....75..624C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1969MNRAS.144..333W</bibcode>
			<title>Ca II K emission in southern late-type stars</title>
			<authors>Warner, Brian</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 144, p.333</journal>
			<date>0/1969</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1969MNRAS.144..333W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1968ApJ...154..115S</bibcode>
			<title>Correlation Between the Regional Variations in Wavelength Dependence of Interstellar Extinction and Polarization</title>
			<authors>Serkowski, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 154, p.115</journal>
			<date>10/1968</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1968ApJ...154..115S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1965AJ.....70...19E</bibcode>
			<title>Masses, luminosities, colors, and space motions of 228 visual binaries</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, Vol. 70, p. 19</journal>
			<date>2/1965</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1965AJ.....70...19E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1963PASP...75..408B</bibcode>
			<title>A Six-color Criterion for Blanketing</title>
			<authors>Breckinridge, J. B.; Kron, G. E.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Vol. 75, No. 446, p.408</journal>
			<date>10/1963</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1963PASP...75..408B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1963ZA.....57..135K</bibcode>
			<title>Statistische Betrachtungen zur empirischen Masse-Leuchtkraft-Beziehung</title>
			<authors>Kurth, R.</authors>
			<journal>Zeitschrift fr Astrophysik, Vol. 57, p.135</journal>
			<date>0/1963</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1963ZA.....57..135K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1960MNRAS.121...17W</bibcode>
			<title>Absolute measures of stellar radiation, I</title>
			<authors>Willstrop, R. V.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 121, 17</journal>
			<date>0/1960</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1960MNRAS.121...17W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1959SvA.....3..633M</bibcode>
			<title>The Visual Stellar Magnitude of the Sun, the Moon, and the Lux.</title>
			<authors>Martynov, D. Ya.</authors>
			<journal>Soviet Astronomy, Vol. 3, p.633</journal>
			<date>8/1959</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1959SvA.....3..633M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1958AJ.....63..381S</bibcode>
			<title>Van Vleck Observatory</title>
			<authors>Stearns, C. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, Vol. 63, p. 381-381 (1958)</journal>
			<date>0/1958</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1958AJ.....63..381S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1957JO.....40...57B</bibcode>
			<title>Dtermination de la masse "hypothtique" et couple de la parallaxe dynamique d'un couple dont le type spectral est inconnu</title>
			<authors>Baize, P.</authors>
			<journal>Journal des Observateurs, Vol. 40, p.57</journal>
			<date>1/1957</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1957JO.....40...57B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1957MNRAS.117..640A</bibcode>
			<title>Radial velocity observations of southern visual binaries</title>
			<authors>Archer, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 117, p.640</journal>
			<date>0/1957</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1957MNRAS.117..640A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1957AJ.....62..205K</bibcode>
			<title>Red and infrared magnitudes for 282 stars with known trigonometric parallaxes.</title>
			<authors>Kron, G. E.; Gascoigne, S. C. B.; White, H. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, Vol. 62, p. 205-220 (1957)</journal>
			<date>0/1957</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1957AJ.....62..205K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1956AJ.....61..361E</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric parallaxes and the mass-luminosity relation.</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, Vol. 61, p. 361-380 (1956)</journal>
			<date>10/1956</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1956AJ.....61..361E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1954BAICz...5....4S</bibcode>
			<title>A Note on the Dwarf Flare Stars</title>
			<authors>Svestka, Zd.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Astronomical Institute of Czechoslovakia, vol. 5, p.4</journal>
			<date>2/1954</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1954BAICz...5....4S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1954MNRAS.114..635F</bibcode>
			<title>Note on the spectra of K-type dwarfs in the region of H and K, M. W. Feast and A. D. Thackeray</title>
			<authors>Feast, M. W.; Thackeray, A. D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 114, p.635</journal>
			<date>0/1954</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1954MNRAS.114..635F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1953ApJ...118...55K</bibcode>
			<title>The System of Alpha Coronae Borealis.</title>
			<authors>Kron, Gerald E.; Gordon, Katherine C.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 118, p.55</journal>
			<date>7/1953</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1953ApJ...118...55K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1951AnAp...14...85B</bibcode>
			<title>Formule corrective nouvelle pour dterminer  partir des estimations visuelles, la diffrence de magnitude des composantes d'toiles doubles</title>
			<authors>Baize, Paul</authors>
			<journal>Annales d'Astrophysique, Vol. 14, p.85</journal>
			<date>1/1951</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1951AnAp...14...85B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1918ApJ....48..261L</bibcode>
			<title>The radial velocities of 119 stars observed at the Cape.</title>
			<authors>Lunt, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, 48, 261-278 (1918)</journal>
			<date>12/1918</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1918ApJ....48..261L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1918ApJ....48..182L</bibcode>
			<title>Alpha Centauri as a spectroscopic binary.</title>
			<authors>Lunt, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, 48, 182-194 (1918)</journal>
			<date>10/1918</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1918ApJ....48..182L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1918ApJ....47..289P</bibcode>
			<title>On the cause underlying the spectral differences of the stars.</title>
			<authors>Perrine, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, 47, 289-323 (1918)</journal>
			<date>6/1918</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1918ApJ....47..289P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1904ApJ....20..140W</bibcode>
			<title>On some results obtained by the D. O. Mills expedition to the southern hemisphere.</title>
			<authors>Wright, W. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, 20, 140-145 (1904)</journal>
			<date>9/1904</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1904ApJ....20..140W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1897ApJ.....6..349P</bibcode>
			<title>Spectra of bright southern stars.</title>
			<authors>Pickering, E. C.; Cannon, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, 6, 349-352 (1897)</journal>
			<date>10/1897</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1897ApJ.....6..349P</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
