<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013AJ....146....9A</bibcode>
			<title>Adaptive Optics Images. II. 12 Kepler Objects of Interest and 15 Confirmed Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Dupree, A. K.; Kulesa, C.; McCarthy, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 146, Issue 1, article id. 9, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013AJ....146....9A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...767...76K</bibcode>
			<title>Three-dimensional Atmospheric Circulation of Hot Jupiters on Highly Eccentric Orbits</title>
			<authors>Kataria, T.; Showman, A. P.; Lewis, N. K.; Fortney, J. J.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 767, Issue 1, article id. 76, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;19&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...767...76K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...766....9S</bibcode>
			<title>An Ultraviolet Investigation of Activity on Exoplanet Host Stars</title>
			<authors>Shkolnik, Evgenya L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 766, Issue 1, article id. 9, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...766....9S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013PASP..125..154B</bibcode>
			<title>HATSouth: A Global Network of Fully Automated Identical Wide-Field Telescopes</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Csubry, Z.; Penev, K.; Bayliss, D.; Jordn, A.; Afonso, C.; Hartman, J. D.; Henning, T.; Kovcs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Bky, B.; Suc, V.; Csk, B.; Rabus, M.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.; Conroy, P.; Zhou, G.; Sackett, P. D.; Schmidt, B.; Mancini, L.; Sasselov, D. D.; Ueltzhoeffer, K.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 125, issue 924, pp.154-182</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013PASP..125..154B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764...18L</bibcode>
			<title>Pulsation Frequencies and Modes of Giant Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Le Bihan, Bastien; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. 18, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764...18L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...549A.134H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-52b, WASP-58b, WASP-59b, and WASP-60b: Four new transiting close-in giant planets</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Collier Cameron, A.; Brown, D. J. A.; Daz, R. F.; Faedi, F.; Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Armstrong, D.; Barros, S. C. C.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Doyle, A. P.; Enoch, B.; Gmez Maqueo Chew, Y.; Hbrard, . M.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Moutou, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Skillen, I.; Southworth, J.; Tregloan-Reed, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; Vanhuysse, M.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 549, id.A134, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...549A.134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757....5V</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical Timescales in the Atmospheres of Highly Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Visscher, Channon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 1, article id. 5, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757....5V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.3151H</bibcode>
			<title>Observational constraints on tidal effects using orbital eccentricities</title>
			<authors>Husnoo, Nawal; Pont, Frdric; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel; Hbrard, Guillaume; Bouchy, Franois; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 4, pp. 3151-3177.</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.3151H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750...84B</bibcode>
			<title>Qatar-2: A K Dwarf Orbited by a Transiting Hot Jupiter and a More Massive Companion in an Outer Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bryan, Marta L.; Alsubai, Khalid A.; Latham, David W.; Parley, Neil R.; Collier Cameron, Andrew; Quinn, Samuel N.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fulton, Benjamin J.; Berlind, Perry; Brown, Warren R.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Calkins, Michael L.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Fursz, Gbor; Gre Jrgensen, Uffe; Horne, Keith D.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Street, Rachel A.; Torres, Guillermo; West, Richard G.; Dominik, Martin; Harpse, Kennet B. W.; Liebig, Christine; Calchi Novati, Sebastiano; Ricci, Davide; Skottfelt, Jesper F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 1, article id. 84, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750...84B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..134H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-17b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Saturn and a Long-period, Cold Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Howard, A. W.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Mazeh, T.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Bky, B.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 134, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749..134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..82K</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for enhanced chromospheric Ca II H and K emission in stars with close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A82, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..82K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>The Heavy-element Masses of Extrasolar Giant Planets, Revealed</title>
			<authors>Miller, Neil; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L29, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1573V</bibcode>
			<title>Transit variability in bow shock-hosting planets</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1573-1582.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1573V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734..109B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-27b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a G Star on a 3 Day Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bky, B.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Jordn, A.; Arriagada, P.; Bayliss, D.; Kiss, L. L.; Kovcs, Gza; Quinn, S. N.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 109, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734..109B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..54B</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-38b: a transiting exoplanet in an eccentric, 6.87d period orbit</title>
			<authors>Barros, S. C. C.; Faedi, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Lister, T. A.; McCormac, J.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Hbrard, G.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Bento, J.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Skillen, I.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A54, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..54B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..866K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-15b: A 10.9 Day Extrasolar Planet Transiting a Solar-type Star</title>
			<authors>Kovcs, G.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fernandez, J. M.; Lzr, B. Bky J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 866-877 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..866K</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...772...80F</bibcode>
			<title>The Stellar Obliquity and the Long-period Planet in the HAT-P-17 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Fulton, Benjamin J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Winn, Joshua N.; Albrecht, Simon; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Crepp, Justin R.; Bakos, Gaspar A.; Johnson, John Asher; Hartman, Joel D.; Isaacson, Howard; Knutson, Heather A.; Zhao, Ming</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 772, Issue 2, article id. 80, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>8/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...772...80F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...771...11A</bibcode>
			<title>Low Stellar Obliquities in Compact Multiplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Albrecht, Simon; Winn, Joshua N.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 771, Issue 1, article id. 11, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...771...11A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...551A.108M</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-site campaign for transit timing variations of WASP-12 b: possible detection of a long-period signal of planetary origin</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Seeliger, M.; Raetz, St.; Bukowiecki, L.; Kitze, M.; Errmann, R.; Nowak, G.; Niedzielski, A.; Popov, V.; Marka, C.; Gozdziewski, K.; Neuhuser, R.; Ohlert, J.; Hinse, T. C.; Lee, J. W.; Lee, C.-U.; Yoon, J.-N.; Berndt, A.; Gilbert, H.; Ginski, Ch.; Hohle, M. M.; Mugrauer, M.; Rll, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Tetzlaff, N.; Mancini, L.; Southworth, J.; Dall'Ora, M.; Ciceri, S.; Zambelli, R.; Corfini, G.; Takahashi, H.; Tachihara, K.; Benko , J. M.; Srneczky, K.; Szabo, Gy. M.; Varga, T. N.; Vanko, M.; Joshi, Y. C.; Chen, W. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 551, id.A108, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...551A.108M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...761..163D</bibcode>
			<title>The Photoeccentric Effect and Proto-hot Jupiters. II. KOI-1474.01, a Candidate Eccentric Planet Perturbed by an Unseen Companion</title>
			<authors>Dawson, Rebekah I.; Johnson, John Asher; Morton, Timothy D.; Crepp, Justin R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Howard, Andrew W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 761, Issue 2, article id. 163, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...761..163D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757..161T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Spectroscopic Parameters for Transiting Planet Hosts</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Fischer, Debra A.; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Buchhave, Lars A.; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 2, article id. 161, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757..161T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..134H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-17b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Saturn and a Long-period, Cold Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Howard, A. W.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Mazeh, T.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Bky, B.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 134, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749..134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1573V</bibcode>
			<title>Transit variability in bow shock-hosting planets</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1573-1582.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1573V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
