<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...772...76S</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Processes Governing Hot-Jupiter Radii</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 772, Issue 1, article id. 76, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...772...76S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013AJ....146....9A</bibcode>
			<title>Adaptive Optics Images. II. 12 Kepler Objects of Interest and 15 Confirmed Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Dupree, A. K.; Kulesa, C.; McCarthy, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 146, Issue 1, article id. 9, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013AJ....146....9A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764...18L</bibcode>
			<title>Pulsation Frequencies and Modes of Giant Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Le Bihan, Bastien; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. 18, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764...18L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...547A..61S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-78b and WASP-79b: two highly-bloated hot Jupiter-mass exoplanets orbiting F-type stars in Eridanus</title>
			<authors>Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Fumel, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, , C.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 547, id.A61, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>11/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...547A..61S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.426..739H</bibcode>
			<title>Seven transiting hot Jupiters from WASP-South, Euler and TRAPPIST: WASP-47b, WASP-55b, WASP-61b, WASP-62b, WASP-63b, WASP-66b and WASP-67b</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Fumel, A.; Gillon, M.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 426, Issue 1, pp. 739-750.</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.426..739H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.1988A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-44b, WASP-45b and WASP-46b: three short-period, transiting extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Sgransan, D.; Todd, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 3, pp. 1988-1998.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.1988A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..56M</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler KOI-13.01 - Detection of beaming and ellipsoidal modulations pointing to a massive hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Nachmani, G.; Sokol, G.; Faigler, S.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A56, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..56M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..82K</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for enhanced chromospheric Ca II H and K emission in stars with close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A82, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..82K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...59H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-32b and HAT-P-33b: Two Highly Inflated Hot Jupiters Transiting High-jitter Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Bky, B.; Quinn, S. N.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; Szklenr, T.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 59, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;19&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...59H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...766L..20F</bibcode>
			<title>Absorbing Gas around the WASP-12 Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Fossati, L.; Ayres, T. R.; Haswell, C. A.; Bohlender, D.; Kochukhov, O.; Fl er, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 766, Issue 2, article id. L20, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...766L..20F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....144..139H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-39b-HAT-P-41b: Three Highly Inflated Transiting Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Bky, B.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Csubry, Z.; Penev, K.; Shporer, A.; Fulton, B. J.; Buchhave, L. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Howard, A. W.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Kovcs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Szklenr, T.; Quinn, S. N.; Bieryla, A.; Knox, R. P.; Hinz, P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Fursz, G.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 144, Issue 5, article id. 139, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;18&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>11/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....144..139H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.426.1338S</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision photometry by telescope defocusing - IV. Confirmation of the huge radius of WASP-17 b</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Dominik, M.; Fang, X.-S.; Harpse, K.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kerins, E.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Skottfelt, J.; Anderson, D. R.; Smalley, B.; Tregloan-Reed, J.; Wertz, O.; Alsubai, K. A.; Bozza, V.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dreizler, S.; Gu, S.-H.; Hundertmark, M.; Jessen-Hansen, J.; Kains, N.; Kjeldsen, H.; Lund, M. N.; Lundkvist, M.; Mathiasen, M.; Penny, M. T.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 426, Issue 2, pp. 1338-1348.</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.426.1338S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.1988A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-44b, WASP-45b and WASP-46b: three short-period, transiting extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Sgransan, D.; Todd, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 3, pp. 1988-1998.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.1988A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..189A</bibcode>
			<title>A High Stellar Obliquity in the WASP-7 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Albrecht, Simon; Winn, Joshua N.; Butler, R. Paul; Crane, Jeffrey D.; Shectman, Stephen A.; Thompson, Ian B.; Hirano, Teruyuki; Wittenmyer, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 189, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..189A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...59H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-32b and HAT-P-33b: Two Highly Inflated Hot Jupiters Transiting High-jitter Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Bky, B.; Quinn, S. N.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; Szklenr, T.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 59, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;19&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...59H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
