<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750...84B</bibcode>
			<title>Qatar-2: A K Dwarf Orbited by a Transiting Hot Jupiter and a More Massive Companion in an Outer Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bryan, Marta L.; Alsubai, Khalid A.; Latham, David W.; Parley, Neil R.; Collier Cameron, Andrew; Quinn, Samuel N.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fulton, Benjamin J.; Berlind, Perry; Brown, Warren R.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Calkins, Michael L.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Fursz, Gbor; Gre Jrgensen, Uffe; Horne, Keith D.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Street, Rachel A.; Torres, Guillermo; West, Richard G.; Dominik, Martin; Harpse, Kennet B. W.; Liebig, Christine; Calchi Novati, Sebastiano; Ricci, Davide; Skottfelt, Jesper F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 1, article id. 84, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750...84B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..134H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-17b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Saturn and a Long-period, Cold Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Howard, A. W.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Mazeh, T.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Bky, B.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 134, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749..134H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...772...80F</bibcode>
			<title>The Stellar Obliquity and the Long-period Planet in the HAT-P-17 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Fulton, Benjamin J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Winn, Joshua N.; Albrecht, Simon; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Crepp, Justin R.; Bakos, Gaspar A.; Johnson, John Asher; Hartman, Joel D.; Isaacson, Howard; Knutson, Heather A.; Zhao, Ming</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 772, Issue 2, article id. 80, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>8/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...772...80F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...771...11A</bibcode>
			<title>Low Stellar Obliquities in Compact Multiplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Albrecht, Simon; Winn, Joshua N.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 771, Issue 1, article id. 11, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...771...11A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...551A.108M</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-site campaign for transit timing variations of WASP-12 b: possible detection of a long-period signal of planetary origin</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Seeliger, M.; Raetz, St.; Bukowiecki, L.; Kitze, M.; Errmann, R.; Nowak, G.; Niedzielski, A.; Popov, V.; Marka, C.; Gozdziewski, K.; Neuhuser, R.; Ohlert, J.; Hinse, T. C.; Lee, J. W.; Lee, C.-U.; Yoon, J.-N.; Berndt, A.; Gilbert, H.; Ginski, Ch.; Hohle, M. M.; Mugrauer, M.; Rll, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Tetzlaff, N.; Mancini, L.; Southworth, J.; Dall'Ora, M.; Ciceri, S.; Zambelli, R.; Corfini, G.; Takahashi, H.; Tachihara, K.; Benko , J. M.; Srneczky, K.; Szabo, Gy. M.; Varga, T. N.; Vanko, M.; Joshi, Y. C.; Chen, W. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 551, id.A108, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...551A.108M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...761..163D</bibcode>
			<title>The Photoeccentric Effect and Proto-hot Jupiters. II. KOI-1474.01, a Candidate Eccentric Planet Perturbed by an Unseen Companion</title>
			<authors>Dawson, Rebekah I.; Johnson, John Asher; Morton, Timothy D.; Crepp, Justin R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Howard, Andrew W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 761, Issue 2, article id. 163, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...761..163D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757..161T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Spectroscopic Parameters for Transiting Planet Hosts</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Fischer, Debra A.; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Buchhave, Lars A.; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 2, article id. 161, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757..161T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..134H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-17b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Saturn and a Long-period, Cold Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Howard, A. W.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Mazeh, T.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Bky, B.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 134, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749..134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1573V</bibcode>
			<title>Transit variability in bow shock-hosting planets</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1573-1582.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1573V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
