<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...771..112A</bibcode>
			<title>Dusty OB Stars in the Small Magellanic Cloud. II. Extragalactic Disks or Examples of the Pleiades Phenomenon?</title>
			<authors>Adams, Joshua J.; Simon, Joshua D.; Bolatto, Alberto D.; Sloan, G. C.; Sandstrom, Karin M.; Schmiedeke, Anika; van Loon, Jacco Th.; Oliveira, Joana M.; Keller, Luke D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 771, Issue 2, article id. 112, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;23&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...771..112A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...771...45D</bibcode>
			<title>The 0.5-2.22 mum Scattered Light Spectrum of the Disk around TW Hya: Detection of a Partially Filled Disk Gap at 80 AU</title>
			<authors>Debes, John H.; Jang-Condell, Hannah; Weinberger, Alycia J.; Roberge, Aki; Schneider, Glenn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 771, Issue 1, article id. 45, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;15&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...771...45D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...771...34R</bibcode>
			<title>Petrologic Constraints on Amorphous and Crystalline Magnesium Silicates: Dust Formation and Evolution in Selected Herbig Ae/Be Systems</title>
			<authors>Rietmeijer, Frans J. M.; Nuth, Joseph A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 771, Issue 1, article id. 34, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...771...34R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...770..123G</bibcode>
			<title>Embedded Protostars in the Dust, Ice, and Gas In Time (DIGIT) Herschel Key Program: Continuum SEDs, and an Inventory of Characteristic Far-infrared Lines from PACS Spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Green, Joel D.; Evans, Neal J., II; Jrgensen, Jes K.; Herczeg, Gregory J.; Kristensen, Lars E.; Lee, Jeong-Eun; Dionatos, Odysseas; Yildiz, Umut A.; Salyk, Colette; Meeus, Gwendolyn; Bouwman, Jeroen; Visser, Ruud; Bergin, Edwin A.; van Dishoeck, Ewine F.; Rascati, Michelle R.; Karska, Agata; van Kempen, Tim A.; Dunham, Michael M.; Lindberg, Johan E.; Fedele, Davide; DIGIT Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 770, Issue 2, article id. 123, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;45&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>6/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...770..123G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...770...94B</bibcode>
			<title>VLT-CRIRES Survey of Rovibrational CO Emission from Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>Brown, J. M.; Pontoppidan, K. M.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Herczeg, G. J.; Blake, G. A.; Smette, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 770, Issue 2, article id. 94, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;21&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>6/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...770...94B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013PASP..125..477D</bibcode>
			<title>GASPS - A Herschel Survey of Gas and Dust in Protoplanetary Disks: Summary and Initial Statistics</title>
			<authors>Dent, W. R. F.; Thi, W. F.; Kamp, I.; Williams, J. P.; Menard, F.; Andrews, S.; Ardila, D.; Aresu, G.; Augereau, J.-C.; Barrado y Navascues, D.; Brittain, S.; Carmona, A.; Ciardi, D.; Danchi, W.; Donaldson, J.; Duchene, G.; Eiroa, C.; Fedele, D.; Grady, C.; de Gregorio-Molsalvo, I.; Howard, C.; Hulamo, N.; Krivov, A.; Lebreton, J.; Liseau, R.; Martin-Zaidi, C.; Mathews, G.; Meeus, G.; Mendiguta, I.; Montesinos, B.; Morales-Calderon, M.; Mora, A.; Nomura, H.; Pantin, E.; Pascucci, I.; Phillips, N.; Pinte, C.; Podio, L.; Ramsay, S. K.; Riaz, B.; Riviere-Marichalar, P.; Roberge, A.; Sandell, G.; Solano, E.; Tilling, I.; Torrelles, J. M.; Vandenbusche, B.; Vicente, S.; White, G. J.; Woitke, P.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 125, issue 927, pp.477-505</journal>
			<date>5/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013PASP..125..477D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...768...80K</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the Gap and AU-scale Asymmetries in the Pre-transitional Disk of V1247 Orionis</title>
			<authors>Kraus, Stefan; Ireland, Michael J.; Sitko, Michael L.; Monnier, John D.; Calvet, Nuria; Espaillat, Catherine; Grady, Carol A.; Harries, Tim J.; Hnig, Sebastian F.; Russell, Ray W.; Swearingen, Jeremy R.; Werren, Chelsea; Wilner, David J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 768, Issue 1, article id. 80, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;15&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>5/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...768...80K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...767..159B</bibcode>
			<title>High-resolution Near-infrared Spectroscopy of HD 100546. II. Analysis of Variable Rovibrational CO Emission Lines</title>
			<authors>Brittain, Sean D.; Najita, Joan R.; Carr, John S.; Liskowsky, Joseph; Troutman, Matthew R.; Doppmann, Greg W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 767, Issue 2, article id. 159, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...767..159B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...766...80Z</bibcode>
			<title>H2(v = 0,1) + C+(2 P) --&gt; H+CH+ State-to-state Rate Constants for Chemical Pumping Models in Astrophysical Media</title>
			<authors>Zanchet, Alexandre; Godard, B.; Bulut, Niyazi; Roncero, Octavio; Halvick, Philippe; Cernicharo, Jos</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 766, Issue 2, article id. 80, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...766...80Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...552A...4O</bibcode>
			<title>Sculpting the disk around T Chamaeleontis: an interferometric view</title>
			<authors>Olofsson, J.; Benisty, M.; Le Bouquin, J.-B.; Berger, J.-P.; Lacour, S.; M nard, F.; Henning, Th.; Crida, A.; Burtscher, L.; Meeus, G.; Ratzka, T.; Pinte, C.; Augereau, J.-C.; Malbet, F.; Lazareff, B.; Traub, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 552, id.A4, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...552A...4O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...766L...2Q</bibcode>
			<title>Gaps in the HD 169142 Protoplanetary Disk Revealed by Polarimetric Imaging: Signs of Ongoing Planet Formation?</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Avenhaus, Henning; Buenzli, Esther; Garufi, Antonio; Schmid, Hans Martin; Wolf, Sebastian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 766, Issue 1, article id. L2, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...766L...2Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...766L...1Q</bibcode>
			<title>A Young Protoplanet Candidate Embedded in the Circumstellar Disk of HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Amara, Adam; Meyer, Michael R.; Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Kasper, Markus; Girard, Julien H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 766, Issue 1, article id. L1, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...766L...1Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...766...54L</bibcode>
			<title>Absorption Efficiencies of Forsterite. I. Discrete Dipole Approximation Explorations in Grain Shape and Size</title>
			<authors>Lindsay, Sean S.; Wooden, Diane H.; Harker, David E.; Kelley, Michael S.; Woodward, Charles E.; Murphy, Jim R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 766, Issue 1, article id. 54, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;25&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...766...54L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...765...72J</bibcode>
			<title>Crystalline Silicates in Evolved Stars. I. Spitzer/Infrared Spectrograph Spectroscopy of IRAS 16456-3542, 18354-0638, and 23239+5754</title>
			<authors>Jiang, B. W.; Zhang, Ke; Li, Aigen; Lisse, C. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 765, Issue 1, article id. 72, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...765...72J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...551A..49T</bibcode>
			<title>Radiation thermo-chemical models of protoplanetary discs. IV. Modelling CO ro-vibrational emission from Herbig Ae discs</title>
			<authors>Thi, W. F.; Kamp, I.; Woitke, P.; van der Plas, G.; Bertelsen, R.; Wiesenfeld, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 551, id.A49, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;26&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...551A..49T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...550A..96N</bibcode>
			<title>The chemistry of ions in the Orion Bar I. - CH+, SH+, and CF+. The effect of high electron density and vibrationally excited H2 in a warm PDR surface</title>
			<authors>Nagy, Z.; Van der Tak, F. F. S.; Ossenkopf, V.; Gerin, M.; Le Petit, F.; Le Bourlot, J.; Black, J. H.; Goicoechea, J. R.; Joblin, C.; Rllig, M.; Bergin, E. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 550, id.A96, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...550A..96N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...550A...8G</bibcode>
			<title>A complete model of CH+ rotational excitation including radiative and chemical pumping processes</title>
			<authors>Godard, B.; Cernicharo, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 550, id.A8, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;19&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...550A...8G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...549A.112M</bibcode>
			<title>Why circumstellar disks are so faint in scattered light: the case of HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Mulders, G. D.; Min, M.; Dominik, C.; Debes, J. H.; Schneider, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 549, id.A112, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...549A.112M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012PASJ...64..124T</bibcode>
			<title>High-Resolution Near-Infrared Polarimetry of a Circumstellar Disk around UX Tau A</title>
			<authors>Tanii, Ryoko; Itoh, Yoichi; Kudo, Tomoyuki; Hioki, Tomonori; Oasa, Yumiko; Gupta, Ranjan; Sen, Asoke K.; Wisniewski, John P.; Muto, Takayuki; Grady, Carol A.; Hashimoto, Jun; Fukagawa, Misato; Mayama, Satoshi; Hornbeck, Jeremy; Sitko, Michael L.; Russell, Ray W.; Werren, Chelsea; Cur, Michel; Currie, Thayne; Ohashi, Nagayoshi; Okamoto, Yoshiko; Momose, Munetake; Honda, Mitsuhiko; Inutsuka, Shu-ichi; Takeuchi, Taku; Dong, Ruobing; Abe, Lyu; Brandner, Wolfgang; Brandt, Timothy D.; Carson, Joseph; Egner, Sebastian E.; Feldt, Markus; Fukue, Tsubasa; Goto, Miwa; Guyon, Olivier; Hayano, Yutaka; Hayashi, Masahiko; Hayashi, Saeko S.; Henning, Thomas; Hodapp, Klaus W.; Ishii, Miki; Iye, Masanori; Janson, Markus; Kandori, Ryo; Knapp, Gillian R.; Kusakabe, Nobuhiko; Kuzuhara, Masayuki; Matsuo, Taro; McElwain, Michael W.; Miyama, Shoken; Morino, Jun-ichi; Moro-Martn, Amaya; Nishimura, Tetsuro; Pyo, Tae-Soo; Serabyn, Eugene; Suto, Hiroshi; Suzuki, Ryuji; Takami, Michihiro; Takato, Naruhisa; Terada, Hiroshi; Thalmann, Christian; Tomono, Daigo; Turner, Edwin L.; Watanabe, Makoto; Yamada, Toru; Takami, Hideki; Usuda, Tomonori; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.64, No.6, Article No.124, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012PASJ...64..124T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...760..153L</bibcode>
			<title>High-resolution Near-infrared Spectroscopy of HD 100546. I. Analysis of Asymmetric Ro-vibrational OH Emission Lines</title>
			<authors>Liskowsky, Joseph P.; Brittain, Sean D.; Najita, Joan R.; Carr, John S.; Doppmann, Greg W.; Troutman, Matthew R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 760, Issue 2, article id. 153, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...760..153L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...548A..40C</bibcode>
			<title>Nanostructuration of carbonaceous dust as seen through the positions of the 6.2 and 7.7 mum AIBs</title>
			<authors>Carpentier, Y.; Fraud, G.; Dartois, E.; Brunetto, R.; Charon, E.; Cao, A.-T.; d'Hendecourt, L.; Brchignac, Ph.; Rouzaud, J.-N.; Pino, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 548, id.A40, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...548A..40C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...547A..68M</bibcode>
			<title>Far-ultraviolet and X-ray irradiated protoplanetary disks: a grid of models. I. The disk structure</title>
			<authors>Meijerink, R.; Aresu, G.; Kamp, I.; Spaans, M.; Thi, W.-F.; Woitke, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 547, id.A68, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>11/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...547A..68M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...547A..58G</bibcode>
			<title>Planet gaps in the dust layer of 3D protoplanetary disks. II. Observability with ALMA</title>
			<authors>Gonzalez, J.-F.; Pinte, C.; Maddison, S. T.; Mnard, F.; Fouchet, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 547, id.A58, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;15&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>11/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...547A..58G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757..129R</bibcode>
			<title>Kinematics of the CO Gas in the Inner Regions of the TW Hya Disk</title>
			<authors>Rosenfeld, Katherine A.; Qi, Chunhua; Andrews, Sean M.; Wilner, David J.; Corder, Stuartt A.; Dullemond, C. P.; Lin, Shin-Yi; Hughes, A. M.; D'Alessio, Paola; Ho, P. T. P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 2, article id. 129, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;15&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757..129R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757...28C</bibcode>
			<title>Keck/NIRC2 Imaging of the Warped, Asymmetric Debris Disk around HD 32297</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Rodigas, Timothy J.; Debes, John; Plavchan, Peter; Kuchner, Marc; Jang-Condell, Hannah; Wilner, David; Andrews, Sean; Kraus, Adam; Dahm, Scott; Robitaille, Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 1, article id. 28, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;15&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757...28C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...756..133C</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer MIPS Study of 2.5-2.0 M &amp;sun; Stars in Scorpius-Centaurus</title>
			<authors>Chen, Christine H.; Pecaut, Mark; Mamajek, Eric E.; Su, Kate Y. L.; Bitner, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 756, Issue 2, article id. 133, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;24&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...756..133C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...545A..81P</bibcode>
			<title>Ring shaped dust accumulation in transition disks</title>
			<authors>Pinilla, P.; Benisty, M.; Birnstiel, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 545, id.A81, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...545A..81P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJS..201...11K</bibcode>
			<title>Mid-infrared Spectral Variability Atlas of Young Stellar Objects</title>
			<authors>Kspl, .; brahm, P.; Acosta-Pulido, J. A.; Dullemond, C. P.; Henning, Th.; Kun, M.; Leinert, Ch.; Mor, A.; Turner, N. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 201, Issue 2, article id. 11, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;34&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJS..201...11K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754L..31C</bibcode>
			<title>The Dynamically Disrupted Gap in HD 142527</title>
			<authors>Casassus, S.; Perez M., S.; Jordn, A.; Mnard, F.; Cuadra, J.; Schreiber, M. R.; Hales, A. S.; Ercolano, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 754, Issue 2, article id. L31, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754L..31C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AN....333..594P</bibcode>
			<title>Measuring the mass accretion rates of Herbig Ae/Be stars with X-shooter</title>
			<authors>Pogodin, M. A.; Hubrig, S.; Yudin, R. V.; Schller, M.; Gonzlez, J. F.; Stelzer, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.333, Issue 7, p.594-612</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AN....333..594P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...544A..78M</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of Herbig Ae/Be stars with Herschel/PACS. The atomic and molecular contents of their protoplanetary discs</title>
			<authors>Meeus, G.; Montesinos, B.; Mendiguta, I.; Kamp, I.; Thi, W. F.; Eiroa, C.; Grady, C. A.; Mathews, G.; Sandell, G.; Martin-Zadi, C.; Brittain, S.; Dent, W. R. F.; Howard, C.; Mnard, F.; Pinte, C.; Roberge, A.; Vandenbussche, B.; Williams, J. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 544, id.A78, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...544A..78M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...753..153K</bibcode>
			<title>High-contrast Near-infrared Polarization Imaging of MWC480</title>
			<authors>Kusakabe, N.; Grady, C. A.; Sitko, M. L.; Hashimoto, J.; Kudo, T.; Fukagawa, M.; Muto, T.; Wisniewski, J. P.; Min, M.; Mayama, S.; Werren, C.; Day, A. N.; Beerman, L. C.; Lynch, D. K.; Russell, R. W.; Brafford, S. M.; Kuzuhara, M.; Brandt, T. D.; Abe, L.; Brandner, W.; Carson, J.; Egner, S.; Feldt, M.; Goto, M.; Guyon, O.; Hayano, Y.; Hayashi, M.; Hayashi, S. S.; Henning, T.; Hodapp, K. W.; Ishii, M.; Iye, M.; Janson, M.; Kandori, R.; Knapp, G. R.; Matsuo, T.; McElwain, M. W.; Miyama, S.; Morino, J.-I.; Moro-Martin, A.; Nishimura, T.; Pyo, T.-S.; Suto, H.; Suzuki, R.; Takami, M.; Takato, N.; Terada, H.; Thalmann, C.; Tomono, D.; Turner, E. L.; Watanabe, M.; Yamada, T.; Takami, H.; Usuda, T.; Tamura, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 753, Issue 2, article id. 153, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...753..153K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752..143H</bibcode>
			<title>Mid-infrared Imaging of the Transitional Disk of HD 169142: Measuring the Size of the Gap</title>
			<authors>Honda, M.; Maaskant, Koen; Okamoto, Y. K.; Kataza, H.; Fukagawa, M.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Dominik, C.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.; Mulders, G. D.; Min, M.; Yamashita, T.; Fujiyoshi, T.; Miyata, T.; Sako, S.; Sakon, I.; Fujiwara, H.; Onaka, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 2, article id. 143, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752..143H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.2072F</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical abundances of magnetic and non-magnetic Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Folsom, C. P.; Bagnulo, S.; Wade, G. A.; Alecian, E.; Landstreet, J. D.; Marsden, S. C.; Waite, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 3, pp. 2072-2101.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.2072F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..149T</bibcode>
			<title>Crystallographically Anisotropic Shape of Forsterite: New Probe for Evaluating Dust Formation History from Infrared Spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Takigawa, Aki; Tachibana, Shogo</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 149, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..149T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..91B</bibcode>
			<title>The warm gas atmosphere of the HD 100546 disk seen by Herschel. Evidence of a gas-rich, carbon-poor atmosphere?</title>
			<authors>Bruderer, S.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Doty, S. D.; Herczeg, G. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A91, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;28&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..91B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.421.2368J</bibcode>
			<title>Density waves in debris discs and galactic nuclei</title>
			<authors>Jalali, Mir Abbas; Tremaine, Scott</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 421, Issue 3, pp. 2368-2383.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.421.2368J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...748L..22M</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of Small-scale Spiral Structures in the Disk of SAO 206462 (HD 135344B): Implications for the Physical State of the Disk from Spiral Density Wave Theory</title>
			<authors>Muto, T.; Grady, C. A.; Hashimoto, J.; Fukagawa, M.; Hornbeck, J. B.; Sitko, M.; Russell, R.; Werren, C.; Cur, M.; Currie, T.; Ohashi, N.; Okamoto, Y.; Momose, M.; Honda, M.; Inutsuka, S.; Takeuchi, T.; Dong, R.; Abe, L.; Brandner, W.; Brandt, T.; Carson, J.; Egner, S.; Feldt, M.; Fukue, T.; Goto, M.; Guyon, O.; Hayano, Y.; Hayashi, M.; Hayashi, S.; Henning, T.; Hodapp, K. W.; Ishii, M.; Iye, M.; Janson, M.; Kandori, R.; Knapp, G. R.; Kudo, T.; Kusakabe, N.; Kuzuhara, M.; Matsuo, T.; Mayama, S.; McElwain, M. W.; Miyama, S.; Morino, J.-I.; Moro-Martin, A.; Nishimura, T.; Pyo, T.-S.; Serabyn, E.; Suto, H.; Suzuki, R.; Takami, M.; Takato, N.; Terada, H.; Thalmann, C.; Tomono, D.; Turner, E. L.; Watanabe, M.; Wisniewski, J. P.; Yamada, T.; Takami, H.; Usuda, T.; Tamura, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 748, Issue 2, article id. L22, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...748L..22M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..84H</bibcode>
			<title>Water in star-forming regions with Herschel: highly excited molecular emission from the NGC 1333 IRAS 4B outflow</title>
			<authors>Herczeg, G. J.; Karska, A.; Bruderer, S.; Kristensen, L. E.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Jrgensen, J. K.; Visser, R.; Wampfler, S. F.; Bergin, E. A.; Yildiz, U. A.; Pontoppidan, K. M.; Gracia-Carpio, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A84, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;23&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..84H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.420.2569B</bibcode>
			<title>Laboratory far-infrared spectroscopy of terrestrial sulphides to support analysis of cosmic dust spectra</title>
			<authors>Brusentsova, T.; Peale, R. E.; Maukonen, D.; Figueiredo, P.; Harlow, G. E.; Ebel, D. S.; Nissinboim, A.; Sherman, K.; Lisse, C. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 420, Issue 3, pp. 2569-2579.</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.420.2569B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...747...93L</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Evidence for a Late-heavy Bombardment and the Formation of Ureilites in eta Corvi at ~1 Gyr</title>
			<authors>Lisse, C. M.; Wyatt, M. C.; Chen, C. H.; Morlok, A.; Watson, D. M.; Manoj, P.; Sheehan, P.; Currie, T. M.; Thebault, P.; Sitko, M. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 747, Issue 2, article id. 93, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;25&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...747...93L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..81G</bibcode>
			<title>Warm gas at 50 AU in the disk around Herbig Be star HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Goto, M.; van der Plas, G.; van den Ancker, M.; Dullemond, C. P.; Carmona, A.; Henning, Th.; Meeus, G.; Linz, H.; Stecklum, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A81, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..81G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A.129B</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic field measurements and their uncertainties: the FORS1 legacy</title>
			<authors>Bagnulo, S.; Landstreet, J. D.; Fossati, L.; Kochukhov, O.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A129, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;22&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A.129B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A..92Q</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the inner regions of the HD 97048 circumstellar disk with VLT/NACO polarimetric differential imaging</title>
			<authors>Quanz, S. P.; Birkmann, S. M.; Apai, D.; Wolf, S.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A92, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A..92Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..116B</bibcode>
			<title>A 30 AU Radius CO Gas Hole in the Disk around the Herbig Ae Star Oph IRS 48</title>
			<authors>Brown, J. M.; Herczeg, G. J.; Pontoppidan, K. M.; van Dishoeck, E. F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 116, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744...54H</bibcode>
			<title>PDS 144: The First Confirmed Herbig Ae-Herbig Ae Wide Binary</title>
			<authors>Hornbeck, J. B.; Grady, C. A.; Perrin, M. D.; Wisniewski, J. P.; Tofflemire, B. M.; Brown, A.; Holtzman, J. A.; Arraki, K.; Hamaguchi, K.; Woodgate, B.; Petre, R.; Daly, B.; Grogin, N. A.; Bonfield, D. G.; Williger, G. M.; Lauroesch, J. T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 1, article id. 54, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744...54H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.102M</bibcode>
			<title>Enhanced H2O formation through dust grain chemistry in X-ray exposed environments</title>
			<authors>Meijerink, R.; Cazaux, S.; Spaans, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A102, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...537A.102M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012BaltA..21..379B</bibcode>
			<title>Science with the Vo: Spectroscopic Studies of Herbig Ae/Be Stars</title>
			<authors>Baines, D.; Gonzalez, J.; Arviset, C.; Barbarisi, I.; Laruelo, A.; Leon, I.; Ortiz de Landaluce, I.; Osuna, P.; Rios, C.; Salgado, J.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, Vol. 21, p. 379-386</journal>
			<date>0/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012BaltA..21..379B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Msngr.146...25Q</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the Inner Regions of Circumstellar Discs with VLT/NACO Polarimetric Differential Imaging</title>
			<authors>Quanz, S. P.; Schmid, H. M.; Birkmann, S. M.; Apai, D.; Wolf, S.; Brandner, W.; Meyer, M. R.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 146, p. 25-27</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Msngr.146...25Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..112S</bibcode>
			<title>CO Rovibrational Emission as a Probe of Inner Disk Structure</title>
			<authors>Salyk, C.; Blake, G. A.; Boogert, A. C. A.; Brown, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 112, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..112S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416.3108R</bibcode>
			<title>Multidimensional Bayesian membership analysis of the Sco OB2 moving group</title>
			<authors>Rizzuto, A. C.; Ireland, M. J.; Robertson, J. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 416, Issue 4, pp. 3108-3117.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.416.3108R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...23Q</bibcode>
			<title>Very Large Telescope/NACO Polarimetric Differential Imaging of HD100546---Disk Structure and Dust Grain Properties between 10 and 140 AU</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Schmid, Hans Martin; Geissler, Kerstin; Meyer, Michael R.; Henning, Thomas; Brandner, Wolfgang; Wolf, Sebastian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 23, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...23Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..39C</bibcode>
			<title>A survey for near-infrared H2 emission in Herbig Ae/Be stars: emission from the outer disks of HD 97048 and HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Carmona, A.; van der Plas, G.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Audard, M.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Fedele, D.; Acke, B.; Pantin, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A39, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..39C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.1105S</bibcode>
			<title>Distance limits to intermediate- and high-velocity clouds</title>
			<authors>Smoker, J. V.; Fox, A. J.; Keenan, F. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 2, pp. 1105-1118.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.1105S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A.101D</bibcode>
			<title>Accretion through the inner hole of transitional disks: what happens to the dust?</title>
			<authors>Dominik, C.; Dullemond, C. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A101, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A.101D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..93M</bibcode>
			<title>Low abundance, strong features: window-dressing crystalline forsterite in the disk wall of HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Mulders, G. D.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Dominik, C.; Sturm, B.; Bouwman, J.; Min, M.; Verhoeff, A. P.; Acke, B.; Augereau, J. C.; Evans, N. J.; Henning, Th.; Meeus, G.; Olofsson, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A93, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;17&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..93M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A...1T</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining the structure of the planet-forming region in the disk of the Herbig Be star HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Tatulli, E.; Benisty, M.; Mnard, F.; Varnire, P.; Martin-Zadi, C.; Thi, W.-F.; Pinte, C.; Massi, F.; Weigelt, G.; Hofmann, K.-H.; Petrov, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A1, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A...1T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734..115C</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Infrared Spectrograph Spectroscopy of the 10 Myr Old EF Cha Debris Disk: Evidence for Phyllosilicate-rich Dust in the Terrestrial Zone</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Lisse, Carey M.; Sicilia-Aguilar, Aurora; Rieke, George H.; Su, Kate Y. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 115, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734..115C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734...51O</bibcode>
			<title>On the Evolution of Dust Mineralogy, from Protoplanetary Disks to Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Oliveira, Isa; Olofsson, Johan; Pontoppidan, Klaus M.; van Dishoeck, Ewine F.; Augereau, Jean-Charles; Mern, Bruno</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 1, article id. 51, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;17&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734...51O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...530L...2T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of CH+ emission from the disc around HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Thi, W.-F.; Mnard, F.; Meeus, G.; Martin-Zadi, C.; Woitke, P.; Tatulli, E.; Benisty, M.; Kamp, I.; Pascucci, I.; Pinte, C.; Grady, C. A.; Brittain, S.; White, G. J.; Howard, C. D.; Sandell, G.; Eiroa, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 530, id.L2, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...530L...2T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732..106F</bibcode>
			<title>Water Depletion in the Disk Atmosphere of Herbig AeBe Stars</title>
			<authors>Fedele, D.; Pascucci, I.; Brittain, S.; Kamp, I.; Woitke, P.; Williams, J. P.; Dent, W. R. F.; Thi, W.-F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. 106, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732..106F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732....6K</bibcode>
			<title>IRAS 15099-5856: Remarkable Mid-infrared Source with Prominent Crystalline Silicate Emission Embedded in the Supernova Remnant MSH15-52</title>
			<authors>Koo, Bon-Chul; McKee, Christopher F.; Suh, Kyung-Won; Moon, Dae-Sik; Onaka, Takashi; Burton, Michael G.; Hiramatsu, Masaaki; Bessell, Michael S.; Gaensler, B. M.; Kim, Hyun-Jeong; Lee, Jae-Joon; Jeong, Woong-Seob; Lee, Ho-Gyu; Im, Myungshin; Tatematsu, Ken'ichi; Kohno, Kotaro; Kawabe, Ryohei; Ezawa, Hajime; Wilson, Grant; Yun, Min S.; Hughes, David H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 6, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732....6K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528L...6O</bibcode>
			<title>Warm dust resolved in the cold disk around T Chamaeleontis with VLTI/AMBER</title>
			<authors>Olofsson, J.; Benisty, M.; Augereau, J.-C.; Pinte, C.; Mnard, F.; Tatulli, E.; Berger, J.-P.; Malbet, F.; Mern, B.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Lacour, S.; Pontoppidan, K. M.; Monin, J.-L.; Brown, J. M.; Blake, G. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.L6, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528L...6O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729L..17H</bibcode>
			<title>Direct Imaging of Fine Structures in Giant Planet-forming Regions of the Protoplanetary Disk Around AB Aurigae</title>
			<authors>Hashimoto, J.; Tamura, M.; Muto, T.; Kudo, T.; Fukagawa, M.; Fukue, T.; Goto, M.; Grady, C. A.; Henning, T.; Hodapp, K.; Honda, M.; Inutsuka, S.; Kokubo, E.; Knapp, G.; McElwain, M. W.; Momose, M.; Ohashi, N.; Okamoto, Y. K.; Takami, M.; Turner, E. L.; Wisniewski, J.; Janson, M.; Abe, L.; Brandner, W.; Carson, J.; Egner, S.; Feldt, M.; Golota, T.; Guyon, O.; Hayano, Y.; Hayashi, M.; Hayashi, S.; Ishii, M.; Kandori, R.; Kusakabe, N.; Matsuo, T.; Mayama, S.; Miyama, S.; Morino, J.-I.; Moro-Martin, A.; Nishimura, T.; Pyo, T.-S.; Suto, H.; Suzuki, R.; Takato, N.; Terada, H.; Thalmann, C.; Tomono, D.; Watanabe, M.; Yamada, T.; Takami, H.; Usuda, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. L17, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729L..17H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASP..123..138V</bibcode>
			<title>Water in Star-forming Regions with the Herschel Space Observatory (WISH). I. Overview of Key Program and First Results</title>
			<authors>van Dishoeck, E. F.; Kristensen, L. E.; Benz, A. O.; Bergin, E. A.; Caselli, P.; Cernicharo, J.; Herpin, F.; Hogerheijde, M. R.; Johnstone, D.; Liseau, R.; Nisini, B.; Shipman, R.; Tafalla, M.; van der Tak, F.; Wyrowski, F.; Aikawa, Y.; Bachiller, R.; Baudry, A.; Benedettini, M.; Bjerkeli, P.; Blake, G. A.; Bontemps, S.; Braine, J.; Brinch, C.; Bruderer, S.; Chavarra, L.; Codella, C.; Daniel, F.; de Graauw, Th.; Deul, E.; di Giorgio, A. M.; Dominik, C.; Doty, S. D.; Dubernet, M. L.; Encrenaz, P.; Feuchtgruber, H.; Fich, M.; Frieswijk, W.; Fuente, A.; Giannini, T.; Goicoechea, J. R.; Helmich, F. P.; Herczeg, G. J.; Jacq, T.; Jrgensen, J. K.; Karska, A.; Kaufman, M. J.; Keto, E.; Larsson, B.; Lefloch, B.; Lis, D.; Marseille, M.; McCoey, C.; Melnick, G.; Neufeld, D.; Olberg, M.; Pagani, L.; Panic, O.; Parise, B.; Pearson, J. C.; Plume, R.; Risacher, C.; Salter, D.; Santiago-Garca, J.; Saraceno, P.; Stuber, P.; van Kempen, T. A.; Visser, R.; Viti, S.; Walmsley, M.; Wampfler, S. F.; Yildiz, U. A.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 123, issue 900, pp.138-170</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASP..123..138V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...46D</bibcode>
			<title>Measuring the Stellar Accretion Rates of Herbig Ae/Be Stars</title>
			<authors>Donehew, Brian; Brittain, Sean</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 46, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...46D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A..24V</bibcode>
			<title>Distinguishing post-AGB impostors in a sample of pre-main sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Vieira, R. G.; Gregorio-Hetem, J.; Hetem, A.; Stasinska, G.; Szczerba, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A24, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A..24V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.410..190T</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of young runaway Hipparcos stars within 3 kpc from the Sun</title>
			<authors>Tetzlaff, N.; Neuhuser, R.; Hohle, M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 410, Issue 1, pp. 190-200.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.410..190T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..470M</bibcode>
			<title>Shocks and a Giant Planet in the Disk Orbiting BP Piscium?</title>
			<authors>Melis, C.; Gielen, C.; Chen, C. H.; Rhee, Joseph H.; Song, Inseok; Zuckerman, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. 470-479 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..470M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L.243B</bibcode>
			<title>The Protoplanetary Disk Around the M4 Star RECX 5: Witnessing the Influence of Planet Formation?</title>
			<authors>Bouwman, J.; Lawson, W. A.; Juhsz, A.; Dominik, C.; Feigelson, E. D.; Henning, Th.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 2, pp. L243-L247 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723L.243B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..65C</bibcode>
			<title>Abundances in the Herbig Ae star HD 101412. Abundance anomalies; lambda Boo-Vega characteristics?</title>
			<authors>Cowley, C. R.; Hubrig, S.; Gonzlez, J. F.; Savanov, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A65, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..65C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48...21H</bibcode>
			<title>Cosmic Silicates</title>
			<authors>Henning, Thomas</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.21-46</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48...21H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721..431J</bibcode>
			<title>Dust Evolution in Protoplanetary Disks Around Herbig Ae/Be Stars---the Spitzer View</title>
			<authors>Juhsz, A.; Bouwman, J.; Henning, Th.; Acke, B.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Meeus, G.; Dominik, C.; Min, M.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 1, pp. 431-455 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721..431J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..61C</bibcode>
			<title>C I observations in the CQ Tauri proto-planetary disk: evidence of a very low gas-to-dust ratio ?</title>
			<authors>Chapillon, E.; Parise, B.; Guilloteau, S.; Dutrey, A.; Wakelam, V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A61, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..61C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A.110P</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of warm molecular gas and kinematics in the disc around HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Panic, O.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Hogerheijde, M. R.; Belloche, A.; Gsten, R.; Boland, W.; Baryshev, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A110, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A.110P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719.1565G</bibcode>
			<title>Locating the Accretion Footprint on a Herbig Ae Star: MWC 480</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Hamaguchi, K.; Schneider, G.; Stecklum, B.; Woodgate, B. E.; McCleary, J. E.; Williger, G. M.; Sitko, M. L.; Mnard, F.; Henning, Th.; Brittain, S.; Troutmann, M.; Donehew, B.; Hines, D.; Wisniewski, J. P.; Lynch, D. K.; Russell, R. W.; Rudy, R. J.; Day, A. N.; Shenoy, A.; Wilner, D.; Silverstone, M.; Bouret, J.-C.; Meusinger, H.; Clampin, M.; Kim, S.; Petre, R.; Sahu, M.; Endres, M.; Collins, K. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 2, pp. 1565-1581 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719.1565G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.199H</bibcode>
			<title>Pre-transitional Disk Nature of the AB Aur Disk</title>
			<authors>Honda, M.; Inoue, A. K.; Okamoto, Y. K.; Kataza, H.; Fukagawa, M.; Yamashita, T.; Fujiyoshi, T.; Tamura, M.; Hashimoto, J.; Miyata, T.; Sako, S.; Sakon, I.; Fujiwara, H.; Kamizuka, T.; Onaka, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L199-L203 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.199H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..558A</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer's View on Aromatic and Aliphatic Hydrocarbon Emission in Herbig Ae Stars</title>
			<authors>Acke, B.; Bouwman, J.; Juhsz, A.; Henning, Th.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Meeus, G.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 1, pp. 558-574 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..558A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;ARv..18..317A</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and evolution of planetary systems: the impact of high-angular resolution optical techniques</title>
			<authors>Absil, Olivier; Mawet, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomy and Astrophysics Review, Volume 18, Issue 3, pp.317-382</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26ARv..18..317A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518L.129S</bibcode>
			<title>First results of the Herschel key program ``Dust, Ice and Gas In Time'' (DIGIT): Dust and gas spectroscopy of HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Sturm, B.; Bouwman, J.; Henning, Th.; Evans, N. J.; Acke, B.; Mulders, G. D.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Meeus, G.; Green, J. D.; Augereau, J. C.; Olofsson, J.; Salyk, C.; Najita, J.; Herczeg, G. J.; van Kempen, T. A.; Kristensen, L. E.; Dominik, C.; Carr, J. S.; Waelkens, C.; Bergin, E.; Blake, G. A.; Brown, J. M.; Chen, J.-H.; Cieza, L.; Dunham, M. M.; Glassgold, A.; Gdel, M.; Harvey, P. M.; Hogerheijde, M. R.; Jaffe, D.; Jrgensen, J. K.; Kim, H. J.; Knez, C.; Lacy, J. H.; Lee, J.-E.; Maret, S.; Meijerink, R.; Mern, B.; Mundy, L.; Pontoppidan, K. M.; Visser, R.; Yildiz, U. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.L129, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518L.129S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518L.128V</bibcode>
			<title>Dust, Ice, and Gas In Time (DIGIT) Herschel program first results. A full PACS-SED scan of the gas line emission in protostar DK Chamaeleontis</title>
			<authors>van Kempen, T. A.; Green, J. D.; Evans, N. J.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Kristensen, L. E.; Herczeg, G. J.; Mern, B.; Lee, J.-E.; Jrgensen, J. K.; Bouwman, J.; Acke, B.; Adamkovics, M.; Augereau, J. C.; Bergin, E.; Blake, G. A.; Brown, J. M.; Carr, J. S.; Chen, J.-H.; Cieza, L.; Dominik, C.; Dullemond, C. P.; Dunham, M. M.; Glassgold, A.; Gdel, M.; Harvey, P. M.; Henning, Th.; Hogerheijde, M. R.; Jaffe, D.; Kim, H. J.; Knez, C.; Lacy, J. H.; Maret, S.; Meeus, G.; Meijerink, R.; Mulders, G. D.; Mundy, L.; Najita, J.; Olofsson, J.; Pontoppidan, K. M.; Salyk, C.; Sturm, B.; Visser, R.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Waelkens, C.; Yildiz, U. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.L128, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518L.128V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518L.121V</bibcode>
			<title>Origin of the hot gas in low-mass protostars. Herschel-PACS spectroscopy of HH 46</title>
			<authors>van Kempen, T. A.; Kristensen, L. E.; Herczeg, G. J.; Visser, R.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Wampfler, S. F.; Bruderer, S.; Benz, A. O.; Doty, S. D.; Brinch, C.; Hogerheijde, M. R.; Jrgensen, J. K.; Tafalla, M.; Neufeld, D.; Bachiller, R.; Baudry, A.; Benedettini, M.; Bergin, E. A.; Bjerkeli, P.; Blake, G. A.; Bontemps, S.; Braine, J.; Caselli, P.; Cernicharo, J.; Codella, C.; Daniel, F.; di Giorgio, A. M.; Dominik, C.; Encrenaz, P.; Fich, M.; Fuente, A.; Giannini, T.; Goicoechea, J. R.; de Graauw, Th.; Helmich, F.; Herpin, F.; Jacq, T.; Johnstone, D.; Kaufman, M. J.; Larsson, B.; Lis, D.; Liseau, R.; Marseille, M.; McCoey, C.; Melnick, G.; Nisini, B.; Olberg, M.; Parise, B.; Pearson, J. C.; Plume, R.; Risacher, C.; Santiago-Garca, J.; Saraceno, P.; Shipman, R.; van der Tak, F.; Wyrowski, F.; Yildiz, U. A.; Ciechanowicz, M.; Dubbeldam, L.; Glenz, S.; Huisman, R.; Lin, R. H.; Morris, P.; Murphy, J. A.; Trappe, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.L121, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518L.121V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A.110M</bibcode>
			<title>Where is the warm H2? A search for H2 emission from disks around Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Martin-Zadi, C.; Augereau, J.-C.; Mnard, F.; Olofsson, J.; Carmona, A.; Pinte, C.; Habart, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A110, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A.110M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...515A.111S</bibcode>
			<title>The PASTEL catalogue of stellar parameters</title>
			<authors>Soubiran, C.; Le Campion, J.-F.; Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Caillo, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 515, id.A111, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...515A.111S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...514A...2I</bibcode>
			<title>AKARI's infrared view on nearby stars. Using AKARI infrared camera all-sky survey, 2MASS, and Hipparcos catalogs</title>
			<authors>Ita, Y.; Matsuura, M.; Ishihara, D.; Oyabu, S.; Takita, S.; Kataza, H.; Yamamura, I.; Matsunaga, N.; Tanab, T.; Nakada, Y.; Fujiwara, H.; Wada, T.; Onaka, T.; Matsuhara, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 514, id.A2, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...514A...2I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..347F</bibcode>
			<title>Subaru Near-Infrared Imaging of Herbig Ae Stars</title>
			<authors>Fukagawa, Misato; Tamura, Motohide; Itoh, Yoichi; Oasa, Yumiko; Kudo, Tomoyuki; Hayashi, Saeko S.; Kato, Eri; Ootsubo, Takafumi; Itoh, Yusuke; Shibai, Hiroshi; Hayashi, Masahiko</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.2, pp.347--370</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..347F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403..211T</bibcode>
			<title>Dust settling in magnetorotationally-driven turbulent discs - II. The pervasiveness of the streaming instability and its consequences</title>
			<authors>Tilley, David A.; Balsara, Dinshaw S.; Brittain, Sean D.; Rettig, Terrence</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 1, pp. 211-228.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403..211T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..187..149A</bibcode>
			<title>StarCAT: A Catalog of Space Telescope Imaging Spectrograph Ultraviolet Echelle Spectra of Stars</title>
			<authors>Ayres, Thomas R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 187, Issue 1, pp. 149-171 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..187..149A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..186..259R</bibcode>
			<title>The Taurus Spitzer Survey: New Candidate Taurus Members Selected Using Sensitive Mid-Infrared Photometry</title>
			<authors>Rebull, L. M.; Padgett, D. L.; McCabe, C.-E.; Hillenbrand, L. A.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Noriega-Crespo, A.; Carey, S. J.; Brooke, T.; Huard, T.; Terebey, S.; Audard, M.; Monin, J.-L.; Fukagawa, M.; Gdel, M.; Knapp, G. R.; Menard, F.; Allen, L. E.; Angione, J. R.; Baldovin-Saavedra, C.; Bouvier, J.; Briggs, K.; Dougados, C.; Evans, N. J.; Flagey, N.; Guieu, S.; Grosso, N.; Glauser, A. M.; Harvey, P.; Hines, D.; Latter, W. B.; Skinner, S. L.; Strom, S.; Tromp, J.; Wolf, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 186, Issue 2, pp. 259-307 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..186..259R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511A..75B</bibcode>
			<title>The complex structure of the disk around HD 100546. The inner few astronomical units</title>
			<authors>Benisty, M.; Tatulli, E.; Mnard, F.; Swain, M. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.A75, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...511A..75B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....139...27S</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of the Pico Dos Dias Survey Herbig Ae/Be Candidates</title>
			<authors>Sartori, Marlia J.; Gregorio-Hetem, Jane; Rodrigues, Claudia V.; Hetem, Annibal, Jr.; Batalha, Celso</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 139, Issue 1, article id. 27-38 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....139...27S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707L..97T</bibcode>
			<title>Anisotropic Evaporation of Forsterite and Its Implication for Dust Formation Conditions in Circumstellar Environments</title>
			<authors>Takigawa, A.; Tachibana, S.; Nagahara, H.; Ozawa, K.; Yokoyama, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 707, Issue 1, pp. L97-L101 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707L..97T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508..707P</bibcode>
			<title>Characterising discs around Herbig Ae/Be stars through modelling of low-J 12CO lines</title>
			<authors>Panic, O.; Hogerheijde, M. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 2, 2009, pp.707-716</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508..707P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702...85B</bibcode>
			<title>Tracing the Inner Edge of the Disk Around HD 100546 with Rovibrational CO Emission Lines</title>
			<authors>Brittain, Sean D.; Najita, Joan R.; Carr, John S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 1, pp. 85-99 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702...85B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.2019L</bibcode>
			<title>Abundant Circumstellar Silica Dust and SiO Gas Created by a Giant Hypervelocity Collision in the ~12 Myr HD172555 System</title>
			<authors>Lisse, C. M.; Chen, C. H.; Wyatt, M. C.; Morlok, A.; Song, I.; Bryden, G.; Sheehan, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 2019-2032 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.2019L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009RAA.....9..770Z</bibcode>
			<title>An infrared study of Be stars based on ISO SWS01 spectra</title>
			<authors>Zhang, Pin; Fu, Zai-Qi</authors>
			<journal>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 9, Issue 7, pp. 770-776 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009RAA.....9..770Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.397...24B</bibcode>
			<title>Dust settling in magnetorotationally driven turbulent discs - I. Numerical methods and evidence for a vigorous streaming instability</title>
			<authors>Balsara, Dinshaw S.; Tilley, David A.; Rettig, Terrence; Brittain, Sean D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 397, Issue 1, pp. 24-43.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.397...24B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699.1822G</bibcode>
			<title>Revealing the Structure of a Pre-Transitional Disk: The Case of the Herbig F Star SAO 206462 (HD 135344B)</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Schneider, G.; Sitko, M. L.; Williger, G. M.; Hamaguchi, K.; Brittain, S. D.; Ablordeppey, K.; Apai, D.; Beerman, L.; Carpenter, W. J.; Collins, K. A.; Fukagawa, M.; Hammel, H. B.; Henning, Th.; Hines, D.; Kimes, R.; Lynch, D. K.; Mnard, F.; Pearson, R.; Russell, R. W.; Silverstone, M.; Smith, P. S.; Troutman, M.; Wilner, D.; Woodgate, B.; Clampin, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 2, pp. 1822-1842 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699.1822G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...502..367S</bibcode>
			<title>Tracing the potential planet-forming regions around seven pre-main-sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Schegerer, A. A.; Wolf, S.; Hummel, C. A.; Quanz, S. P.; Richichi, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 502, Issue 1, 2009, pp.367-383</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...502..367S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...502..283H</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for a link between the magnetic nature and other observed properties of Herbig Ae/Be stars and stars with debris disks</title>
			<authors>Hubrig, S.; Stelzer, B.; Schller, M.; Grady, C.; Schtz, O.; Pogodin, M. A.; Cur, M.; Hamaguchi, K.; Yudin, R. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 502, Issue 1, 2009, pp.283-301</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...502..283H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.2031R</bibcode>
			<title>The Alignment of the Polarization of Herbig Ae/Be Stars with the Interstellar Magnetic Field</title>
			<authors>Rodrigues, Cludia V.; Sartori, Marlia J.; Gregorio-Hetem, Jane; Magalhes, A. Mrio</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 2031-2035 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.2031R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698..131H</bibcode>
			<title>A Spatially Resolved Inner Hole in the Disk Around GM Aurigae</title>
			<authors>Hughes, A. Meredith; Andrews, Sean M.; Espaillat, Catherine; Wilner, David J.; Calvet, Nuria; D'Alessio, Paola; Qi, Chunhua; Williams, Jonathan P.; Hogerheijde, Michiel R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 1, pp. 131-142 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698..131H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500.1137V</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for CO depletion in the inner regions of gas-rich protoplanetary disks</title>
			<authors>van der Plas, G.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Acke, B.; Carmona, A.; Dominik, C.; Fedele, D.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1137-1141</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500.1137V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...697..557C</bibcode>
			<title>HD 100453: A Link Between Gas-Rich Protoplanetary Disks and Gas-Poor Debris Disks</title>
			<authors>Collins, K. A.; Grady, C. A.; Hamaguchi, K.; Wisniewski, J. P.; Brittain, S.; Sitko, M.; Carpenter, W. J.; Williams, J. P.; Mathews, G. S.; Williger, G. M.; van Boekel, R.; Carmona, A.; Henning, Th.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Meeus, G.; Chen, X. P.; Petre, R.; Woodgate, B. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 697, Issue 1, pp. 557-572 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...697..557C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394.1338B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of averaged stellar effective magnetic fields - II. Re-discussion of chemically peculiar A and B stars</title>
			<authors>Bychkov, V. D.; Bychkova, L. V.; Madej, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 3, pp. 1338-1350.</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394.1338B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...497..379M</bibcode>
			<title>MBM 12: young protoplanetary discs at high galactic latitude</title>
			<authors>Meeus, G.; Juhsz, A.; Henning, Th.; Bouwman, J.; Chen, C.; Lawson, W.; Apai, D.; Pascucci, I.; Sicilia-Aguilar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 497, Issue 2, 2009, pp.379-392</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...497..379M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...497..117A</bibcode>
			<title>Circumstellar disks around Herbig Be stars</title>
			<authors>Alonso-Albi, T.; Fuente, A.; Bachiller, R.; Neri, R.; Planesas, P.; Testi, L.; Bern, O.; Joblin, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 497, Issue 1, 2009, pp.117-136</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...497..117A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..697R</bibcode>
			<title>The Dust Cloud around the White Dwarf G 29-38. II. Spectrum from 5 to 40 mum and Mid-Infrared Photometric Variability</title>
			<authors>Reach, William T.; Lisse, Carey; von Hippel, Ted; Mullally, Fergal</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 697-712 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..697R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..610G</bibcode>
			<title>Spatially Resolved 3 mum Spectroscopy of Elias 1: Origin of Diamonds in Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>Goto, M.; Henning, Th.; Kouchi, A.; Takami, H.; Hayano, Y.; Usuda, T.; Takato, N.; Terada, H.; Oya, S.; Jger, C.; Andersen, A. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 610-616 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..610G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...495..901M</bibcode>
			<title>Parameters of Herbig Ae/Be and Vega-type stars</title>
			<authors>Montesinos, B.; Eiroa, C.; Mora, A.; Mern, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 495, Issue 3, 2009, pp.901-917</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...495..901M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...495..869L</bibcode>
			<title>Large grains in discs around young stars: ATCA observations of WW Chamaeleontis, RU Lupi, and CS Chamaeleontis</title>
			<authors>Lommen, D.; Maddison, S. T.; Wright, C. M.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Wilner, D. J.; Bourke, T. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 495, Issue 3, 2009, pp.869-879</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...495..869L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692.1609V</bibcode>
			<title>Disk Masses in the Embedded and T Tauri Phases of Stellar Evolution</title>
			<authors>Vorobyov, E. I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 692, Issue 2, pp. 1609-1622 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692.1609V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AJ....137...53S</bibcode>
			<title>STIS Imaging of the HR 4796A Circumstellar Debris Ring</title>
			<authors>Schneider, G.; Weinberger, A. J.; Becklin, E. E.; Debes, J. H.; Smith, B. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 137, Issue 1, pp. 53-61 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AJ....137...53S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...492..451M</bibcode>
			<title>A parameter study of self-consistent disk models around Herbig AeBe stars</title>
			<authors>Meijer, J.; Dominik, C.; de Koter, A.; Dullemond, C. P.; van Boekel, R.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 492, Issue 2, 2008, pp.451-461</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...492..451M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...492..245C</bibcode>
			<title>Identification of anthracene in Comet 1P/Halley</title>
			<authors>Clairemidi, J.; Moreels, G.; Mousis, O.; Brchignac, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 492, Issue 1, 2008, pp.245-250</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...492..245C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...492..117M</bibcode>
			<title>Far-infrared spectra of hydrous silicates at low temperatures. Providing laboratory data for Herschel and ALMA</title>
			<authors>Mutschke, H.; Zeidler, S.; Posch, Th.; Kerschbaum, F.; Baier, A.; Henning, Th.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 492, Issue 1, 2008, pp.117-125</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...492..117M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...490..725G</bibcode>
			<title>SPITZER survey of dust grain processing in stable discs around binary post-AGB stars</title>
			<authors>Gielen, C.; van Winckel, H.; Min, M.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Lloyd Evans, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 490, Issue 2, 2008, pp.725-735</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...490..725G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ARA&amp;A..46..289T</bibcode>
			<title>Interstellar Polycyclic Aromatic Hydrocarbon Molecules</title>
			<authors>Tielens, A. G. G. M.</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, vol. 46, Issue 1, pp.289-337</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ARA%26A..46..289T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684L..41D</bibcode>
			<title>Color Gradients Detected in the HD 15115 Circumstellar Disk</title>
			<authors>Debes, John H.; Weinberger, Alycia J.; Song, Inseok</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 1, pp. L41-L44.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684L..41D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684..411K</bibcode>
			<title>PAH Emission from Herbig Ae/Be Stars</title>
			<authors>Keller, Luke D.; Sloan, G. C.; Forrest, W. J.; Ayala, S.; D'Alessio, P.; Shah, S.; Calvet, N.; Najita, J.; Li, A.; Hartmann, L.; Sargent, B.; Watson, D. M.; Chen, C. H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 1, pp. 411-429.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684..411K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...485..487V</bibcode>
			<title>The structure of protoplanetary disks surrounding three young intermediate mass stars. I. Resolving the disk rotation in the [OI] 6300  line</title>
			<authors>van der Plas, G.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Fedele, D.; Acke, B.; Dominik, C.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Bouwman, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 485, Issue 2, 2008, pp.487-495</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...485..487V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008NewAR..52..117D</bibcode>
			<title>High-angular resolution imaging of disks and planets</title>
			<authors>Duchne, Gaspard</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 52, Issue 2-5, p. 117-144.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008NewAR..52..117D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008NewAR..52..105T</bibcode>
			<title>High angular resolution millimeter observations of circumstellar disks</title>
			<authors>Testi, Leonard; Leurini, Silvia</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 52, Issue 2-5, p. 105-116.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008NewAR..52..105T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008NewAR..52...94A</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of circumstellar disks with infrared interferometry</title>
			<authors>Akeson, Rachel</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 52, Issue 2-5, p. 94-104.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008NewAR..52...94A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.387..407P</bibcode>
			<title>The serendipitous discovery of a stellar ring at mid-infrared wavelengths</title>
			<authors>Phillips, J. P.; Ramos-Larios, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 387, Issue 1, pp. 407-414.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.387..407P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...679.1574O</bibcode>
			<title>The Solar-System-Scale Disk around AB Aurigae</title>
			<authors>Oppenheimer, Ben R.; Brenner, Douglas; Hinkley, Sasha; Zimmerman, Neil; Sivaramakrishnan, Anand; Soummer, Remi; Kuhn, Jeffrey; Graham, James R.; Perrin, Marshall; Lloyd, James P.; Roberts, Lewis C., Jr.; Harrington, David M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 679, Issue 2, pp. 1574-1581.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...679.1574O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...484..241B</bibcode>
			<title>The characteristics of the IR emission features in the spectra of Herbig Ae stars: evidence for chemical evolution</title>
			<authors>Boersma, C.; Bouwman, J.; Lahuis, F.; van Kerckhoven, C.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 484, Issue 1, 2008, pp.241-249</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...484..241B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...484..225M</bibcode>
			<title>Molecular hydrogen in the circumstellar environments of Herbig Ae/Be stars probed by FUSE</title>
			<authors>Martin-Zadi, C.; Deleuil, M.; Le Bourlot, J.; Bouret, J.-C.; Roberge, A.; Dullemond, C. P.; Testi, L.; Feldman, P. D.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 484, Issue 1, 2008, pp.225-239</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...484..225M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...483..485N</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling of diffuse molecular gas applied to HD 102065 observations</title>
			<authors>Nehm, C.; Le Bourlot, J.; Boulanger, F.; Pineau Des Forts, G.; Gry, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 483, Issue 2, 2008, pp.485-493</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...483..485N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1140W</bibcode>
			<title>Submillimeter Array Imaging of the Maser Emission from the H30alpha Radio Recombination Line in MWC 349A</title>
			<authors>Weintroub, Jonathan; Moran, James M.; Wilner, David J.; Young, Ken; Rao, Ramprasad; Shinnaga, Hiroko</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1140-1150.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1140W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AJ....135.1474H</bibcode>
			<title>The X-Ray Origin of Herbig AeBe Systems: New Insights</title>
			<authors>Hamidouche, Murad; Wang, Shiya; Looney, Leslie W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 135, Issue 4, pp. 1474-1481 (2008).</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AJ....135.1474H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.385..391A</bibcode>
			<title>Characterization of the magnetic field of the Herbig Be star HD200775</title>
			<authors>Alecian, E.; Catala, C.; Wade, G. A.; Donati, J.-F.; Petit, P.; Landstreet, J. D.; Bhm, T.; Bouret, J.-C.; Bagnulo, S.; Folsom, C.; Grunhut, J.; Silvester, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 385, Issue 1, pp. 391-403.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.385..391A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673.1106L</bibcode>
			<title>Circumstellar Dust Created by Terrestrial Planet Formation in HD 113766</title>
			<authors>Lisse, C. M.; Chen, C. H.; Wyatt, M. C.; Morlok, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 2, pp. 1106-1122.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673.1106L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476..853C</bibcode>
			<title>A search for near-infrared molecular hydrogen emission in the CTTS LkHalpha 264 and the debris disk 49 Ceti</title>
			<authors>Carmona, A.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Henning, Th.; Goto, M.; Fedele, D.; Stecklum, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 2, December III 2007, pp.853-862</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...476..853C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476..279G</bibcode>
			<title>Spatially extended polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons in circumstellar disks around T Tauri and Herbig Ae stars</title>
			<authors>Geers, V. C.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Visser, R.; Pontoppidan, K. M.; Augereau, J.-C.; Habart, E.; Lagrange, A. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 1, December II 2007, pp.279-289</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...476..279G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.381.1009V</bibcode>
			<title>Self-regulated gravitational accretion in protostellar discs</title>
			<authors>Vorobyov, E. I.; Basu, Shantanu</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 381, Issue 3, pp. 1009-1017.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.381.1009V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..629G</bibcode>
			<title>Dust-grain processing in circumbinary discs around evolved binaries. The RV Tauri spectral twins RU Centauri and AC Herculis</title>
			<authors>Gielen, C.; van Winckel, H.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Min, M.; Dominik, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.629-637</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..629G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...665.1391G</bibcode>
			<title>The Disk and Environment of a Young Vega Analog: HD 169142</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Schneider, G.; Hamaguchi, K.; Sitko, M. L.; Carpenter, W. J.; Hines, D.; Collins, K. A.; Williger, G. M.; Woodgate, B. E.; Henning, Th.; Mnard, F.; Wilner, D.; Petre, R.; Palunas, P.; Quirrenbach, A.; Nuth, J. A., III; Silverstone, M. D.; Kim, J. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 665, Issue 2, pp. 1391-1406.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...665.1391G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...665..512A</bibcode>
			<title>Hubble Space Telescope Advanced Camera for Surveys Coronagraphic Observations of the Dust Surrounding HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Ardila, D. R.; Golimowski, D. A.; Krist, J. E.; Clampin, M.; Ford, H. C.; Illingworth, G. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 665, Issue 1, pp. 512-534.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...665..512A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664L.107B</bibcode>
			<title>Cold Disks: Spitzer Spectroscopy of Disks around Young Stars with Large Gaps</title>
			<authors>Brown, J. M.; Blake, G. A.; Dullemond, C. P.; Mern, B.; Augereau, J. C.; Boogert, A. C. A.; Evans, N. J., II; Geers, V. C.; Lahuis, F.; Kessler-Silacci, J. E.; Pontoppidan, K. M.; van Dishoeck, E. F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. L107-L110.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664L.107B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660.1556R</bibcode>
			<title>Characterization of Dusty Debris Disks: The IRAS and Hipparcos Catalogs</title>
			<authors>Rhee, Joseph H.; Song, Inseok; Zuckerman, B.; McElwain, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 2, pp. 1556-1571.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660.1556R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AJ....133.2122D</bibcode>
			<title>HD 97048's Circumstellar Environment as Revealed by a Hubble Space Telescope ACS Coronagraphic Study of Disk Candidate Stars</title>
			<authors>Doering, R. L.; Meixner, M.; Holfeltz, S. T.; Krist, J. E.; Ardila, D. R.; Kamp, I.; Clampin, M. C.; Lubow, S. H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 133, Issue 5, pp. 2122-2131.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AJ....133.2122D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.376.1145W</bibcode>
			<title>A search for strong, ordered magnetic fields in Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Wade, G. A.; Bagnulo, S.; Drouin, D.; Landstreet, J. D.; Monin, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 376, Issue 3, pp. 1145-1161.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.376.1145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1164L</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of Herbig Ae Disks with Nulling Interferometry</title>
			<authors>Liu, Wilson M.; Hinz, Philip M.; Meyer, Michael R.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Hoffmann, William F.; Brusa, Guido; Miller, Doug; Kenworthy, Matthew A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1164-1172.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1164L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658..584L</bibcode>
			<title>On the Nature of the Dust in the Debris Disk around HD 69830</title>
			<authors>Lisse, C. M.; Beichman, C. A.; Bryden, G.; Wyatt, M. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 1, pp. 584-592.</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658..584L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...462..211L</bibcode>
			<title>Investigating grain growth in disks around southern T Tauri stars at millimetre wavelengths</title>
			<authors>Lommen, D.; Wright, C. M.; Maddison, S. T.; Jrgensen, J. K.; Bourke, T. L.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Hughes, A.; Wilner, D. J.; Burton, M.; van Langevelde, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 462, Issue 1, January IV 2007, pp.211-220</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...462..211L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...461..537G</bibcode>
			<title>Collisional dust avalanches in debris discs</title>
			<authors>Grigorieva, A.; Artymowicz, P.; Thbault, Ph.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 461, Issue 2, January II 2007, pp.537-549</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...461..537G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PABei..25..132L</bibcode>
			<title>Silicate dust in astrophysical environments.</title>
			<authors>Li, M.-P.; Zhao, G.; Li, A.-G.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, Vol. 25, p. 132-146 (2007)</journal>
			<date>0/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PABei..25..132L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.373.1619R</bibcode>
			<title>Dust filtration at gap edges: implications for the spectral energy distributions of discs with embedded planets</title>
			<authors>Rice, W. K. M.; Armitage, Philip J.; Wood, Kenneth; Lodato, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 373, Issue 4, pp. 1619-1626.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.373.1619R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653..657M</bibcode>
			<title>Evolution of Emission-Line Activity in Intermediate-Mass Young Stars</title>
			<authors>Manoj, P.; Bhatt, H. C.; Maheswar, G.; Muneer, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. 657-674.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653..657M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..117D</bibcode>
			<title>Mid-infrared imaging of the circumstellar dust around three Herbig Ae stars: HD 135344, CQ Tau, and HD 163296</title>
			<authors>Doucet, C.; Pantin, E.; Lagage, P. O.; Dullemond, C. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 1, December II 2006, pp.117-124</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..117D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650..956V</bibcode>
			<title>The Burst Mode of Protostellar Accretion</title>
			<authors>Vorobyov, E. I.; Basu, Shantanu</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 2, pp. 956-969.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650..956V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650..414S</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of an 86 AU Radius Debris Ring around HD 181327</title>
			<authors>Schneider, Glenn; Silverstone, Murray D.; Hines, Dean C.; Augereau, Jean-Charles; Pinte, Christophe; Mnard, Franois; Krist, John; Clampin, Mark; Grady, Carol; Golimowski, David; Ardila, David; Henning, Thomas; Wolf, Sebastian; Rodmann, Jens</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 1, pp. 414-431.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650..414S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...457..581G</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar parameters and evidence of circumstellar activity for a sample of Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Guimares, M. M.; Alencar, S. H. P.; Corradi, W. J. B.; Vieira, S. L. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 457, Issue 2, 2006, pp.581-589</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...457..581G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...457..223S</bibcode>
			<title>On the origin of the X-ray emission from Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Stelzer, B.; Micela, G.; Hamaguchi, K.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 457, Issue 1, October I 2006, pp.223-235</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...457..223S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...457..171A</bibcode>
			<title>A survey for nanodiamond features in the 3 micron spectra of Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Acke, B.; van den Ancker, M. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 457, Issue 1, October I 2006, pp.171-181</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...457..171A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.371..252L</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic analysis of southern B and Be stars</title>
			<authors>Levenhagen, R. S.; Leister, N. V.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 371, Issue 1, pp. 252-262.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.371..252L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...456.1045B</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling of PMS Ae/Fe stars using UV spectra</title>
			<authors>Blondel, P. F. C.; Djie, H. R. E. Tjin A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 456, Issue 3, September IV 2006, pp.1045-1068</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...456.1045B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006Sci...313..635L</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Spectral Observations of the Deep Impact Ejecta</title>
			<authors>Lisse, C. M.; VanCleve, J.; Adams, A. C.; A'Hearn, M. F.; Fernndez, Y. R.; Farnham, T. L.; Armus, L.; Grillmair, C. J.; Ingalls, J.; Belton, M. J. S.; Groussin, O.; McFadden, L. A.; Meech, K. J.; Schultz, P. H.; Clark, B. C.; Feaga, L. M.; Sunshine, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 313, Issue 5787, pp. 635-640 (2006).</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006Sci...313..635L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.370.1599S</bibcode>
			<title>Low-temperature single crystal reflection spectra of forsterite</title>
			<authors>Suto, H.; Sogawa, H.; Tachibana, S.; Koike, C.; Karoji, H.; Tsuchiyama, A.; Chihara, H.; Mizutani, K.; Akedo, J.; Ogiso, K.; Fukui, T.; Ohara, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 370, Issue 4, pp. 1599-1606.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.370.1599S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...645.1272P</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of an Optically Thick, Edge-on Disk around the Herbig Ae Star PDS 144N</title>
			<authors>Perrin, Marshall D.; Duchne, Gaspard; Kalas, Paul; Graham, James R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 645, Issue 2, pp. 1272-1282.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...645.1272P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006RMxAC..26..160G</bibcode>
			<title>Circumstellar Activity in Herbig Ae/Be Stars</title>
			<authors>Guimares, M. M.; Alencar, S. H. P.; Corradi, W. J. B.; Vieira, S. L. A.</authors>
			<journal>XI IAU Regional Latin American Meeting of Astronomy (Eds. L. Infante &amp; M. Rubio) Revista Mexicana de Astronoma y Astrofsica (Serie de Conferencias) Vol. 26, pp. 160</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006RMxAC..26..160G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.367..737B</bibcode>
			<title>On the binarity of Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Baines, Deborah; Oudmaijer, Ren D.; Porter, John M.; Pozzo, Monica</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 367, Issue 2, pp. 737-753.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.367..737B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...640.1078Q</bibcode>
			<title>The Warped Circumstellar Disk of HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Quillen, Alice C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 640, Issue 2, pp. 1078-1085.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...640.1078Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...449.1067H</bibcode>
			<title>Spatially resolved PAH emission in the inner disks of Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Habart, E.; Natta, A.; Testi, L.; Carbillet, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 449, Issue 3, April III 2006, pp.1067-1075</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...449.1067H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...449..267A</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the disk rotation of HD 97048 and HD 100546 in the [O I] 6300  line: evidence for a giant planet orbiting HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Acke, B.; van den Ancker, M. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 449, Issue 1, April I 2006, pp.267-279</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...449..267A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...446..785M</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of eclipsing variables</title>
			<authors>Malkov, O. Yu.; Oblak, E.; Snegireva, E. A.; Torra, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 446, Issue 2, February I 2006, pp.785-789</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...446..785M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...636..348V</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared and the Inner Regions of Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>Vinkovic, Dejan; Ivezic, Zeljko; Jurkic, Tomislav; Elitzur, Moshe</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 636, Issue 1, pp. 348-361.</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...636..348V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...445..331C</bibcode>
			<title>VLT/NACO adaptive optics imaging of the Herbig Ae star HD 100453</title>
			<authors>Chen, X. P.; Henning, T.; van Boekel, R.; Grady, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 445, Issue 1, January I 2006, pp.331-335</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...445..331C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005KFNT...21..414Z</bibcode>
			<title>The structure of our stellar system</title>
			<authors>Zakhozhay, V. A.</authors>
			<journal>Kinematika i Fizika Nebesnykh Tel, vol. 21, no. 6, p. 414-440</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005KFNT...21..414Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...632..956S</bibcode>
			<title>Mid-Infrared Spectra of Polycyclic Aromatic Hydrocarbon Emission in Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Sloan, G. C.; Keller, L. D.; Forrest, W. J.; Leibensperger, E.; Sargent, B.; Li, A.; Najita, J.; Watson, D. M.; Brandl, B. R.; Chen, C. H.; Green, J. D.; Markwick-Kemper, F.; Herter, T. L.; D'Alessio, P.; Morris, P. W.; Barry, D. J.; Hall, P.; Myers, P. C.; Houck, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 632, Issue 2, pp. 956-963.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...632..956S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...441..563V</bibcode>
			<title>Flaring and self-shadowed disks around Herbig Ae stars: simulations for 10 mum interferometers</title>
			<authors>van Boekel, R.; Dullemond, C. P.; Dominik, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 441, Issue 2, October II 2005, pp.563-571</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...441..563V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...630..958G</bibcode>
			<title>Coronagraphic Imaging of Pre-Main-Sequence Stars with the Hubble Space Telescope Space Telescope Imaging Spectrograph. I. The Herbig Ae Stars</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Woodgate, B. E.; Bowers, C. W.; Gull, T. R.; Sitko, M. L.; Carpenter, W. J.; Lynch, D. K.; Russell, R. W.; Perry, R. B.; Williger, G. M.; Roberge, A.; Bouret, Jean-Claude; Sahu, Meena</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 630, Issue 2, pp. 958-975.</journal>
			<date>9/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...630..958G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...440..921M</bibcode>
			<title>FUSE observations of molecular hydrogen on the line of sight towards HD 141569A</title>
			<authors>Martin-Zadi, C.; Deleuil, M.; Simon, T.; Bouret, J.-C.; Roberge, A.; Feldman, P. D.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 440, Issue 3, September IV 2005, pp.921-928</journal>
			<date>9/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...440..921M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005NewA...10..545E</bibcode>
			<title>An ISO-LWS two-colour diagram of Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Elia, Davide; Strafella, Francesco; Campeggio, Loretta; Maiolo, Berlinda; Pezzuto, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 10, Issue 7, p. 545-550.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005NewA...10..545E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...627..286T</bibcode>
			<title>The Differential Lifetimes of Protostellar Gas and Dust Disks</title>
			<authors>Takeuchi, Taku; Clarke, C. J.; Lin, D. N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 627, Issue 1, pp. 286-292.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...627..286T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...437..189V</bibcode>
			<title>A 10 mum spectroscopic survey of Herbig Ae star disks: Grain growth and crystallization</title>
			<authors>van Boekel, R.; Min, M.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; de Koter, A.; Dominik, C.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Bouwman, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 437, Issue 1, July I 2005, pp.189-208</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...437..189V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...626.1061B</bibcode>
			<title>An Excess Due to Small Grains around the Nearby K0 V Star HD 69830: Asteroid or Cometary Debris?</title>
			<authors>Beichman, C. A.; Bryden, G.; Gautier, T. N.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Werner, M. W.; Misselt, K.; Rieke, G.; Stansberry, J.; Trilling, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 626, Issue 2, pp. 1061-1069.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...626.1061B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...436..209A</bibcode>
			<title>[O I] 6300  emission in Herbig Ae/Be systems: Signature of Keplerian rotation</title>
			<authors>Acke, B.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Dullemond, C. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 436, Issue 1, June II 2005, pp.209-230</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...436..209A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...625..414T</bibcode>
			<title>Dust Growth and Settling in Protoplanetary Disks and Disk Spectral Energy Distributions. I. Laminar Disks</title>
			<authors>Tanaka, Hidekazu; Himeno, Youhei; Ida, Shigeru</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 625, Issue 1, pp. 414-426.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...625..414T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005AJ....129.2481Q</bibcode>
			<title>Driving Spiral Arms in the Circumstellar Disks of HD 100546 and HD 141569A</title>
			<authors>Quillen, Alice C.; Varnire, Peggy; Minchev, Ivan; Frank, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 129, Issue 5, pp. 2481-2495.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005AJ....129.2481Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...435..563C</bibcode>
			<title>The mid-IR spatially resolved environment of OH 26.5+0.6 at maximum luminosity</title>
			<authors>Chesneau, O.; Verhoelst, T.; Lopez, B.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Leinert, Ch.; Jaffe, W.; Khler, R.; de Koter, A.; Dijkstra, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 435, Issue 2, May IV 2005, pp.563-574</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...435..563C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Msngr.119...36W</bibcode>
			<title>Recent Astrophysical Results from the VLTI</title>
			<authors>Wittkowski, M.; Paresce, F.; Chesneau, O.; Kervella, P.; Meilland, A.; Meisenheimer, K.; Ohnaka, K.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger (ISSN0722-6691), No.119, p. 36-42 (March 2005)</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Msngr.119...36W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622..451M</bibcode>
			<title>Adaptive Optics Imaging of the AU Microscopii Circumstellar Disk: Evidence for Dynamical Evolution</title>
			<authors>Metchev, Stanimir A.; Eisner, Joshua A.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Wolf, Sebastian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 1, pp. 451-462.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622..451M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622..430H</bibcode>
			<title>The Disk Atmospheres of Three Herbig Ae/Be Stars</title>
			<authors>Harker, David E.; Woodward, Charles E.; Wooden, Diane H.; Temi, Pasquale</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 1, pp. 430-439.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622..430H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622..404K</bibcode>
			<title>8-13 mum Spectroscopy of Young Stellar Objects: Evolution of the Silicate Feature</title>
			<authors>Kessler-Silacci, Jacqueline E.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Blake, Geoffrey A.; Meyer, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 1, pp. 404-429.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622..404K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...621..461D</bibcode>
			<title>The Truncated Disk of CoKu Tau/4</title>
			<authors>D'Alessio, Paola; Hartmann, Lee; Calvet, Nuria; Franco-Hernndez, Ramiro; Forrest, William J.; Sargent, Ben; Furlan, Elise; Uchida, Keven; Green, Joel D.; Watson, Dan M.; Chen, Christine H.; Kemper, F.; Sloan, G. C.; Najita, Joan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 621, Issue 1, pp. 461-472.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...621..461D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...431..773R</bibcode>
			<title>CHARM2: An updated Catalog of High Angular Resolution Measurements</title>
			<authors>Richichi, A.; Percheron, I.; Khristoforova, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.431, p.773-777 (2005)</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...431..773R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...431..175S</bibcode>
			<title>Mid-IR observations of circumstellar disks.  II. Vega-type stars and a post-main sequence object</title>
			<authors>Schtz, O.; Meeus, G.; Sterzik, M. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.431, p.175-182 (2005)</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...431..175S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...431..165S</bibcode>
			<title>Mid-IR observations of circumstellar disks.  I. Pre-main sequence objects</title>
			<authors>Schtz, O.; Meeus, G.; Sterzik, M. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.431, p.165-174 (2005)</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...431..165S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...618L.133L</bibcode>
			<title>Resolved Mid-Infrared Emission around AB Aurigae and V892 Tauri with Adaptive Optics Nulling Interferometric Observations</title>
			<authors>Liu, Wilson M.; Hinz, Philip M.; Hoffmann, William F.; Brusa, Guido; Miller, Doug; Kenworthy, Matthew A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 618, Issue 2, pp. L133-L136.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...618L.133L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...430..137K</bibcode>
			<title>The primordial binary population.  I. A near-infrared adaptive optics search for close visual companions to A star members of Scorpius OB2</title>
			<authors>Kouwenhoven, M. B. N.; Brown, A. G. A.; Zinnecker, H.; Kaper, L.; Portegies Zwart, S. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.430, p.137-154 (2005)</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...430..137K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...429..247D</bibcode>
			<title>New insights in the FUV into the activity of the Herbig Ae star HD 163296</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Bouret, J.-C.; Catala, C.; Lecavelier des Etangs, A.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Roberge, A.; Feldman, P. D.; Martin, C.; Ferlet, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.429, p.247-255 (2005)</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...429..247D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AAS...205.1716L</bibcode>
			<title>Adaptive Optics Nulling Interferometric Observations of AB Aur and V892 Tau: Resolved Disks in the Mid-IR</title>
			<authors>Liu, W. M.; Hinz, P. M.; Hoffmann, W. F.; Brusa, G.; Miller, D.; Kenworthy, M. A.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society Meeting 205, #17.16; &lt;ALTJOURNAL&gt;Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 36, p.1367&lt;/ALTJOURNAL&gt;</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AAS...205.1716L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...427.1009A</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical analysis of 24 dusty (pre-)main-sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Acke, B.; Waelkens, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.427, p.1009-1017 (2004)</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...427.1009A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004PASP..116.1061B</bibcode>
			<title>The Four-Quadrant Phase Mask Coronagraph. IV. First Light at the Very Large Telescope</title>
			<authors>Boccaletti, A.; Riaud, P.; Baudoz, P.; Baudrand, J.; Rouan, D.; Gratadour, D.; Lacombe, F.; Lagrange, A.-M.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 116, Issue 825, pp. 1061-1071.</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004PASP..116.1061B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...427..179H</bibcode>
			<title>PAHs in circumstellar disks around Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Habart, E.; Natta, A.; Krgel, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.427, p.179-192 (2004)</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...427..179H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...426L..53A</bibcode>
			<title>Grain growth and dust settling in a brown dwarf disk. Gemini/T-ReCS observations of CFHT-BD-Tau 4</title>
			<authors>Apai, D.; Pascucci, I.; Sterzik, M. F.; van der Bliek, N.; Bouwman, J.; Dullemond, C. P.; Henning, Th.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.426, p.L53-L57 (2004)</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...426L..53A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...614..221S</bibcode>
			<title>New Perspectives on the X-Ray Emission of HD 104237 and Other Nearby Herbig Ae/Be Stars from XMM-Newton and Chandra</title>
			<authors>Skinner, Stephen L.; Gdel, Manuel; Audard, Marc; Smith, Kester</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 614, Issue 1, pp. 221-234.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...614..221S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...426..151A</bibcode>
			<title>ISO spectroscopy of disks around Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Acke, B.; van den Ancker, M. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.426, p.151-170 (2004)</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...426..151A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004NewA....9..509Z</bibcode>
			<title>A new approach to IRAS observations of Be stars</title>
			<authors>Zhang, P.; Chen, P. S.; He, J. H.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 9, Issue 7, p. 509-524.</journal>
			<date>9/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004NewA....9..509Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ARA&amp;A..42..119V</bibcode>
			<title>ISO Spectroscopy of Gas and Dust: From Molecular Clouds to Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>van Dishoeck, Ewine F.</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy &amp;Astrophysics, vol. 42, Issue 1, pp.119-167</journal>
			<date>9/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ARA%26A..42..119V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...611..928V</bibcode>
			<title>The Profiles of the 3-12 Micron Polycyclic Aromatic Hydrocarbon Features</title>
			<authors>van Diedenhoven, B.; Peeters, E.; Van Kerckhoven, C.; Hony, S.; Hudgins, D. M.; Allamandola, L. J.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 611, Issue 2, pp. 928-939.</journal>
			<date>8/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...611..928V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...423..537L</bibcode>
			<title>Mid-infrared sizes of circumstellar disks around Herbig Ae/Be stars measured with MIDI on the VLTI</title>
			<authors>Leinert, Ch.; van Boekel, R.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Chesneau, O.; Malbet, F.; Khler, R.; Jaffe, W.; Ratzka, Th.; Dutrey, A.; Preibisch, Th.; Graser, U.; Bakker, E.; Chagnon, G.; Cotton, W. D.; Dominik, C.; Dullemond, C. P.; Glazenborg-Kluttig, A. W.; Glindemann, A.; Henning, Th.; Hofmann, K.-H.; de Jong, J.; Lenzen, R.; Ligori, S.; Lopez, B.; Meisner, J.; Morel, S.; Paresce, F.; Pel, J.-W.; Percheron, I.; Perrin, G.; Przygodda, F.; Richichi, A.; Schller, M.; Schuller, P.; Stecklum, B.; van den Ancker, M. E.; von der Lhe, O.; Weigelt, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.423, p.537-548 (2004)</journal>
			<date>8/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...423..537L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...422..621A</bibcode>
			<title>Correlation between grain growth and disk geometry in Herbig Ae/Be systems</title>
			<authors>Acke, B.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Dullemond, C. P.; van Boekel, R.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.422, p.621-626 (2004)</journal>
			<date>8/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...422..621A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...610L..49H</bibcode>
			<title>Crystalline Silicate Feature of the Vega-like Star HD 145263</title>
			<authors>Honda, Mitsuhiko; Kataza, Hirokazu; Okamoto, Yoshiko K.; Miyata, Takashi; Yamashita, Takuya; Sako, Shigeyuki; Fujiyoshi, Takuya; Ito, Meguru; Okada, Yoko; Sakon, Itsuki; Onaka, Takashi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 610, Issue 1, pp. L49-L52.</journal>
			<date>7/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...610L..49H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AJ....128..357S</bibcode>
			<title>Does the 3.3 Micron Polycyclic Aromatic Hydrocarbon Emission Feature Require Ultraviolet Excitation?</title>
			<authors>Smith, Tracy L.; Clayton, Geoffrey C.; Valencic, Lynne</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 128, Issue 1, pp. 357-362.</journal>
			<date>7/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AJ....128..357S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...608..809G</bibcode>
			<title>The Environment of the Optically Brightest Herbig Ae Star, HD 104237</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Woodgate, B.; Torres, Carlos A. O.; Henning, Th.; Apai, D.; Rodmann, J.; Wang, Hongchi; Stecklum, B.; Linz, H.; Williger, G. M.; Brown, A.; Wilkinson, E.; Harper, G. M.; Herczeg, G. J.; Danks, A.; Vieira, G. L.; Malumuth, E.; Collins, N. R.; Hill, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 608, Issue 2, pp. 809-830.</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...608..809G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...606L..69C</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Planetesimal Infall onto the Very Young Herbig Be Star LkHalpha 234</title>
			<authors>Chakraborty, Abhijit; Ge, Jian; Mahadevan, Suvrath</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 606, Issue 1, pp. L69-L72.</journal>
			<date>5/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...606L..69C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...418..577D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for wind and accretion in the Herbig Be star HD 100546 from FUSE observations</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Lecavelier des Etangs, A.; Bouret, J.-C.; Roberge, A.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Martin, C.; Feldman, P. D.; Ferlet, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.418, p.577-591 (2004)</journal>
			<date>5/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...418..577D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004S&amp;T...107d..44S</bibcode>
			<title>Imaging exoplanets.</title>
			<authors>Shiga, D.</authors>
			<journal>Sky Telesc., 107, part no 4, 44-52 (2004)</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004S%26T...107d..44S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJS..151..299H</bibcode>
			<title>Classification of Spectra from the Infrared Space Observatory PHT-S Database</title>
			<authors>Hodge, Tracy M.; Kraemer, Kathleen E.; Price, Stephan D.; Walker, Helen J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 151, Issue 2, pp. 299-312.</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJS..151..299H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...605L..53F</bibcode>
			<title>Spiral Structure in the Circumstellar Disk around AB Aurigae</title>
			<authors>Fukagawa, Misato; Hayashi, Masahiko; Tamura, Motohide; Itoh, Yoichi; Hayashi, Saeko S.; Oasa, Yumiko; Takeuchi, Taku; Morino, Jun-ichi; Murakawa, Koji; Oya, Shin; Yamashita, Takuya; Suto, Hiroshi; Mayama, Satoshi; Naoi, Takahiro; Ishii, Miki; Pyo, Tae-Soo; Nishikawa, Takayuki; Takato, Naruhisa; Usuda, Tomonori; Ando, Hiroyasu; Iye, Masanori; Miyama, Shoken M.; Kaifu, Norio</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 605, Issue 1, pp. L53-L56.</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...605L..53F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...418..177V</bibcode>
			<title>Spatially and spectrally resolved 10 mum emission in Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>van Boekel, R.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Dominik, C.; Dullemond, C. P.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.; de Koter, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.418, p.177-184 (2004)</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...418..177V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...416L...5M</bibcode>
			<title>Far Ultraviolet Spectroscopy of HD 76534</title>
			<authors>Martin, C.; Bouret, J.-C.; Deleuil, M.; Simon, T.; Catala, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.416, p.L5-L8 (2004)</journal>
			<date>3/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...416L...5M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...601.1000E</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling the Continuum Emission from the Circumstellar Environment of Herbig Ae/Be Stars</title>
			<authors>Elia, D.; Strafella, F.; Campeggio, L.; Giannini, T.; Lorenzetti, D.; Nisini, B.; Pezzuto, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 601, Issue 2, pp. 1000-1012.</journal>
			<date>2/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...601.1000E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AJ....127.1176L</bibcode>
			<title>Physical Parameters of Southern B- and Be-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Levenhagen, R. S.; Leister, N. V.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 127, Issue 2, pp. 1176-1180.</journal>
			<date>2/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AJ....127.1176L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...414..955B</bibcode>
			<title>Active phenomena in the circumstellar environmentof the Herbig Ae star HD 31648</title>
			<authors>Beskrovnaya, N. G.; Pogodin, M. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.414, p.955-967 (2004)</journal>
			<date>2/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...414..955B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003MNRAS.346.1151V</bibcode>
			<title>Discs and haloes in pre-main-sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Vinkovic, Dejan; Ivezic, Zeljko; Miroshnichenko, Anatoly S.; Elitzur, Moshe</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 346, Issue 4, pp. 1151-1161.</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003MNRAS.346.1151V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...599.1207F</bibcode>
			<title>The &amp;epsil Chamaeleontis Young Stellar Group and the Characterization of Sparse Stellar Clusters</title>
			<authors>Feigelson, Eric D.; Lawson, Warrick A.; Garmire, Gordon P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 599, Issue 2, pp. 1207-1222.</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...599.1207F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...598L.111L</bibcode>
			<title>A Resolved Circumstellar Disk around the Herbig Ae Star HD 100546 in the Thermal Infrared</title>
			<authors>Liu, Wilson M.; Hinz, Philip M.; Meyer, Michael R.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Hoffmann, William F.; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 598, Issue 2, pp. L111-L114.</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...598L.111L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003AJ....126.2971V</bibcode>
			<title>Investigation of 131 Herbig Ae/Be Candidate Stars</title>
			<authors>Vieira, S. L. A.; Corradi, W. J. B.; Alencar, S. H. P.; Mendes, L. T. S.; Torres, C. A. O.; Quast, G. R.; Guimares, M. M.; da Silva, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 126, Issue 6, pp. 2971-2987.</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003AJ....126.2971V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...596..597W</bibcode>
			<title>Disks around the Young Stars TW Hydrae and HD 100546 Imaged at 3.4 Millimeters with the Australia Telescope Compact Array</title>
			<authors>Wilner, D. J.; Bourke, T. L.; Wright, C. M.; Jrgensen, J. K.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Wong, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 596, Issue 1, pp. 597-602.</journal>
			<date>10/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...596..597W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...410..175B</bibcode>
			<title>Far UV spectroscopy of the circumstellar environment of the Herbig Be stars HD 259431 and HD 250550</title>
			<authors>Bouret, J.-C.; Martin, C.; Deleuil, M.; Simon, T.; Catala, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.410, p.175-188 (2003)</journal>
			<date>10/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...410..175B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003PASP..115.1036G</bibcode>
			<title>Coronagraphic Imaging with the Hubble Space Telescope and the Space Telescope Imaging Spectrograph</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Proffitt, C. R.; Malumuth, E.; Woodgate, B. E.; Gull, T. R.; Bowers, C. W.; Heap, S. R.; Kimble, R. A.; Lindler, D.; Plait, P.; Weinberger, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 115, Issue 811, pp. 1036-1049.</journal>
			<date>9/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003PASP..115.1036G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...407..935L</bibcode>
			<title>FUSE observations of H2 around the Herbig AeBe stars  HD 100546 and HD 163296</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier des Etangs, A.; Deleuil, M.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Roberge, A.; Le Petit, F.; Hbrard, G.; Ferlet, R.; Feldman, P. D.; Dsert, J.-M.; Bouret, J.-C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.407, p.935-939 (2003)</journal>
			<date>9/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...407..935L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJS..147..305V</bibcode>
			<title>An IUE Atlas of Pre-Main-Sequence Stars. III. Co-added Final Archive Spectra from the Long-Wavelength Cameras</title>
			<authors>Valenti, Jeff A.; Fallon, Adam A.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 147, Issue 2, pp. 305-336.</journal>
			<date>8/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJS..147..305V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...407..631B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of averaged stellar effective magnetic fields. I. Chemically peculiar A and B type stars</title>
			<authors>Bychkov, V. D.; Bychkova, L. V.; Madej, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.407, p.631-642 (2003)</journal>
			<date>8/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...407..631B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003AJ....126..385C</bibcode>
			<title>Hubble Space Telescope ACS Coronagraphic Imaging of the Circumstellar Disk around HD 141569A</title>
			<authors>Clampin, M.; Krist, J. E.; Ardila, D. R.; Golimowski, D. A.; Hartig, G. F.; Ford, H. C.; Illingworth, G. D.; Bartko, F.; Bentez, N.; Blakeslee, J. P.; Bouwens, R. J.; Broadhurst, T. J.; Brown, R. A.; Burrows, C. J.; Cheng, E. S.; Cross, N. J. G.; Feldman, P. D.; Franx, M.; Gronwall, C.; Infante, L.; Kimble, R. A.; Lesser, M. P.; Martel, A. R.; Menanteau, F.; Meurer, G. R.; Miley, G. K.; Postman, M.; Rosati, P.; Sirianni, M.; Sparks, W. B.; Tran, H. D.; Tsvetanov, Z. I.; White, R. L.; Zheng, W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 126, Issue 1, pp. 385-392.</journal>
			<date>7/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003AJ....126..385C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...590L..49F</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Imaging of the Circumstellar Disk around Herbig Ae Star HD 150193A</title>
			<authors>Fukagawa, Misato; Tamura, Motohide; Itoh, Yoichi; Hayashi, Saeko S.; Oasa, Yumiko</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 590, Issue 1, pp. L49-L52.</journal>
			<date>6/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...590L..49F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...404..913S</bibcode>
			<title>Formation scenarios for the young stellar associations between galactic longitudes l = 280degr - 360degr</title>
			<authors>Sartori, M. J.; Lpine, J. R. D.; Dias, W. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.404, p.913-926 (2003)</journal>
			<date>6/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...404..913S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...401..577B</bibcode>
			<title>The origin of crystalline silicates in the Herbig Be star HD 100546 and in comet Hale-Bopp</title>
			<authors>Bouwman, J.; de Koter, A.; Dominik, C.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.401, p.577-592 (2003)</journal>
			<date>4/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...401..577B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...398..607D</bibcode>
			<title>Understanding the spectra of isolated Herbig stars in the frame  of a passive disk model</title>
			<authors>Dominik, C.; Dullemond, C. P.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Walch, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.398, p.607-619 (2003)</journal>
			<date>2/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...398..607D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003CoKon.103..109E</bibcode>
			<title>ISO Observations of the Infrared Continuum of the Herbig Ae/Be Stars</title>
			<authors>Elia, D.; Strafella, F.; Campeggio, L.</authors>
			<journal>Communications of the Konkoly Observatory, Hungary Proceedings of the conference: 'The interaction of stars with their environment II.', held at the Etvs Lornd University, Budapest, Hungary, May 15-18, 2003; editors: Cs. Kiss, M. Kun, V. Knyves, p. 109-112</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003CoKon.103..109E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AAS...201.4914D</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the circumstellar environment of the Herbig Be star HD 100546 with FUSE.</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Lecavelier des Etangs, A.; Bouret, J.-C.; Roberge, A.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Feldman, P. D.; Ferlet, R.; Martin, C.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 201st AAS Meeting, #49.14; &lt;ALTJOURNAL&gt;Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 34, p.1186&lt;/ALTJOURNAL&gt;</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AAS...201.4914D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AAS...201.2502R</bibcode>
			<title>Ultraviolet Spectroscopy of Circumstellar Disks</title>
			<authors>Roberge, A.; Feldman, P. D.; Lecavelier des Etangs, A.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Deleuil, M.; Bouret, J.-C.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 201st AAS Meeting, #25.02; &lt;ALTJOURNAL&gt;Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 34, p.1145&lt;/ALTJOURNAL&gt;</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AAS...201.2502R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AAS...201.2019W</bibcode>
			<title>Spectral Imaging of Herbig Ae Stars in Lyman Alpha: Jets, Disk Winds, and Envelopes</title>
			<authors>Woodgate, B.; Grady, C.; Heap, S.; Danks, A.; Vieira, G.; Gull, T.; Brown, A.; Wilkinson, E.; Harper, G.; Herzceg, G.; Linsky, J.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 201st AAS Meeting, #20.19; &lt;ALTJOURNAL&gt;Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 34, p.1136&lt;/ALTJOURNAL&gt;</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AAS...201.2019W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AAS...201.2011H</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining the Relative Mass Fractions of Amorphous and Crystalline Silicates in the Disk Atmospheres of Three Herbig Ae Stars Using Radiative Transfer Models</title>
			<authors>Harker, D. E.; Wooden, D. H.; Woodward, C. E.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 201st AAS Meeting, #20.11; &lt;ALTJOURNAL&gt;Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 34, p.1135&lt;/ALTJOURNAL&gt;</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AAS...201.2011H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...579L..91C</bibcode>
			<title>The Infrared Emission Features in the Spectrum of the Wolf-Rayet star WR 48a</title>
			<authors>Chiar, J. E.; Peeters, E.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 579, Issue 2, pp. L91-L94.</journal>
			<date>11/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...579L..91C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...395..637L</bibcode>
			<title>The complete far infrared spectroscopic survey of Herbig AeBe stars obtained by ISO-LWS</title>
			<authors>Lorenzetti, D.; Giannini, T.; Nisini, B.; Benedettini, M.; Elia, D.; Campeggio, L.; Strafella, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.395, p.637-645 (2002)</journal>
			<date>11/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...395..637L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...392.1039M</bibcode>
			<title>The absence of the 10 mu m silicate feature in the isolated Herbig Ae star HD 100453</title>
			<authors>Meeus, G.; Bouwman, J.; Dominik, C.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; de Koter, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.392, p.1039-1046 (2002)</journal>
			<date>9/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...392.1039M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...390.1089P</bibcode>
			<title>The rich 6 to 9 vec mu m spectrum of interstellar PAHs</title>
			<authors>Peeters, E.; Hony, S.; Van Kerckhoven, C.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.; Allamandola, L. J.; Hudgins, D. M.; Bauschlicher, C. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.390, p.1089-1113 (2002)</journal>
			<date>8/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...390.1089P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...390.1033V</bibcode>
			<title>The ISO-SWS post-helium atlas of near-infrared stellar spectra</title>
			<authors>Vandenbussche, B.; Beintema, D.; de Graauw, T.; Decin, L.; Feuchtgruber, H.; Heras, A.; Kester, D.; Lahuis, F.; Lenorzer, A.; Lorente, R.; Salama, A.; Waelkens, C.; Waters, L.; Wieprecht, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.390, p.1033-1048 (2002)</journal>
			<date>8/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...390.1033V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.334...94B</bibcode>
			<title>A mineralogy of extrasolar silicate dust from 10-mum spectra</title>
			<authors>Bowey, J. E.; Adamson, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 334, Issue 1, pp. 94-106.</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.334...94B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJS..140..389K</bibcode>
			<title>Classification of 2.4-45.2 Micron Spectra from the Infrared Space Observatory Short Wavelength Spectrometer</title>
			<authors>Kraemer, Kathleen E.; Sloan, G. C.; Price, Stephan D.; Walker, Helen J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 140, Issue 2, pp. 389-406.</journal>
			<date>6/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJS..140..389K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...386.1103S</bibcode>
			<title>The low temperature crystallization effect reevaluated</title>
			<authors>Schutte, W. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.386, p.1103-1105 (2002)</journal>
			<date>5/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...386.1103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.331L...1B</bibcode>
			<title>The 69-mum forsterite band as a dust temperature indicator</title>
			<authors>Bowey, J. E.; Barlow, M. J.; Molster, F. J.; Hofmeister, A. M.; Lee, C.; Tucker, C.; Lim, T.; Ade, P. A. R.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 331, Issue 1, pp. L1-L6.</journal>
			<date>3/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.331L...1B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...384..568V</bibcode>
			<title>Nanodiamonds around HD 97048 and Elias 1</title>
			<authors>Van Kerckhoven, C.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.; Waelkens, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.384, p.568-584 (2002)</journal>
			<date>3/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...384..568V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...382..222M</bibcode>
			<title>Crystalline silicate dust around evolved stars. II. The crystalline silicate complexes</title>
			<authors>Molster, F. J.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.382, p.222-240 (2002)</journal>
			<date>1/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...382..222M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...382...92S</bibcode>
			<title>The mass ratio distribution of B-type visual binaries in the Sco OB2 association</title>
			<authors>Shatsky, N.; Tokovinin, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.382, p.92-103 (2002)</journal>
			<date>1/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...382...92S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...381..446M</bibcode>
			<title>Astrometric radial velocities. III. Hipparcos measurements of nearby star clusters and associations</title>
			<authors>Madsen, Sren; Dravins, Dainis; Lindegren, Lennart</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.381, p.446-463 (2002)</journal>
			<date>1/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...381..446M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001AJ....122.3396G</bibcode>
			<title>The Disk and Environment of the Herbig Be Star HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Polomski, E. F.; Henning, Th.; Stecklum, B.; Woodgate, B. E.; Telesco, C. M.; Pia, R. K.; Gull, T. R.; Boggess, A.; Bowers, C. W.; Bruhweiler, F. C.; Clampin, M.; Danks, A. C.; Green, R. F.; Heap, S. R.; Hutchings, J. B.; Jenkins, E. B.; Joseph, C.; Kaiser, M. E.; Kimble, R. A.; Kraemer, S.; Lindler, D.; Linsky, J. L.; Maran, S. P.; Moos, H. W.; Plait, P.; Roesler, F.; Timothy, J. G.; Weistrop, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 122, Issue 6, pp. 3396-3406.</journal>
			<date>12/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001AJ....122.3396G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...380..609D</bibcode>
			<title>A photometric catalogue of southern emission-line stars</title>
			<authors>de Winter, D.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Maira, A.; Th, P. S.; Djie, H. R. E. Tjin A.; Redondo, I.; Eiroa, C.; Molster, F. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.380, p.609-614 (2001)</journal>
			<date>12/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...380..609D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...378..228F</bibcode>
			<title>Steps toward interstellar silicate mineralogy. VI. Dependence of crystalline olivine IR spectra on iron content and particle shape</title>
			<authors>Fabian, D.; Henning, T.; Jger, C.; Mutschke, H.; Dorschner, J.; Wehrhan, O.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.378, p.228-238 (2001)</journal>
			<date>10/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...378..228F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...377..994T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of the unusual 3.5 mu m feature in the Herbig Be star MWC 297</title>
			<authors>Terada, H.; Imanishi, M.; Goto, M.; Maihara, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.377, p.994-998 (2001)</journal>
			<date>10/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...377..994T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...375..950B</bibcode>
			<title>Processing of silicate dust grains in Herbig Ae/Be systems</title>
			<authors>Bouwman, J.; Meeus, G.; de Koter, A.; Hony, S.; Dominik, C.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.375, p.950-962 (2001)</journal>
			<date>9/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...375..950B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...557..844H</bibcode>
			<title>The Infrared Continuum Spectrum of VY Canis Majoris</title>
			<authors>Harwit, Martin; Malfait, Koen; Decin, Leen; Waelkens, Christoffel; Feuchtgruber, Helmut; Melnick, Gary J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 557, Issue 2, pp. 844-853.</journal>
			<date>8/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...557..844H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...366..945B</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Evaporating Bodies around Herbig stars. A theoretical study</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Karmann, C.; Lagrange, A.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.366, p.945-964 (2001)</journal>
			<date>2/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...366..945B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...365..476M</bibcode>
			<title>ISO spectroscopy of circumstellar dust in 14 Herbig Ae/Be systems: Towards an understanding of dust processing</title>
			<authors>Meeus, G.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Bouwman, J.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Waelkens, C.; Malfait, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.365, p.476-490 (2001)</journal>
			<date>1/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...365..476M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...365...78A</bibcode>
			<title>HST/NICMOS2 coronagraphic observations of the circumstellar environment of three old PMS stars: HD 100546, SAO 206462 and MWC 480</title>
			<authors>Augereau, J. C.; Lagrange, A. M.; Mouillet, D.; Mnard, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.365, p.78-89 (2001)</journal>
			<date>1/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...365...78A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ASPC..244..104M</bibcode>
			<title>The Dispersal of Young Stars and the Greater Sco-Cen Association</title>
			<authors>Mamajek, E. E.; Feigelson, E. D.</authors>
			<journal>Young Stars Near Earth: Progress and Prospects, ASP Conference Series Vol. 244.  Edited by Ray Jayawardhana and Thomas Greene. San Francisco: Astronomical Society of the Pacific, ISBN: 1-58381-082-X, 2001., p.104-115</journal>
			<date>0/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ASPC..244..104M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000AAS...197.4702G</bibcode>
			<title>The Disk and Environment of HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Polomski, E.; Henning, Th.; Stecklum, B.; Woodgate, B.; Telesco, C.; Pina, R.; Plait, P.; Gull, T.; Boggess, A.; Bowers, C.; Bruhweiler, F. C.; Clampin, M.; Danks, A.; Green, R. F.; Heap, S. R.; Hutchings, J. B.; Jenkins, E.; Kaiser, M.; Kimble, R.; Kraemer, S.; Lindler, D.; Linsky, J. L.; Maran, S. P.; Moos, H. W.; Roesler, F.; Timothy, J. G.; Weistrop, D.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 197th AAS Meeting, #47.02; &lt;ALTJOURNAL&gt;Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 32, p.1481&lt;/ALTJOURNAL&gt;</journal>
			<date>12/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000AAS...197.4702G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000AJ....120.2609S</bibcode>
			<title>Silicate Emission in the TW Hydrae Association</title>
			<authors>Sitko, Michael L.; Lynch, David K.; Russell, Ray W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 120, Issue 5, pp. 2609-2614.</journal>
			<date>11/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000AJ....120.2609S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...363.1115K</bibcode>
			<title>Absorption spectra of Mg-rich Mg-Fe and Ca pyroxenes in the mid- and far-infrared regions</title>
			<authors>Koike, C.; Tsuchiyama, A.; Shibai, H.; Suto, H.; Tanab, T.; Chihara, H.; Sogawa, H.; Mouri, H.; Okada, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.363, p.1115-1122 (2000)</journal>
			<date>11/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...363.1115K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...361L...9P</bibcode>
			<title>ADONIS observations of the HD 100546 circumstellar dust disk</title>
			<authors>Pantin, E.; Waelkens, C.; Lagage, P. O.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.361, p.L9-L12 (2000)</journal>
			<date>9/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...361L...9P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000RPPh...63.1209P</bibcode>
			<title>Extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Perryman, M. A. C.</authors>
			<journal>Reports on Progress in Physics, Volume 63, Issue 8, pp. 1209-1272 (2000).</journal>
			<date>8/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000RPPh...63.1209P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...360..213B</bibcode>
			<title>The composition of the circumstellar dust around the Herbig Ae stars AB Aur and HD 163296</title>
			<authors>Bouwman, J.; de Koter, A.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Vol. 360, p.213-226</journal>
			<date>8/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...360..213B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJS..129..399V</bibcode>
			<title>An IUE Atlas of Pre-Main-Sequence Stars. I. Co-added Final Archive Spectra from the SWP Camera</title>
			<authors>Valenti, Jeff A.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 129, Issue 1, pp. 399-420.</journal>
			<date>7/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJS..129..399V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;AS..144..285Y</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of correlations between polarimetric and photometric characteristics of young stars. A new approach to the problem after eleven years' study</title>
			<authors>Yudin, R. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.144, p.285-306</journal>
			<date>6/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26AS..144..285Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...357..533D</bibcode>
			<title>The Vega phenomenon around G dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Decin, G.; Dominik, C.; Malfait, K.; Mayor, M.; Waelkens, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.357, p.533-542 (2000)</journal>
			<date>5/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...357..533D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...357..325V</bibcode>
			<title>ISO spectroscopy of circumstellar dust in the Herbig Ae systems AB Aur and HD 163296</title>
			<authors>van den Ancker, M. E.; Bouwman, J.; Wesselius, P. R.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Dougherty, S. M.; van Dishoeck, E. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.357, p.325-329 (2000)</journal>
			<date>5/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...357..325V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000SSRv...92...69A</bibcode>
			<title>Beta Pictoris and Other Solar Systems</title>
			<authors>Artymowicz, Pawel</authors>
			<journal>Space Science Reviews, v. 92, Issue 1/2, p. 69-86 (2000).</journal>
			<date>4/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000SSRv...92...69A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000MNRAS.313...43H</bibcode>
			<title>OB association members in the ACT and TRC catalogues</title>
			<authors>Hoogerwerf, Ronnie</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 313, Issue 1, pp. 43-65.</journal>
			<date>3/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000MNRAS.313...43H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000Icar..143..126W</bibcode>
			<title>Mg-Rich Silicate Crystals in Comet Hale-Bopp: ISM Relics or Solar Nebula Condensates?</title>
			<authors>Wooden, Diane H.; Butner, Harold M.; Harker, David E.; Woodward, Charles E.</authors>
			<journal>Icarus, Volume 143, pp. 126-137 (2000).</journal>
			<date>1/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000Icar..143..126W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000Ap&amp;SS.271..259C</bibcode>
			<title>Herbig Ae/Be stars with the IRAS low-resolution spectra.</title>
			<authors>Chen, P. S.; Wang, X. H.; He, J. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, Vol. 271, No. 3, p. 259 - 276</journal>
			<date>0/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000Ap%26SS.271..259C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999Natur.401..563M</bibcode>
			<title>Low-temperature crystallization of silicate dust in circumstellar disks</title>
			<authors>Molster, F. J.; Yamamura, I.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Tielens, A. G. G. M.; de Graauw, Th.; de Jong, T.; de Koter, A.; Malfait, K.; van den Ancker, M. E.; van Winckel, H.; Voors, R. H. M.; Waelkens, C.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 401, Issue 6753, pp. 563-565 (1999).</journal>
			<date>10/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999Natur.401..563M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999ApJ...521L.133G</bibcode>
			<title>Diamond Infrared Emission Bands in Circumstellar Media</title>
			<authors>Guillois, O.; Ledoux, G.; Reynaud, C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 521, Issue 2, pp. L133-L36.</journal>
			<date>8/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999ApJ...521L.133G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999AcApS..19..292S</bibcode>
			<title>The evolution status of HD 104237, &amp;epsil Cha and HD 100546.</title>
			<authors>Shen, Chuanjian; Hu, Jingyao</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astrophys. Sin., Vol. 19, No. 3, p. 292 - 296</journal>
			<date>7/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999AcApS..19..292S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...347..590C</bibcode>
			<title>Polarimetric variability of the Herbig Be star HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Clarke, D.; Smith, R. A.; Yudin, R. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.347, p.590-593 (1999)</journal>
			<date>7/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...347..590C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999S&amp;T....97f..40P</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos: The Stars</title>
			<authors>Perryman, Michael</authors>
			<journal>Sky and Telescope, volume 97, number 6, page 40.</journal>
			<date>6/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999S%26T....97f..40P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...346..604L</bibcode>
			<title>ISO-LWS observations of Herbig Ae/Be stars. I. Fine structure lines</title>
			<authors>Lorenzetti, D.; Tommasi, E.; Giannini, T.; Nisini, B.; Benedettini, M.; Pezzuto, S.; Strafella, F.; Barlow, M.; Clegg, P. E.; Cohen, M.; di Giorgio, A. M.; Liseau, R.; Molinari, S.; Palla, F.; Saraceno, P.; Smith, H. A.; Spinoglio, L.; White, G. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.346, p.604-616 (1999)</journal>
			<date>6/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...346..604L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;AS..136..429C</bibcode>
			<title>A search for spectroscopic binaries among Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Corporon, P.; Lagrange, A.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.136, p.429-444</journal>
			<date>5/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26AS..136..429C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...345..559V</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic study of the Herbig Be star HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Vieira, S. L. A.; Pogodin, M. A.; Franco, G. A. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.345, p.559-575 (1999)</journal>
			<date>5/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...345..559V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...345..181M</bibcode>
			<title>The ISO spectrum of the young star HD 142527</title>
			<authors>Malfait, K.; Waelkens, C.; Bouwman, J.; de Koter, A.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.345, p.181-186 (1999)</journal>
			<date>5/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...345..181M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...344..614H</bibcode>
			<title>Emission line star 3G71: a Herbig Ae/Be star candidate</title>
			<authors>Hang, H.-R.; Liu, Q.-Z.; Xia, J.-P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.344, p.614-616 (1999)</journal>
			<date>4/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...344..614H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...343..137D</bibcode>
			<title>Episodic accretion around the Herbig AE star BF Orionis. Evidence for the presence of extra-solar comets</title>
			<authors>de Winter, D.; Grady, C. A.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Prez, M. R.; Eiroa, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.343, p.137-150 (1999)</journal>
			<date>3/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...343..137D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999ApJ...511..925G</bibcode>
			<title>Transient Infall Events in the Disk of AB Aurigae: The beta Pictoris Phenomenon at 2-4 Megayears</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Prez, Mario R.; Bjorkman, K. S.; Massa, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 511, Issue 2, pp. 925-931.</journal>
			<date>2/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999ApJ...511..925G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999MNRAS.302..612M</bibcode>
			<title>Six intermediate-mass stars with far-infrared excess: a search for evolutionary connections</title>
			<authors>Miroshnichenko, Anatoly S.; Mulliss, Christopher L.; Bjorkman, Karen S.; Morrison, Nancy D.; Kuratov, Kenesken S.; Wisniewski, John P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 302, Issue 3, pp. 612-624.</journal>
			<date>1/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999MNRAS.302..612M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999IBVS.4659....1K</bibcode>
			<title>The 74th Special Name-list of Variable Stars</title>
			<authors>Kazarovets, E. V.; Samus, N. N.; Durlevich, O. V.; Frolov, M. S.; Antipin, S. V.; Kireeva, N. N.; Pastukhova, E. N.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4659, 1.</journal>
			<date>1/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999IBVS.4659....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999ApJ...510..408S</bibcode>
			<title>Cometary Dust in the Debris Disks of HD 31648 and HD 163296: Two ``Baby'' beta Pictoris Stars</title>
			<authors>Sitko, Michael L.; Grady, Carol A.; Lynch, David K.; Russell, Ray W.; Hanner, Martha S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 510, Issue 1, pp. 408-412.</journal>
			<date>1/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999ApJ...510..408S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999AJ....117..354D</bibcode>
			<title>A HIPPARCOS Census of the Nearby OB Associations</title>
			<authors>de Zeeuw, P. T.; Hoogerwerf, R.; de Bruijne, J. H. J.; Brown, A. G. A.; Blaauw, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 117, Issue 1, pp. 354-399.</journal>
			<date>1/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999AJ....117..354D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999Ap&amp;SS.268..229W</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared Evidence for Panspermia: An Update</title>
			<authors>Wickramasinghe, N. C.; Hoyle, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, v. 268, Issue 1/3, p. 229-246 (1999).</journal>
			<date>0/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999Ap%26SS.268..229W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...338..674W</bibcode>
			<title>Beta Pic-like circumstellar disk gas surrounding HR 10 and HD 85905</title>
			<authors>Welsh, B. Y.; Craig, N.; Crawford, I. A.; Price, R. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.338, p.674-682 (1998)</journal>
			<date>10/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...338..674W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...338..364L</bibcode>
			<title>The dust properties of a short period comet: comet P/Borrelly</title>
			<authors>Li, Aigen; Greenberg, J. Mayo</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.338, p.364-370 (1998)</journal>
			<date>10/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...338..364L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998Ap&amp;SS.259..385W</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared Evidence for Panspermia: An Update</title>
			<authors>Wickramasinghe, N. C.; Hoyle, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, v. 259, Issue 4, p. 385-401 (1998).</journal>
			<date>9/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998Ap%26SS.259..385W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;AS..131..401Y</bibcode>
			<title>Polarimetry of southern peculiar early-type stars</title>
			<authors>Yudin, R. V.; Evans, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.131, p.401-429</journal>
			<date>9/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26AS..131..401Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...336..565H</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared imaging and millimetre continuum mapping of Herbig Ae/Be and FU Orionis stars</title>
			<authors>Henning, Th.; Burkert, A.; Launhardt, R.; Leinert, Ch.; Stecklum, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.336, p.565-586 (1998)</journal>
			<date>8/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...336..565H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998AJ....115.2101F</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared Photometry of beta Pictoris Type Systems</title>
			<authors>Fajardo-Acosta, S. B.; Telesco, C. M.; Knacke, R. F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 115, Issue 5, pp. 2101-2121.</journal>
			<date>5/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998AJ....115.2101F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...332L..25M</bibcode>
			<title>The spectrum of the young star HD 100546 observed with the Infrared Space Observatory</title>
			<authors>Malfait, K.; Waelkens, C.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Vandenbussche, B.; Huygen, E.; de Graauw, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.332, p.L25-L28 (1998)</journal>
			<date>4/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...332L..25M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...331..211M</bibcode>
			<title>An ultraviolet, optical and infrared study of Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Malfait, K.; Bogaert, E.; Waelkens, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.331, p.211-223 (1998)</journal>
			<date>3/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...331..211M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...330..145V</bibcode>
			<title>HIPPARCOS photometry of Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>van den Ancker, M. E.; de Winter, D.; Tjin A Djie, H. R. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.330, p.145-154 (1998)</journal>
			<date>2/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...330..145V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998BSAO...45..105G</bibcode>
			<title>On magnetic fields of Herbig Ae/Be stars.</title>
			<authors>Glagolevskij, Yu. V.; Chuntonov, G. A.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Special Astrophysical Observatory, Vol. 45, p. 105 - 109</journal>
			<date>0/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998BSAO...45..105G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998ARA&amp;A..36..233W</bibcode>
			<title>Herbig Ae/Be Stars</title>
			<authors>Waters, L. B. F. M.; Waelkens, C.</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 36, 1998, pp. 233-266.</journal>
			<date>0/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998ARA%26A..36..233W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998Ap&amp;SS.255..427H</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared Observations of the Transition from Chaotic to Crystalline Silicates via Thermal Annealing in the Laboratory</title>
			<authors>Hallenbeck, S.; Nuth, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, v. 255, Issue 1/2, p. 427-433 (1997).</journal>
			<date>0/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998Ap%26SS.255..427H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998Ap&amp;SS.255...43M</bibcode>
			<title>The ISO-Spectrum of the Young Star HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Malfait, K.; Waelkens, C.; Vandenbussche, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, v. 255, Issue 1/2, p. 43-44 (1997).</journal>
			<date>0/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998Ap%26SS.255...43M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998Ap&amp;SS.255...35G</bibcode>
			<title>The Intermittently Embedded Herbig Ae/Be Stars ISO and Ground-Based IR Observations</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Prez, M. R.; Bjorkman, K. S.; Sitko, M. L.; Th, P. S.; de Winter, D.; Grinin, V. P.; Russell, R. W.; Lynch, D. K.; Hanner, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, v. 255, Issue 1/2, p. 35-41 (1997).</journal>
			<date>0/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998Ap%26SS.255...35G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998Ap&amp;SS.255...25W</bibcode>
			<title>ISO Observations of Isolated Herbig AE/BE Stars</title>
			<authors>Waelkens, C.; Malfait, K.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, v. 255, Issue 1/2, p. 25-33 (1997).</journal>
			<date>0/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998Ap%26SS.255...25W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...491..885N</bibcode>
			<title>The Evolutionary Status of UX Orionis-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Natta, A.; Grinin, V. P.; Mannings, V.; Ungerechts, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.491, p.885</journal>
			<date>12/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...491..885N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;AS..126..479G</bibcode>
			<title>Near infrared photometry of IRAS sources with colours like planetary nebulae. III</title>
			<authors>Garcia-Lario, P.; Manchado, A.; Pych, W.; Pottasch, S. R.</authors>
			<journal>A &amp; A Supplement series, Vol. 126, December II 1997, 479-502.</journal>
			<date>12/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26AS..126..479G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997SSRv...82..407P</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Overview of Young Intermediate-Mass Objects: Herbig Ae/Be Stars</title>
			<authors>Perez, Mario R.; Grady, Carol A.</authors>
			<journal>Space Science Reviews, v. 82, Issue 3/4, p. 407-450.</journal>
			<date>11/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997SSRv...82..407P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997MNRAS.291..658D</bibcode>
			<title>Spectropolarimetric observations of active stars</title>
			<authors>Donati, J.-F.; Semel, M.; Carter, B. D.; Rees, D. E.; Collier Cameron, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, vol. 291, p. 658</journal>
			<date>11/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997MNRAS.291..658D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJS..112..557K</bibcode>
			<title>Classification and Identification of IRAS Sources with Low-Resolution Spectra</title>
			<authors>Kwok, Sun; Volk, Kevin; Bidelman, William P.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement, v.112, p.557</journal>
			<date>10/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJS..112..557K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997EM&amp;P...79..265W</bibcode>
			<title>Comet Hale-Bopp, Circumstellar Dust, and the Interstellar Medium</title>
			<authors>Waelkens, C.; Malfait, K.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Earth, Moon, and Planets, v. 79, Issue 1/3, p. 265-274 (1997).</journal>
			<date>9/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997EM%26P...79..265W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...485..290P</bibcode>
			<title>On the Circumstellar Matter Distribution around Herbig Ae/Be Stars</title>
			<authors>Pezzuto, Stefano; Strafella, Francesco; Lorenzetti, Dario</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.485, p.290</journal>
			<date>8/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...485..290P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;A...324L..33V</bibcode>
			<title>HIPPARCOS data on Herbig Ae/Be stars: an evolutionary scenario.</title>
			<authors>van den Ancker, M. E.; The, P. S.; Tjin A Djie, H. R. E.; Catala, C.; de Winter, D.; Blondel, P. F. C.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.324, p.L33-L36</journal>
			<date>8/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26A...324L..33V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...483..449G</bibcode>
			<title>The Star-grazing Extrasolar Comets in the HD 100546 System</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Sitko, M. L.; Bjorkman, Karen S.; Perez, Mario R.; Lynch, D. K.; Russell, R. W.; Hanner, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.483, p.449</journal>
			<date>7/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...483..449G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997Sci...275.1904C</bibcode>
			<title>The spectrum of Comet Hale-Bopp (C/1995 01) observed with the Infrared Space Observatory at 2.9 AU from the Sun</title>
			<authors>Crovisier, J.; Leech, K.; Bockelee-Morvan, D.; Brooke, T. Y.; Hanner, M. S.; Altieri, B.; Keller, H. U.; Lellouch, E.</authors>
			<journal>Science, vol. 275, p. 1904-1907 (1997).</journal>
			<date>3/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997Sci...275.1904C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;A...317..185P</bibcode>
			<title>Circumstellar peculiarities in the unusual Be star HD 50138.</title>
			<authors>Pogodin, M. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.317, p.185-192</journal>
			<date>1/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26A...317..185P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996A&amp;AS..120..157G</bibcode>
			<title>The beta Pictoris phenomenon among Herbig Ae/Be stars. UV and optical high dispersion spectra.</title>
			<authors>Grady, C. A.; Perez, M. R.; Talavera, A.; Bjorkman, K. S.; de Winter, D.; The, P.-S.; Molster, F. J.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Sitko, M. L.; Morrison, N. D.; Beaver, M. L.; McCollum, B.; Castelaz, M. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.120, p.157-177</journal>
			<date>11/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996A%26AS..120..157G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996A&amp;A...315L.245W</bibcode>
			<title>SWS observations of young main-sequence stars with dusty circumstellar disks.</title>
			<authors>Waelkens, C.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; de Graauw, M. S.; Huygen, E.; Malfait, K.; Plets, H.; Vandenbussche, B.; Beintema, D. A.; Boxhoorn, D. R.; Habing, H. J.; Heras, A. M.; Kester, D. J. M.; Lahuis, F.; Morris, P. W.; Roelfsema, P. R.; Salama, A.; Siebenmorgen, R.; Trams, N. R.; van der Bliek, N. R.; Valentijn, E. A.; Wesselius, P. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.315, p.L245-L248</journal>
			<date>11/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996A%26A...315L.245W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996ARep...40..509M</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared Excesses in A-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Miroshnichenko, A. S.; Bergner, Yu. K.; Kuratov, K. S.; Mukanov, D. B.; Sheikina, T. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Reports, v.40, p. 509-519</journal>
			<date>4/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996ARep...40..509M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;A...301..155B</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation, winds and active phenomena in Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Boehm, T.; Catala, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.301, p.155</journal>
			<date>9/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26A...301..155B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995Ap&amp;SS.224..539P</bibcode>
			<title>Structural Peculiarities of Circumstellar Envelopes of the Young A0e Herbig Stars</title>
			<authors>Pogodin, Mikhail</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, Volume 224, Issue 1-2, pp. 539-540</journal>
			<date>2/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995Ap%26SS.224..539P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994A&amp;A...291..546H</bibcode>
			<title>Cold dust around southern Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Henning, Th.; Launhardt, R.; Steinacker, J.; Thamm, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 291, no. 2, p. 546-556</journal>
			<date>11/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994A%26A...291..546H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994A&amp;AS..104..315T</bibcode>
			<title>A new catalogue of members and candidate members of the Herbig Ae/Be (HAEBE) stellar group</title>
			<authors>The, P. S.; de Winter, D.; Perez, M. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Suppl. 104, 315-339 (1994)</journal>
			<date>4/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994A%26AS..104..315T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;AS..100..413H</bibcode>
			<title>A systematic study of IRAS selected proto-planetary nebula candidates. I - Selection of the sample and observations of the southern objects</title>
			<authors>Hu, J. Y.; Slijkhuis, S.; de Jong, T.; Jiang, B. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 100, no. 2, p. 413-430.</journal>
			<date>8/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26AS..100..413H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;A...275..510S</bibcode>
			<title>Search for Hydroxyl in Southern Cold IRAS Sources</title>
			<authors>Silva, A. M.; Azcarate, I. N.; Poppel, W. G. L.; Likkel, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Vol.275, NO.2/AUG(II), P. 510, 1993</journal>
			<date>8/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26A...275..510S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;AS...96..625O</bibcode>
			<title>SAO stars with infrared excess in the IRAS Point Source Catalog</title>
			<authors>Oudmaijer, Rene D.; van der Veen, W. E. C. J.; Waters, L. B. F. M.; Trams, N. R.; Waelkens, C.; Engelsman, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 96, no. 3, p. 625-643.</journal>
			<date>12/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26AS...96..625O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJS...82..117S</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous catalog of new UBV and H-beta photometry of B- and A-type stars in and around the Scorpius-Centaurus OB association</title>
			<authors>Slawson, Robert W.; Hill, Robert J.; Landstreet, John D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 82, no. 1, Sept. 1992, p. 117-144. Research supported by NSERC.</journal>
			<date>9/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJS...82..117S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;AS...93..151F</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared photometry of a sample of IRAS point sources</title>
			<authors>Fouque, P.; Le Bertre, T.; Epchtein, N.; Guglielmo, F.; Kerschbaum, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 93, April 1992, p. 151-171. Research supported by BMFWF.</journal>
			<date>4/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26AS...93..151F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;AS...93..121N</bibcode>
			<title>A survey of circumstellar CO emission from a sample of IRAS point sources</title>
			<authors>Nyman, L.-A.; Booth, R. S.; Carlstrom, U.; Habing, H. J.; Heske, A.; Sahai, R.; Stark, R.; van der Veen, W. E. J. C.; Winnberg, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 93, April 1992, p. 121-150.</journal>
			<date>4/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26AS...93..121N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991A&amp;AS...90..327T</bibcode>
			<title>1612 MHz OH survey of IRAS point sources. I - Observations made at Dwingeloo, Effelsberg and Parkes</title>
			<authors>te Lintel Hekkert, P.; Caswell, J. L.; Habing, H. J.; Haynes, R. F.; Haynes, R. F.; Norris, R. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 90, no. 2, Oct. 1991, p. 327-353. Research supported by CSIRO, NWO, and Leidse Kerhoven-Bosscha Fonds.</journal>
			<date>10/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991A%26AS...90..327T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991AcApS..11..172D</bibcode>
			<title>Early-type emission-line stars with large infrared excesses</title>
			<authors>Dong, Yi-Sun; Hu, Jing-Yao</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 15, Sept. 1991, p. 275-283. Translation. &lt;ALTJOURNAL&gt;Acta Astrophysica Sinica, vol. 11, no. 2, 1991, p. 172-180&lt;/ALTJOURNAL&gt;</journal>
			<date>9/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991AcApS..11..172D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990AcApS..10..154H</bibcode>
			<title>Be stars with peculiar infrared excess and their classification.</title>
			<authors>Hu, Jing-Yao; Xu, Zhou</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astrophys. Sin., Vol. 10, No. 2, p. 154 - 162</journal>
			<date>9/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990AcApS..10..154H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990A&amp;A...227L..29L</bibcode>
			<title>CO observations of very cold southern circumstellar shells and pre-planetary nebulae</title>
			<authors>Loup, C.; Forveille, T.; Omont, A.; Nyman, L. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 227, no. 2, Jan. 1990, p. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>1/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990A%26A...227L..29L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989A&amp;A...208..213H</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric and spectroscopic study of three candidate Herbig Ae/Be stars - HD 37411, HD 100546, and HD 104237</title>
			<authors>Hu, J. Y.; The, P. S.; de Winter, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 208, no. 1-2, Jan. 1989, p. 213-218.</journal>
			<date>1/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989A%26A...208..213H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986A&amp;AS...65..607O</bibcode>
			<title>IRAS catalogues and atlases - Atlas of low-resolution spectra</title>
			<authors>Olnon, F. M.; Raimond, E.; Neugebauer, G.; van Duinen, R. J.; Habing, H. J.; Aumann, H. H.; Beintema, D. A.; Boggess, N.; Borgman, J.; Clegg, P. E.; Gillett, F. C.; Hauser, M. G.; Houck, J. R.; Jennings, R. E.; de Jong, T.; Low, F. J.; Marsden, P. L.; Pottasch, S. R.; Soifer, B. T.; Walker, R. G.; Emerson, J. P.; Rowan-Robinson, M.; Wesselius, P. R.; Baud, B.; Beichman, C. A.; Gautier, T. N.; Harris, S.; Miley, G. K.; Young, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 65, no. 4, Sept. 1986, p. 607-1065. Research supported by the Netherlands Foundation for Space Research.</journal>
			<date>9/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986A%26AS...65..607O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986PASP...98..423E</bibcode>
			<title>Hyades and Sirius supercluster members brighter than magnitude (V) 7.1. II - Right ascension six to twelve hours</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 98, April 1986, p. 423-441.</journal>
			<date>4/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986PASP...98..423E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982IAUS...98..261J</bibcode>
			<title>A Catalogue of Be-Stars</title>
			<authors>Jaschek, M.; Egret, D.</authors>
			<journal>Be Stars, Proceedings of IAU Symposium No. 98, held 6-10 April 1981 in Munich, Germany.  Edited by M. Jaschek and H.-G. Groth.  Dordrecht: D. Reidel Publishing Co., p.261, 1982</journal>
			<date>4/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982IAUS...98..261J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1976ApJS...30..491H</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of southern emission-line stars</title>
			<authors>Henize, K. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, vol. 30, Apr. 1976, p. 491-550. Research supported by the University of Michigan;</journal>
			<date>4/1976</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1976ApJS...30..491H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
