<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1656S</bibcode>
			<title>Constant-Velocity Stars at the North Galactic Pole Suitable for Use as Secondary Velocity Standards</title>
			<authors>Stefanik, Robert P.; Latham, David W.; Davis, Robert J.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 850, pp. 1656-1665.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1656S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991AJ....101..625L</bibcode>
			<title>A search for wide binaries at the north galactic pole using precise radial velocities</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Davis, Robert J.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Abt, Helmut A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 101, Feb. 1991, p. 625-636. Research supported by U.S. - Israel Binational Science Foundation.</journal>
			<date>2/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991AJ....101..625L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988MNRAS.230..273A</bibcode>
			<title>Kinematics and properties of F stars near the North Galactic Pole. II - The isothermal disc</title>
			<authors>Adamson, A. J.; Hilditch, R. W.; Hill, G.; Fisher, W.; Sinclair, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 230, Jan. 15, 1988, p. 273-320.</journal>
			<date>1/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988MNRAS.230..273A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982PDAO...16..111H</bibcode>
			<title>Further Studies of A-Stars and F-Stars in the Region of the North Galactic Pole - Part Four - a Catalogue of Uvbyr Photometry and Derived Quantities</title>
			<authors>Hill, G.; Barnes, J. V.; Hilditch, R. W.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Dominion Astrophysical Observatory, Vol. 16, NO. 10, P. 111, 1982</journal>
			<date>0/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982PDAO...16..111H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982PDAO...16...87H</bibcode>
			<title>Further Studies of A-Stars and F-Stars in the Region of the North Galactic Pole - Part Three - a Catalogue of Star Names and Positions</title>
			<authors>Hill, G.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Dominion Astrophysical Observatory, Vol. 16, NO. 9, P. 87, 1982</journal>
			<date>0/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982PDAO...16...87H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1964ApJ...140..151H</bibcode>
			<title>Photoelectric Magnitudes and Colors of Stars Near the North Galactic Pole.</title>
			<authors>Harris, D. L., III; Upgren, A. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 140, p.151</journal>
			<date>7/1964</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1964ApJ...140..151H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1956AJ.....61...80S</bibcode>
			<title>Photographic photometry at the North galactic Pole.</title>
			<authors>Stock, J.; Welhau, W. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, Vol. 61, p. 80-90 (1956)</journal>
			<date>3/1956</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1956AJ.....61...80S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
