<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...770...52K</bibcode>
			<title>A Gas Giant Circumbinary Planet Transiting the F Star Primary of the Eclipsing Binary Star KIC 4862625 and the Independent Discovery and Characterization of the Two Transiting Planets in the Kepler-47 System</title>
			<authors>Kostov, V. B.; McCullough, P. R.; Hinse, T. C.; Tsvetanov, Z. I.; H brard, G.; Daz, R. F.; Deleuil, M.; Valenti, J. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 770, Issue 1, article id. 52, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;19&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>6/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...770...52K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...769..152P</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-16b: Safe in a Resonance Cell</title>
			<authors>Popova, Elena A.; Shevchenko, Ivan I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 769, Issue 2, article id. 152, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>6/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...769..152P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...763..107L</bibcode>
			<title>An Analytic Theory for the Orbits of Circumbinary Planets</title>
			<authors>Leung, Gene C. K.; Hoi Lee, Man</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 763, Issue 2, article id. 107, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...763..107L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013MNRAS.428.1656B</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical masses, absolute radii and 3D orbits of the triply eclipsing star HD 181068 from Kepler photometry</title>
			<authors>Borkovits, T.; Derekas, A.; Kiss, L. L.; Kirly, A.; Forgcs-Dajka, E.; Br, I. B.; Bedding, T. R.; Bryson, S. T.; Huber, D.; Szab, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 428, Issue 2, p.1656-1672</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013MNRAS.428.1656B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...763...12B</bibcode>
			<title>Emerging Trends in a Period-Radius Distribution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Beaug, C.; Nesvorn, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 763, Issue 1, article id. 12, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...763...12B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...547A.112M</bibcode>
			<title>Characterization of exoplanets from their formation. II. The planetary mass-radius relationship</title>
			<authors>Mordasini, C.; Alibert, Y.; Georgy, C.; Dittkrist, K.-M.; Klahr, H.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 547, id.A112, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;36&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>11/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...547A.112M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012PASJ...64...97S</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-38b: A Saturn-Mass Planet Transiting a Late G Star</title>
			<authors>Sato, Bun'ei; Hartman, Joel D.; Bakos, Gspr .; Bky, Bence; Torres, Guillermo; Latham, David W.; Kovcs, Gza; Csubry, Zoltn; Penev, Kaloyan; Noyes, Robert W.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Everett, Mark; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Fischer, Debra A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John A.; Marcy, Geoff W.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Szklenr, Tams; Lzr, Jzsef; Papp, Istvn; Sri, Pl</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.64, No.5, Article No.97, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012PASJ...64...97S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.425..930G</bibcode>
			<title>On the HU Aquarii planetary system hypothesis</title>
			<authors>Gozdziewski, Krzysztof; Nasiroglu, Ilham; Slowikowska, Aga; Beuermann, Klaus; Kanbach, Gottfried; Gauza, Bartosz; Maciejewski, Andrzej J.; Schwarz, Robert; Schwope, Axel D.; Hinse, Tobias C.; Haghighipour, Nader; Burwitz, Vadim; Sl onina, Mariusz; Rau, Arne</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 425, Issue 2, pp. 930-949.</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.425..930G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012RAA....12.1081Z</bibcode>
			<title>Forming different planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Zhou, Ji-Lin; Xie, Ji-Wei; Liu, Hui-Gen; Zhang, Hui; Sun, Yi-Sui</authors>
			<journal>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 12, Issue 8, pp. 1081-1106 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012RAA....12.1081Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....144...34H</bibcode>
			<title>The Proposed Quadruple System SZ Herculis: Revised LITE Model and Orbital Stability Study</title>
			<authors>Hinse, Tobias Cornelius; Gozdziewski, Krzysztof; Lee, Jae Woo; Haghighipour, Nader; Lee, Chung-Uk</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 144, Issue 2, article id. 34, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....144...34H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754L..16P</bibcode>
			<title>How Not to Build Tatooine: The Difficulty of In Situ Formation of Circumbinary Planets Kepler 16b, Kepler 34b, and Kepler 35b</title>
			<authors>Paardekooper, Sijme-Jan; Leinhardt, Zo M.; Thbault, Philippe; Baruteau, Clment</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 754, Issue 1, article id. L16, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754L..16P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...71M</bibcode>
			<title>Circumbinary Planet Formation in the Kepler-16 System. I. N-body Simulations</title>
			<authors>Meschiari, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 71, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...71M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751L..31B</bibcode>
			<title>The SDSS-HET Survey of Kepler Eclipsing Binaries: Spectroscopic Dynamical Masses of the Kepler-16 Circumbinary Planet Hosts</title>
			<authors>Bender, Chad F.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Deshpande, Rohit; Wright, Jason T.; Roy, Arpita; Terrien, Ryan C.; Sigurdsson, Steinn; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Schneider, Donald P.; Fleming, Scott W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. L31, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751L..31B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..475W</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting circumbinary planets Kepler-34 b and Kepler-35 b</title>
			<authors>Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Bloemen, Steven; Brugamyer, Erik; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Caroline; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Klaus, Todd C.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Quintana, Elisa V.; Robertson, Paul; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Windmiller, Gur; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 475-479 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..475W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..448S</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: A new class of planet</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 448-449 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..448S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...770...52K</bibcode>
			<title>A Gas Giant Circumbinary Planet Transiting the F Star Primary of the Eclipsing Binary Star KIC 4862625 and the Independent Discovery and Characterization of the Two Transiting Planets in the Kepler-47 System</title>
			<authors>Kostov, V. B.; McCullough, P. R.; Hinse, T. C.; Tsvetanov, Z. I.; H brard, G.; Daz, R. F.; Deleuil, M.; Valenti, J. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 770, Issue 1, article id. 52, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;19&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>6/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...770...52K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...769..152P</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-16b: Safe in a Resonance Cell</title>
			<authors>Popova, Elena A.; Shevchenko, Ivan I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 769, Issue 2, article id. 152, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>6/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...769..152P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...767L..38L</bibcode>
			<title>Where to Find Habitable "Earths" in Circumbinary Systems</title>
			<authors>Liu, Hui-Gen; Zhang, Hui; Zhou, Ji-Lin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 767, Issue 2, article id. L38, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...767L..38L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...551A.108M</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-site campaign for transit timing variations of WASP-12 b: possible detection of a long-period signal of planetary origin</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Seeliger, M.; Raetz, St.; Bukowiecki, L.; Kitze, M.; Errmann, R.; Nowak, G.; Niedzielski, A.; Popov, V.; Marka, C.; Gozdziewski, K.; Neuhuser, R.; Ohlert, J.; Hinse, T. C.; Lee, J. W.; Lee, C.-U.; Yoon, J.-N.; Berndt, A.; Gilbert, H.; Ginski, Ch.; Hohle, M. M.; Mugrauer, M.; Rll, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Tetzlaff, N.; Mancini, L.; Southworth, J.; Dall'Ora, M.; Ciceri, S.; Zambelli, R.; Corfini, G.; Takahashi, H.; Tachihara, K.; Benko , J. M.; Srneczky, K.; Szabo, Gy. M.; Varga, T. N.; Vanko, M.; Joshi, Y. C.; Chen, W. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 551, id.A108, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...551A.108M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...551A..73F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-54b, WASP-56b, and WASP-57b: Three new sub-Jupiter mass planets from SuperWASP</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Pollacco, D.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D.; Collier Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Enoch, R.; Gillon, M.; Gmez Maqueo Chew, Y.; Hbrard, G.; Lendl, M.; Liebig, C.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.; Alsubai, K. A.; Anderson, D. R.; Armstrong, D.; Bento, J.; Bochinski, J.; Bouchy, F.; Busuttil, R.; Fossati, L.; Fumel, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Jehin, E.; Kolb, U.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 551, id.A73, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;17&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...551A..73F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764L..16R</bibcode>
			<title>Building Tatooine: Suppression of the Direct Secular Excitation in Kepler Circumbinary Planet Formation</title>
			<authors>Rafikov, Roman R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. L16, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764L..16R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764..106F</bibcode>
			<title>Assembly of Protoplanetary Disks and Inclinations of Circumbinary Planets</title>
			<authors>Foucart, Francois; Lai, Dong</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. 106, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764..106F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...763..107L</bibcode>
			<title>An Analytic Theory for the Orbits of Circumbinary Planets</title>
			<authors>Leung, Gene C. K.; Hoi Lee, Man</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 763, Issue 2, article id. 107, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...763..107L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...763L...8G</bibcode>
			<title>Terrestrial Planet Formation around the Circumbinary Habitable Zone: Inward Migration in the Planetesimal Swarm</title>
			<authors>Gong, Yan-Xiang; Zhou, Ji-Lin; Xie, Ji-Wei</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 763, Issue 1, article id. L8, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...763L...8G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...762....7K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Habitable Zones of Circumbinary Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Hinkel, Natalie R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 762, Issue 1, article id. 7, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...762....7K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...549A..95Z</bibcode>
			<title>Origin of apparent period variations in eclipsing post-common-envelope binaries</title>
			<authors>Zorotovic, M.; Schreiber, M. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 549, id.A95, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...549A..95Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...761L...7M</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Formation in Circumbinary Configurations: Turbulence Inhibits Planetesimal Accretion</title>
			<authors>Meschiari, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 761, Issue 1, article id. L7, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...761L...7M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...761..157B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Studies of Low-mass Eclipsing Binaries. I. Parameters of the Long-period Binary KIC 6131659</title>
			<authors>Bass, Gideon; Orosz, Jerome A.; Welsh, William F.; Windmiller, Gur; Ames Gregg, Trevor; Fetherolf, Tara; Wade, Richard A.; Quinn, Samuel N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 761, Issue 2, article id. 157, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...761..157B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...758...87O</bibcode>
			<title>The Neptune-sized Circumbinary Planet Kepler-38b</title>
			<authors>Orosz, Jerome A.; Welsh, William F.; Carter, Joshua A.; Brugamyer, Erik; Buchhave, Lars A.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Ford, Eric B.; MacQueen, Phillip; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Windmiller, Gur; Agol, Eric; Barclay, Thomas; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Geary, John C.; Haghighipour, Nader; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Li, Jie; Lissauer, Jack J.; Prsa, Andrej; Ragozzine, Darin; Shporer, Avi; Still, Martin; Wade, Richard A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 758, Issue 2, article id. 87, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...758...87O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...337.1511O</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-47: A Transiting Circumbinary Multiplanet System</title>
			<authors>Orosz, Jerome A.; Welsh, William F.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Ford, Eric B.; Haghighipour, Nader; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Agol, Eric; Buchhave, Lars A.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Isaacson, Howard; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Shporer, Avi; Windmiller, Gur; Barclay, Thomas; Boss, Alan P.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Fortney, Jonathan; Geary, John C.; Holman, Matthew J.; Huber, Daniel; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Kruse, Ethan; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Uddin, Kamal; Winn, Joshua N.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 337, Issue 6101, pp. 1511- (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Sci...337.1511O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.425..930G</bibcode>
			<title>On the HU Aquarii planetary system hypothesis</title>
			<authors>Gozdziewski, Krzysztof; Nasiroglu, Ilham; Slowikowska, Aga; Beuermann, Klaus; Kanbach, Gottfried; Gauza, Bartosz; Maciejewski, Andrzej J.; Schwarz, Robert; Schwope, Axel D.; Hinse, Tobias C.; Haghighipour, Nader; Burwitz, Vadim; Sl onina, Mariusz; Rau, Arne</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 425, Issue 2, pp. 930-949.</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.425..930G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012RAA....12.1081Z</bibcode>
			<title>Forming different planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Zhou, Ji-Lin; Xie, Ji-Wei; Liu, Hui-Gen; Zhang, Hui; Sun, Yi-Sui</authors>
			<journal>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 12, Issue 8, pp. 1081-1106 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012RAA....12.1081Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...755...17Y</bibcode>
			<title>Circumbinary Chaos: Using Pluto's Newest Moon to Constrain the Masses of Nix and Hydra</title>
			<authors>Youdin, Andrew N.; Kratter, Kaitlin M.; Kenyon, Scott J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 755, Issue 1, article id. 17, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...755...17Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754L..16P</bibcode>
			<title>How Not to Build Tatooine: The Difficulty of In Situ Formation of Circumbinary Planets Kepler 16b, Kepler 34b, and Kepler 35b</title>
			<authors>Paardekooper, Sijme-Jan; Leinhardt, Zo M.; Thbault, Philippe; Baruteau, Clment</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 754, Issue 1, article id. L16, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754L..16P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...72D</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation between the Eclipse Depths of Kepler Gas Giant Candidates and the Metallicities of Their Parent Stars</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 72, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...72D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...542A..92R</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planets in stellar multiple systems</title>
			<authors>Roell, T.; Neuhuser, R.; Seifahrt, A.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 542, id.A92, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...542A..92R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJS..199...24T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Potential Transit Signals in the First Three Quarters of Kepler Mission Data</title>
			<authors>Tenenbaum, Peter; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Seader, Shawn; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Quintana, Elisa V.; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Stumpe, Martin C.; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Borucki, William J.; Cote, Miles T.; Haas, Michael R.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Girouard, Forrest R.; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Wohler, Bill; Batalha, Natalie M.; Barclay, Thomas; Nickerson, James E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 199, Issue 1, article id. 24, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;15&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJS..199...24T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..475W</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting circumbinary planets Kepler-34 b and Kepler-35 b</title>
			<authors>Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Bloemen, Steven; Brugamyer, Erik; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Caroline; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Klaus, Todd C.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Quintana, Elisa V.; Robertson, Paul; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Windmiller, Gur; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 475-479 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..475W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142....2F</bibcode>
			<title>The Burrell-Optical-Kepler-Survey (BOKS). I. Survey Description and Initial Results</title>
			<authors>Feldmeier, John J.; Howell, Steve B.; Sherry, William; von Braun, Kaspar; Everett, Mark E.; Ciardi, David R.; Harding, Paul; Mihos, J. Christopher; Rudick, Craig S.; Lee, Ting-Hui; Kutsko, Rebecca M.; van Belle, Gerard T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 1, article id. 2, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;19&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142....2F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A..89D</bibcode>
			<title>Global stellar variability study in the field-of-view of the Kepler satellite</title>
			<authors>Debosscher, J.; Blomme, J.; Aerts, C.; De Ridder, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A89, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;15&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A..89D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...83P</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Eclipsing Binary Stars. I. Catalog and Principal Characterization of 1879 Eclipsing Binaries in the First Data Release</title>
			<authors>Prsa, Andrej; Batalha, Natalie; Slawson, Robert W.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Seager, Sara; Rucker, Michael; Mjaseth, Kimberly; Engle, Scott G.; Conroy, Kyle; Jenkins, Jon; Caldwell, Douglas; Koch, David; Borucki, William</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 3, article id. 83, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...83P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Low-mass Eclipsing Binaries in the Initial Kepler Data Release</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, J. L.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Harrison, T. E.; Ule, N.; Hoffman, D. I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 3, article id. 78, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...78C</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
