<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...770...52K</bibcode>
			<title>A Gas Giant Circumbinary Planet Transiting the F Star Primary of the Eclipsing Binary Star KIC 4862625 and the Independent Discovery and Characterization of the Two Transiting Planets in the Kepler-47 System</title>
			<authors>Kostov, V. B.; McCullough, P. R.; Hinse, T. C.; Tsvetanov, Z. I.; H brard, G.; Daz, R. F.; Deleuil, M.; Valenti, J. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 770, Issue 1, article id. 52, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;19&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>6/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...770...52K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...767L..38L</bibcode>
			<title>Where to Find Habitable "Earths" in Circumbinary Systems</title>
			<authors>Liu, Hui-Gen; Zhang, Hui; Zhou, Ji-Lin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 767, Issue 2, article id. L38, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...767L..38L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...765..131K</bibcode>
			<title>Habitable Zones around Main-sequence Stars: New Estimates</title>
			<authors>Kopparapu, Ravi Kumar; Ramirez, Ramses; Kasting, James F.; Eymet, Vincent; Robinson, Tyler D.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Terrien, Ryan C.; Domagal-Goldman, Shawn; Meadows, Victoria; Deshpande, Rohit</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 765, Issue 2, article id. 131, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...765..131K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...337.1511O</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-47: A Transiting Circumbinary Multiplanet System</title>
			<authors>Orosz, Jerome A.; Welsh, William F.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Ford, Eric B.; Haghighipour, Nader; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Agol, Eric; Buchhave, Lars A.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Isaacson, Howard; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Shporer, Avi; Windmiller, Gur; Barclay, Thomas; Boss, Alan P.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Fortney, Jonathan; Geary, John C.; Holman, Matthew J.; Huber, Daniel; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Kruse, Ethan; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Uddin, Kamal; Winn, Joshua N.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 337, Issue 6101, pp. 1511- (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Sci...337.1511O</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...770...52K</bibcode>
			<title>A Gas Giant Circumbinary Planet Transiting the F Star Primary of the Eclipsing Binary Star KIC 4862625 and the Independent Discovery and Characterization of the Two Transiting Planets in the Kepler-47 System</title>
			<authors>Kostov, V. B.; McCullough, P. R.; Hinse, T. C.; Tsvetanov, Z. I.; H brard, G.; Daz, R. F.; Deleuil, M.; Valenti, J. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 770, Issue 1, article id. 52, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;19&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>6/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...770...52K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...769..152P</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-16b: Safe in a Resonance Cell</title>
			<authors>Popova, Elena A.; Shevchenko, Ivan I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 769, Issue 2, article id. 152, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>6/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...769..152P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...768..127S</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Hunters: A Transiting Circumbinary Planet in a Quadruple Star System</title>
			<authors>Schwamb, Megan E.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Welsh, William F.; Fischer, Debra A.; Torres, Guillermo; Howard, Andrew W.; Crepp, Justin R.; Keel, William C.; Lintott, Chris J.; Kaib, Nathan A.; Terrell, Dirk; Gagliano, Robert; Jek, Kian J.; Parrish, Michael; Smith, Arfon M.; Lynn, Stuart; Simpson, Robert J.; Giguere, Matthew J.; Schawinski, Kevin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 768, Issue 2, article id. 127, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;21&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>5/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...768..127S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...767L..38L</bibcode>
			<title>Where to Find Habitable "Earths" in Circumbinary Systems</title>
			<authors>Liu, Hui-Gen; Zhang, Hui; Zhou, Ji-Lin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 767, Issue 2, article id. L38, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...767L..38L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764L..16R</bibcode>
			<title>Building Tatooine: Suppression of the Direct Secular Excitation in Kepler Circumbinary Planet Formation</title>
			<authors>Rafikov, Roman R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. L16, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764L..16R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764..106F</bibcode>
			<title>Assembly of Protoplanetary Disks and Inclinations of Circumbinary Planets</title>
			<authors>Foucart, Francois; Lai, Dong</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. 106, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764..106F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...763..107L</bibcode>
			<title>An Analytic Theory for the Orbits of Circumbinary Planets</title>
			<authors>Leung, Gene C. K.; Hoi Lee, Man</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 763, Issue 2, article id. 107, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...763..107L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...763...41C</bibcode>
			<title>On the Relative Sizes of Planets within Kepler Multiple-candidate Systems</title>
			<authors>Ciardi, David R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, T. N., III; Howell, Steve B.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Rowe, Jason F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 763, Issue 1, article id. 41, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...763...41C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...762....7K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Habitable Zones of Circumbinary Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Hinkel, Natalie R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 762, Issue 1, article id. 7, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...762....7K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...761L...7M</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Formation in Circumbinary Configurations: Turbulence Inhibits Planetesimal Accretion</title>
			<authors>Meschiari, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 761, Issue 1, article id. L7, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...761L...7M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...337.1511O</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-47: A Transiting Circumbinary Multiplanet System</title>
			<authors>Orosz, Jerome A.; Welsh, William F.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Ford, Eric B.; Haghighipour, Nader; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Agol, Eric; Buchhave, Lars A.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Isaacson, Howard; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Shporer, Avi; Windmiller, Gur; Barclay, Thomas; Boss, Alan P.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Fortney, Jonathan; Geary, John C.; Holman, Matthew J.; Huber, Daniel; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Kruse, Ethan; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Uddin, Kamal; Winn, Joshua N.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 337, Issue 6101, pp. 1511- (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Sci...337.1511O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJS..199...24T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Potential Transit Signals in the First Three Quarters of Kepler Mission Data</title>
			<authors>Tenenbaum, Peter; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Seader, Shawn; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Quintana, Elisa V.; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Stumpe, Martin C.; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Borucki, William J.; Cote, Miles T.; Haas, Michael R.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Girouard, Forrest R.; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Wohler, Bill; Batalha, Natalie M.; Barclay, Thomas; Nickerson, James E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 199, Issue 1, article id. 24, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;15&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJS..199...24T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...83P</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Eclipsing Binary Stars. I. Catalog and Principal Characterization of 1879 Eclipsing Binaries in the First Data Release</title>
			<authors>Prsa, Andrej; Batalha, Natalie; Slawson, Robert W.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Seager, Sara; Rucker, Michael; Mjaseth, Kimberly; Engle, Scott G.; Conroy, Kyle; Jenkins, Jon; Caldwell, Douglas; Koch, David; Borucki, William</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 3, article id. 83, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...83P</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
