<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....144...34H</bibcode>
			<title>The Proposed Quadruple System SZ Herculis: Revised LITE Model and Orbital Stability Study</title>
			<authors>Hinse, Tobias Cornelius; Gozdziewski, Krzysztof; Lee, Jae Woo; Haghighipour, Nader; Lee, Chung-Uk</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 144, Issue 2, article id. 34, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....144...34H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754L..16P</bibcode>
			<title>How Not to Build Tatooine: The Difficulty of In Situ Formation of Circumbinary Planets Kepler 16b, Kepler 34b, and Kepler 35b</title>
			<authors>Paardekooper, Sijme-Jan; Leinhardt, Zo M.; Thbault, Philippe; Baruteau, Clment</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 754, Issue 1, article id. L16, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754L..16P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...71M</bibcode>
			<title>Circumbinary Planet Formation in the Kepler-16 System. I. N-body Simulations</title>
			<authors>Meschiari, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 71, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...71M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751L..31B</bibcode>
			<title>The SDSS-HET Survey of Kepler Eclipsing Binaries: Spectroscopic Dynamical Masses of the Kepler-16 Circumbinary Planet Hosts</title>
			<authors>Bender, Chad F.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Deshpande, Rohit; Wright, Jason T.; Roy, Arpita; Terrien, Ryan C.; Sigurdsson, Steinn; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Schneider, Donald P.; Fleming, Scott W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. L31, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751L..31B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..475W</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting circumbinary planets Kepler-34 b and Kepler-35 b</title>
			<authors>Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Bloemen, Steven; Brugamyer, Erik; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Caroline; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Klaus, Todd C.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Quintana, Elisa V.; Robertson, Paul; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Windmiller, Gur; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 475-479 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..475W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..448S</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: A new class of planet</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 448-449 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..448S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...758...87O</bibcode>
			<title>The Neptune-sized Circumbinary Planet Kepler-38b</title>
			<authors>Orosz, Jerome A.; Welsh, William F.; Carter, Joshua A.; Brugamyer, Erik; Buchhave, Lars A.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Ford, Eric B.; MacQueen, Phillip; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Windmiller, Gur; Agol, Eric; Barclay, Thomas; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Geary, John C.; Haghighipour, Nader; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Li, Jie; Lissauer, Jack J.; Prsa, Andrej; Ragozzine, Darin; Shporer, Avi; Still, Martin; Wade, Richard A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 758, Issue 2, article id. 87, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...758...87O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...337.1511O</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-47: A Transiting Circumbinary Multiplanet System</title>
			<authors>Orosz, Jerome A.; Welsh, William F.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Ford, Eric B.; Haghighipour, Nader; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Agol, Eric; Buchhave, Lars A.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Isaacson, Howard; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Shporer, Avi; Windmiller, Gur; Barclay, Thomas; Boss, Alan P.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Fortney, Jonathan; Geary, John C.; Holman, Matthew J.; Huber, Daniel; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Kruse, Ethan; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Uddin, Kamal; Winn, Joshua N.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 337, Issue 6101, pp. 1511- (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Sci...337.1511O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...755...17Y</bibcode>
			<title>Circumbinary Chaos: Using Pluto's Newest Moon to Constrain the Masses of Nix and Hydra</title>
			<authors>Youdin, Andrew N.; Kratter, Kaitlin M.; Kenyon, Scott J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 755, Issue 1, article id. 17, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...755...17Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754L..16P</bibcode>
			<title>How Not to Build Tatooine: The Difficulty of In Situ Formation of Circumbinary Planets Kepler 16b, Kepler 34b, and Kepler 35b</title>
			<authors>Paardekooper, Sijme-Jan; Leinhardt, Zo M.; Thbault, Philippe; Baruteau, Clment</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 754, Issue 1, article id. L16, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754L..16P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...72D</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation between the Eclipse Depths of Kepler Gas Giant Candidates and the Metallicities of Their Parent Stars</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 72, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...72D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...542A..92R</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planets in stellar multiple systems</title>
			<authors>Roell, T.; Neuhuser, R.; Seifahrt, A.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 542, id.A92, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...542A..92R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..475W</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting circumbinary planets Kepler-34 b and Kepler-35 b</title>
			<authors>Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Bloemen, Steven; Brugamyer, Erik; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Caroline; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Klaus, Todd C.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Quintana, Elisa V.; Robertson, Paul; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Windmiller, Gur; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 475-479 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..475W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..448S</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: A new class of planet</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 448-449 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..448S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
