<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJS..204...24B</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. III. Analysis of the First 16 Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Batalha, Natalie M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Barclay, Thomas; Burke, Christopher J.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Mullally, Fergal; Thompson, Susan E.; Brown, Timothy M.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Isaacson, Howard; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Shporer, Avi; Borucki, William J.; Ciardi, David R.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Haas, Michael R.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Rapin, William; Basri, Gibor S.; Boss, Alan P.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Joergen; Clarke, Bruce D.; Cochran, William D.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; Desert, Jean-Michel; Devore, Edna; Doyle, Laurance R.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark; Fressin, Francois; Geary, John C.; Girouard, Forrest R.; Gould, Alan; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Kjeldsen, Hans; Klaus, Todd C.; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Meibom, Sren; Morris, Robert L.; Prsa, Andrej; Quintana, Elisa; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Seader, Shawn E.; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Steffen, Jason H.; Still, Martin; Stumpe, Martin C.; Tarter, Jill C.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Uddin, Kamal; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 204, Issue 2, article id. 24, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;21&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJS..204...24B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754..129S</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Hunters: Assessing the Kepler Inventory of Short-period Planets</title>
			<authors>Schwamb, Megan E.; Lintott, Chris J.; Fischer, Debra A.; Giguere, Matthew J.; Lynn, Stuart; Smith, Arfon M.; Brewer, John M.; Parrish, Michael; Schawinski, Kevin; Simpson, Robert J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 754, Issue 2, article id. 129, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;17&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754..129S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJS..199...24T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Potential Transit Signals in the First Three Quarters of Kepler Mission Data</title>
			<authors>Tenenbaum, Peter; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Seader, Shawn; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Quintana, Elisa V.; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Stumpe, Martin C.; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Borucki, William J.; Cote, Miles T.; Haas, Michael R.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Girouard, Forrest R.; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Wohler, Bill; Batalha, Natalie M.; Barclay, Thomas; Nickerson, James E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 199, Issue 1, article id. 24, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;15&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJS..199...24T</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
