<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...763..141G</bibcode>
			<title>MOA-2010-BLG-523: "Failed Planet" = RS CVn Star</title>
			<authors>Gould, A.; Yee, J. C.; Bond, I. A.; Udalski, A.; Han, C.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Greenhill, J.; Tsapras, Y.; Pinsonneault, M. H.; Bensby, T.; Allen, W.; Almeida, L. A.; Bos, M.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Dong, Subo; Gaudi, B. S.; Hung, L.-W.; Jablonski, F.; Lee, C.-U.; McCormick, J.; Moorhouse, D.; Muoz, J. A.; Natusch, T.; Nola, M.; Pogge, R. W.; Skowron, J.; Thornley, G.; The mu FUN Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Botzler, C. S.; Chote, P.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Harris, P.; Itow, Y.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Ohnishi, K.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Saito, To.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Suzuki, D.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Wada, K.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; Szymanski, M. K.; Soszynski, I.; Kubiak, M.; Poleski, R.; Ulaczyk, K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Wyrzykowski, L.; The OGLE Collaboration; Alsubai, K. A.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dodds, P.; Dominik, M.; Finet, F.; Gerner, T.; Hardis, S.; Harpse, K.; Hessman, F. V.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Kains, N.; Kerins, E.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Mathiasen, M.; Penny, M. T.; Proft, S.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Sahu, K. C.; Scarpetta, G.; Schfer, S.; Schnebeck, F.; Snodgrass, C.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Wambsganss, J.; MiNDSTEp Consortium, The; Street, R. A.; Horne, K.; Bramich, D. M.; Steele, I. A.; The RoboNet Collaboration; Albrow, M. D.; Bachelet, E.; Batista, V.; Beatty, T. G.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bennett, C. S.; Bowens-Rubin, R.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A. A.; Corrales, E.; Coutures, C.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu, P.; Henderson, C. B.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Menzies, J. W.; Shappee, B.; Williams, A.; van Saders, J.; Zub, M.; The PLANET Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 763, Issue 2, article id. 141, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...763..141G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...763...67S</bibcode>
			<title>MOA-2010-BLG-073L: An M-dwarf with a Substellar Companion at the Planet/Brown Dwarf Boundary</title>
			<authors>Street, R. A.; Choi, J.-Y.; Tsapras, Y.; Han, C.; Furusawa, K.; Hundertmark, M.; Gould, A.; Sumi, T.; Bond, I. A.; Wouters, D.; Zellem, R.; Udalski, A.; The RoboNet Collaboration; Snodgrass, C.; Horne, K.; Dominik, M.; Browne, P.; Kains, N.; Bramich, D. M.; Bajek, D.; Steele, I. A.; Ipatov, S.; The MOA Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Botzler, C. S.; Chote, P.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Harris, P.; Itow, Y.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagayama, T.; Nishimaya, S.; Ohnishi, K.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sullivan, D. J.; Suzuki, D.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Wada, K.; Yock, P. C. M.; The OGLE Collaboration; Szyman ski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Poleski, R.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; The muFUN Collaboration; Yee, J.; Dong, S.; Shin, I.-G.; Lee, C.-U.; Skowron, J.; De Almeida, L. Andrade; DePoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Hung, L.-W.; Jablonski, F.; Kaspi, S.; Klein, N.; Hwang, K.-H.; Koo, J.-R.; Maoz, D.; Muoz, J. A.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishhook, D.; Shporer, A.; McCormick, J.; Christie, G.; Natusch, T.; Allen, B.; Drummond, J.; Moorhouse, D.; Thornley, G.; Knowler, M.; Bos, M.; Bolt, G.; The PLANET Collaboration; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Albrow, M. D.; Batista, V.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Corrales, E.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu, P.; Bachelet, E.; Greenhill, J.; Kane, S. R.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Menzies, J.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Wambsganss, J.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; MiNDSTEp; Alsubai, K. A.; Bozza, V.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dodds, P.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Gerner, T.; Hardis, S.; Harpse, K.; Hessman, F.; Hinse, T. C.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kerins, E.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Mathiasen, M.; Penny, M. T.; Proft, S.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Schfer, S.; Schnebeck, F.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 763, Issue 1, article id. 67, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...763...67S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
