<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...769...77Y</bibcode>
			<title>MOA-2010-BLG-311: A Planetary Candidate below the Threshold of Reliable Detection</title>
			<authors>Yee, J. C.; Hung, L.-W.; Bond, I. A.; Allen, W.; Monard, L. A. G.; Albrow, M. D.; Fouqu, P.; Dominik, M.; Tsapras, Y.; Udalski, A.; Gould, A.; Zellem, R.; Bos, M.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Dong, Subo; Drummond, J.; Gaudi, B. S.; Gorbikov, E.; Han, C.; Kaspi, S.; Klein, N.; Lee, C.-U.; Maoz, D.; McCormick, J.; Moorhouse, D.; Natusch, T.; Nola, M.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Shporer, A.; Shvartzvald, Y.; Skowron, J.; Thornley, G.; The mu FUN Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Botzler, C. S.; Chote, P.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Harris, P.; Itow, Y.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Ohnishi, K.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Saito, To.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Suzuki, D.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Wada, K.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; Szymanski, M. K.; Soszynski, I.; Kubiak, M.; Poleski, R.; Ulaczyk, K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Wyrzykowski, L.; The OGLE Collaboration; Bachelet, E.; Batista, V.; Beatty, T. G.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bennett, C. S.; Bowens-Rubin, R.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A. A.; Corrales, E.; Coutures, C.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Greenhill, J.; Henderson, C. B.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Menzies, J. W.; Shappee, B.; Williams, A.; Wouters, D.; van Saders, J.; Zub, M.; The PLANET Collaboration; Street, R. A.; Horne, K.; Bramich, D. M.; Steele, I. A.; The RoboNet Collaboration; Alsubai, K. A.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dodds, P.; Finet, F.; Gerner, T.; Hardis, S.; Harpse, K.; Hessman, F. V.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kains, N.; Kerins, E.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Mathiasen, M.; Penny, M. T.; Proft, S.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Sahu, K. C.; Scarpetta, G.; Schfer, S.; Schnebeck, F.; Snodgrass, C.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Wambsganss, J.; MiNDSTEp Consortium, The</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 769, Issue 1, article id. 77, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>5/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...769...77Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...549A.147B</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical evolution of the Galactic bulge as traced by microlensed dwarf and subgiant stars. V. Evidence for a wide age distribution and a complex MDF</title>
			<authors>Bensby, T.; Yee, J. C.; Feltzing, S.; Johnson, J. A.; Gould, A.; Cohen, J. G.; Asplund, M.; Melndez, J.; Lucatello, S.; Han, C.; Thompson, I.; Gal-Yam, A.; Udalski, A.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Kohei, W.; Sumi, T.; Suzuki, D.; Suzuki, K.; Takino, S.; Tristram, P.; Yamai, N.; Yonehara, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 549, id.A147, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;26&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...549A.147B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...549A.109B</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XXXI. The M-dwarf sample</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.; Forveille, T.; Mayor, M.; Perrier, C.; Bouchy, F.; Gillon, M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S gransan, D.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 549, id.A109, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;75&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...549A.109B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.426.1496I</bibcode>
			<title>Polarization in microlensing events towards the Galactic bulge</title>
			<authors>Ingrosso, G.; Calchi Novati, S.; De Paolis, F.; Jetzer, Ph.; Nucita, A. A.; Strafella, F.; Zakharov, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 426, Issue 2, pp. 1496-1506.</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.426.1496I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...41C</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing Lenses and Lensed Stars of High-magnification Single-lens Gravitational Microlensing Events with Lenses Passing over Source Stars</title>
			<authors>Choi, J.-Y.; Shin, I.-G.; Park, S.-Y.; Han, C.; Gould, A.; Sumi, T.; Udalski, A.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Street, R.; Dominik, M.; Allen, W.; Almeida, L. A.; Bos, M.; Christie, G. W.; Depoy, D. L.; Dong, S.; Drummond, J.; Gal-Yam, A.; Gaudi, B. S.; Henderson, C. B.; Hung, L.-W.; Jablonski, F.; Janczak, J.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Maury, A.; McCormick, J.; McGregor, D.; Monard, L. A. G.; Moorhouse, D.; Mu oz, J. A.; Natusch, T.; Nelson, C.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; "TG" Tan, T.-G.; Thornley, G.; Yee, J. C.; muFUN Collaboration; Abe, F.; Barnard, E.; Baudry, J.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Botzler, C. S.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hayashi, F.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Kobara, S.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Omori, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Suzuki, D.; Suzuki, K.; Sweatman, W. L.; Takino, S.; Tristram, P. J.; Wada, K.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Poleski, R.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Kozlowski, S.; Pietrukowicz, P.; OGLE Collaboration; Albrow, M. D.; Bachelet, E.; Batista, V.; Bennett, C. S.; Bowens-Rubin, R.; Brillant, S.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Corrales, E.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu, P.; Greenhill, J.; Kane, S. R.; Menzies, J.; Sahu, K. C.; Wambsganss, J.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; PLANET Collaboration; Allan, A.; Bramich, D. M.; Browne, P.; Clay, N.; Fraser, S.; Horne, K.; Kains, N.; Mottram, C.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; RoboNet Collaboration; Alsubai, K. A.; Bozza, V.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dodds, P.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Gerner, T.; Glitrup, M.; Grundahl, F.; Hardis, S.; Harpse, K.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kerins, E.; Liebig, C.; Maier, G.; Mancini, L.; Mathiasen, M.; Penny, M. T.; Proft, S.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Schfer, S.; Schnebeck, F.; Skottfelt, J.; Surdej, J.; Southworth, J.; Zimmer, F.; MiNDSTEp Consortium</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 1, article id. 41, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751...41C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewAR..56...25B</bibcode>
			<title>The first extrasolar planet detected via gravitational microlensing</title>
			<authors>Bond, Ian A.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 56, Issue 1, p. 25-32.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewAR..56...25B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.134B</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical evolution of the Galactic bulge as traced by microlensed dwarf and subgiant stars. IV. Two bulge populations</title>
			<authors>Bensby, T.; Adn, D.; Melndez, J.; Gould, A.; Feltzing, S.; Asplund, M.; Johnson, J. A.; Lucatello, S.; Yee, J. C.; Ramrez, I.; Cohen, J. G.; Thompson, I.; Bond, I. A.; Gal-Yam, A.; Han, C.; Sumi, T.; Suzuki, D.; Wada, K.; Miyake, N.; Furusawa, K.; Ohmori, K.; Saito, To.; Tristram, P.; Bennett, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A134, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A.134B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.102B</bibcode>
			<title>MOA-2009-BLG-387Lb: a massive planet orbiting an M dwarf</title>
			<authors>Batista, V.; Gould, A.; Dieters, S.; Dong, S.; Bond, I.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Maoz, D.; Monard, B.; Christie, G. W.; McCormick, J.; Albrow, M. D.; Horne, K.; Tsapras, Y.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Calchi Novati, S.; Skottfelt, J.; Caldwell, J.; Kozl owski, S.; Kubas, D.; Gaudi, B. S.; Han, C.; Bennett, D. P.; An, J.; MOA Collaboration; Abe, F.; Botzler, C. S.; Douchin, D.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, B. S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; von Seggern, E.; Yock, P. C. M.; PLANET Collaboration; Brillant, S.; Calitz, J. J.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Cook, K.; Coutures, C.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Greenhill, J.; Hoffman, M.; Jablonski, F.; Kane, S. R.; Kains, N.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Martioli, E.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pedretti, E.; Pollard, K.; Sahu, K. C.; Vinter, C.; Wambsganss, J.; Watson, R.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; FUN Collaboration; Allen, W.; Bolt, G.; Bos, M.; DePoy, D. L.; Drummond, J.; Eastman, J. D.; Gal-Yam, A.; Gorbikov, E.; Higgins, D.; Janczak, J.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Maury, A.; Monard, L. A. G.; Moorhouse, D.; Morgan, N.; Natusch, T.; Ofek, E. O.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Santallo, R.; Shporer, A.; Spector, O.; Thornley, G.; Yee, J. C.; MiNDSTEp Consortium; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Dominik, M.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Glitrup, M.; Grundahl, F.; Harpse, K.; Hessman, F. V.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Maier, G.; Mancini, L.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Zimmer, F.; RoboNet Collaboration; Allan, A.; Bramich, D. M.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I. A.; Street, R. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A102, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.102B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1073G</bibcode>
			<title>Frequency of Solar-like Systems and of Ice and Gas Giants Beyond the Snow Line from High-magnification Microlensing Events in 2005-2008</title>
			<authors>Gould, A.; Dong, Subo; Gaudi, B. S.; Udalski, A.; Bond, I. A.; Greenhill, J.; Street, R. A.; Dominik, M.; Sumi, T.; Szymanski, M. K.; Han, C.; Allen, W.; Bolt, G.; Bos, M.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Drummond, J.; Eastman, J. D.; Gal-Yam, A.; Higgins, D.; Janczak, J.; Kaspi, S.; Kozlowski, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Maury, A.; Maoz, D.; McCormick, J.; Monard, L. A. G.; Moorhouse, D.; Morgan, N.; Natusch, T.; Ofek, E. O.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Santallo, R.; Shporer, A.; Spector, O.; Thornley, G.; Yee, J. C.; mu FUN Collaboration; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; Poleski, R.; OGLE Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Botzler, C. S.; Douchin, D.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Philpott, L.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; von Seggern, E.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Albrow, M.; Batista, V.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J.; Calitz, J. J.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Cook, K.; Coutures, C.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu, P.; Hill, K.; Hoffman, M.; Jablonski, F.; Kane, S. R.; Kains, N.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Martioli, E.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pedretti, E.; Pollard, K.; Sahu, K. C.; Vinter, C.; Wambsganss, J.; Watson, R.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; PLANET Collaboration; Allan, A.; Bode, M. F.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Clay, N.; Fraser, S.; Hawkins, E.; Horne, K.; Kerins, E.; Lister, T. A.; Mottram, C.; Saunders, E. S.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I. A.; Tsapras, Y.; RoboNet Collaboration; Jrgensen, U. G.; Anguita, T.; Bozza, V.; Calchi Novati, S.; Harpse, K.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Kjrgaard, P.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Thne, C. C.; MiNDSTEp Consortium</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1073-1089 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1073G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AN....331..671D</bibcode>
			<title>Realisation of a fully-deterministic microlensing observing strategy for inferring planet populations</title>
			<authors>Dominik, M.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Mathiasen, M.; Hinse, T. C.; Calchi Novati, S.; Harpse, K.; Bozza, V.; Anguita, T.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Horne, K.; Hundertmark, M.; Kerins, E.; Kjrgaard, P.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Snodgrass, C.; Southworth, J.; Street, R. A.; Surdej, J.; Thne, C. C.; Tsapras, Y.; Wambsganss, J.; Zub, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.331, Issue 7, p.671</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AN....331..671D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518A..51F</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE 2008-BLG-290: an accurate measurement of the limb darkening of a galactic bulge K Giant spatially resolved by microlensing</title>
			<authors>Fouqu, P.; Heyrovsk, D.; Dong, S.; Gould, A.; Udalski, A.; Albrow, M. D.; Batista, V.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Bramich, D. M.; Calchi Novati, S.; Cassan, A.; Coutures, C.; Dieters, S.; Dominik, M.; Dominis Prester, D.; Greenhill, J.; Horne, K.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kozlowski, S.; Kubas, D.; Lee, C.-H.; Marquette, J.-B.; Mathiasen, M.; Menzies, J.; Monard, L. A. G.; Nishiyama, S.; Papadakis, I.; Street, R.; Sumi, T.; Williams, A.; Yee, J. C.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Cole, A.; Cook, K. H.; Donatowicz, J.; Kains, N.; Kane, S. R.; Martin, R.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Tsapras, Y.; Wambsganss, J.; Depoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Han, C.; Lee, C.-U.; Park, B.-G.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Abe, F.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Gilmore, A. C.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A. V.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D.; Sweatman, W.; Tristram, P. J.; Allan, A.; Bode, M. F.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Clay, N.; Fraser, S. N.; Hawkins, E.; Kerins, E.; Lister, T. A.; Mottram, C. J.; Saunders, E. S.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I. A.; Anguita, T.; Bozza, V.; Harpse, K.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Kj rgaard, P.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Thne, C. C.; Riffeser, A.; Seitz, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.A51, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518A..51F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1408B</bibcode>
			<title>An Efficient Method for Modeling High-magnification Planetary Microlensing Events</title>
			<authors>Bennett, David P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1408-1422 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1408B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..837B</bibcode>
			<title>Masses and Orbital Constraints for the OGLE-2006-BLG-109Lb,c Jupiter/Saturn Analog Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Bennett, D. P.; Rhie, S. H.; Nikolaev, S.; Gaudi, B. S.; Udalski, A.; Gould, A.; Christie, G. W.; Maoz, D.; Dong, S.; McCormick, J.; Szymanski, M. K.; Tristram, P. J.; Macintosh, B.; Cook, K. H.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; OGLE Collaboration; DePoy, D. L.; Han, C.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; muFUN Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bond, I. A.; Botzler, C. S.; Fukui, A.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Ling, J.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Motomura, M.; Muraki, Y.; Nakamura, S.; Okumura, T.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Saito, To.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W. L.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Albrow, M.; Allan, A.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Coutures, C.; Dominik, M.; Dieters, S.; Fouqu, P.; Greenhill, J.; Horne, K.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; PLANET, From the; RoboNet Collaborations; Chaboyer, B.; Crocker, A.; Frank, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 837-855 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..837B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..713J</bibcode>
			<title>The Effect of Differential Limb Magnification on Abundance Analysis of Microlensed Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Johnson, Jennifer A.; Dong, Subo; Gould, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 713-720 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..713J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711L..48C</bibcode>
			<title>A Puzzle Involving Galactic Bulge Microlensing Events</title>
			<authors>Cohen, Judith G.; Gould, Andrew; Thompson, Ian B.; Feltzing, Sofia; Bensby, Thomas; Johnson, Jennifer A.; Huang, Wenjin; Melndez, Jorge; Lucatello, Sara; Asplund, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. L48-L52 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711L..48C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..731J</bibcode>
			<title>Sub-Saturn Planet MOA-2008-BLG-310Lb: Likely to be in the Galactic Bulge</title>
			<authors>Janczak, Julia; Fukui, A.; Dong, Subo; Monard, L. A. G.; Kozlowski, Szymon; Gould, A.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Kubas, Daniel; Marquette, J. B.; Sumi, T.; Bond, I. A.; Bennett, D. P.; Abe, F.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nagayama, T.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Saito, To.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; An, Jin H.; Christie, G. W.; Chung, Sun-Ju; DePoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Han, C.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; muFUN Collaboration; Anguita, T.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dominik, M.; J rgensen, U. G.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; MiNDSTEp Collaboration; Batista, V.; Brillant, S.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Corrales, E.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Fouqu, P.; Greenhill, J.; PLANET Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 2, pp. 731-743 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..731J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1800G</bibcode>
			<title>A Second Method to Photometrically Align Multi-Site Microlensing Light Curves: Source Color in Planetary Event MOA-2007-BLG-192</title>
			<authors>Gould, Andrew; Dong, Subo; Bennett, David P.; Bond, Ian A.; Udalski, Andrzej; Kozlowski, Szymon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1800-1805 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1800G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..447E</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical Composition of Faint (I ~ 21 mag) Microlensed Bulge Dwarf OGLE-2007-BLG-514S</title>
			<authors>Epstein, Courtney R.; Johnson, Jennifer A.; Dong, Subo; Udalski, Andrzej; Gould, Andrew; Becker, George</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 447-457 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..447E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNSSA..68..231M</bibcode>
			<title>CCD Activities at the Bronberg Observatory (CBA Pretoria) in 2008</title>
			<authors>Monard, Berto</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notes of the Astronomical Society of South Africa, vol.68, nos.11 and 12, p.231-234</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNSSA..68..231M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699...66C</bibcode>
			<title>Clues to the Metallicity Distribution in the Galactic Bulge: Abundances in MOA-2008-BLG-310S and MOA-2008-BLG-311S</title>
			<authors>Cohen, Judith G.; Thompson, Ian B.; Sumi, Takahiro; Bond, Ian; Gould, Andrew; Johnson, Jennifer A.; Huang, Wenjin; Burley, Greg</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 66-75 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699...66C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...499..737B</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical evolution of the Galactic bulge as traced by microlensed dwarf and subgiant stars. Detailed abundance analysis of OGLE-2008-BLG-209S</title>
			<authors>Bensby, T.; Johnson, J. A.; Cohen, J.; Feltzing, S.; Udalski, A.; Gould, A.; Huang, W.; Thompson, I.; Simmerer, J.; Adn, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 499, Issue 3, 2009, pp.737-753</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...499..737B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
