<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.424..902B</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE-2008-BLG-510: first automated real-time detection of a weak microlensing anomaly - brown dwarf or stellar binary?</title>
			<authors>Bozza, V.; Dominik, M.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Tsapras, Y.; Bramich, D. M.; Udalski, A.; Bond, I. A.; Liebig, C.; Cassan, A.; Fouqu, P.; Fukui, A.; Hundertmark, M.; Shin, I.-G.; Lee, S. H.; Choi, J.-Y.; Park, S.-Y.; Gould, A.; Allan, A.; Mao, S.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Street, R. A.; Buckley, D.; Nagayama, T.; Mathiasen, M.; Hinse, T. C.; Novati, S. Calchi; Harpse, K.; Mancini, L.; Scarpetta, G.; Anguita, T.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Horne, K.; Hornstrup, A.; Kains, N.; Kerins, E.; Kjrgaard, P.; Masi, G.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Snodgrass, C.; Southworth, J.; Steele, I. A.; Surdej, J.; Thne, C. C.; Wambsganss, J.; Zub, M.; Albrow, M. D.; Batista, V.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bennett, D. P.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Cole, A. A.; Cook, K. H.; Coutures, C.; Dieters, S.; Prester, D. Dominis; Donatowicz, J.; Greenhill, J.; Kane, S. R.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Menzies, J.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Williams, A.; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Poleski, R.; Ulaczyk, K.; DePoy, D. L.; Dong, Subo; Han, C.; Janczak, J.; Lee, C.-U.; Pogge, R. W.; Abe, F.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A. V.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Saito, To.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Suzuki, D.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Wada, K.; Yock, P. C. M.; Gulbis, A.; Hashimoto, Y.; Kniazev, A.; Vaisanen, P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 424, Issue 2, pp. 902-918.</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.424..902B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewAR..56...25B</bibcode>
			<title>The first extrasolar planet detected via gravitational microlensing</title>
			<authors>Bond, Ian A.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 56, Issue 1, p. 25-32.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewAR..56...25B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1641S</bibcode>
			<title>A Cold Neptune-Mass Planet OGLE-2007-BLG-368Lb: Cold Neptunes Are Common</title>
			<authors>Sumi, T.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Udalski, A.; Batista, V.; Dominik, M.; Fouqu, P.; Kubas, D.; Gould, A.; Macintosh, B.; Cook, K.; Dong, S.; Skuljan, L.; Cassan, A.; Abe, F.; Botzler, C. S.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nagayama, T.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Beaulieu, J. P.; Cole, A.; Coutures, Ch.; Duran, M. F.; Greenhill, J.; Jablonski, F.; Marboeuf, U.; Martioli, E.; Pedretti, E.; Pejcha, O.; Rojo, P.; Albrow, M. D.; Brillant, S.; Bode, M.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Calitz, H.; Corrales, E.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Hill, K.; Hoffman, M.; Horne, K.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kains, N.; Kane, S.; Marquette, J. B.; Martin, R.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Street, R.; Tsapras, Y.; Wambsganss, J.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; PLANET Collaboration; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; OGLE Collaboration; Allen, W.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Han, C.; Janczak, J.; Lee, C.-U.; McCormick, J.; Mallia, F.; Monard, B.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Santallo, R.; muFUN Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1641-1653 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1641S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
