<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...768..184H</bibcode>
			<title>Galactic Ultracompact X-Ray Binaries: Disk Stability and Evolution</title>
			<authors>Heinke, C. O.; Ivanova, N.; Engel, M. C.; Pavlovskii, K.; Sivakoff, G. R.; Cartwright, T. F.; Gladstone, J. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 768, Issue 2, article id. 184, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>5/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...768..184H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...552A..69V</bibcode>
			<title>Population synthesis of ultracompact X-ray binaries in the Galactic bulge</title>
			<authors>van Haaften, L. M.; Nelemans, G.; Voss, R.; Toonen, S.; Portegies Zwart, S. F.; Yungelson, L. R.; van der Sluys, M. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 552, id.A69, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...552A..69V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...766....5S</bibcode>
			<title>An Asteroid Belt Interpretation for the Timing Variations of the Millisecond Pulsar B1937+21</title>
			<authors>Shannon, R. M.; Cordes, J. M.; Metcalfe, T. S.; Lazio, T. J. W.; Cognard, I.; Desvignes, G.; Janssen, G. H.; Jessner, A.; Kramer, M.; Lazaridis, K.; Purver, M. B.; Stappers, B. W.; Theureau, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 766, Issue 1, article id. 5, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...766....5S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...765..158K</bibcode>
			<title>A Metal-rich Low-gravity Companion to a Massive Millisecond Pulsar</title>
			<authors>Kaplan, D. L.; Bhalerao, V. B.; van Kerkwijk, M. H.; Koester, D.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Stovall, K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 765, Issue 2, article id. 158, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...765..158K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013MNRAS.428.2295B</bibcode>
			<title>A first-order secular theory for the post-Newtonian two-body problem with spin - I. The restricted case</title>
			<authors>Biscani, Francesco; Carloni, Sante</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 428, Issue 3, p.2295-2310</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013MNRAS.428.2295B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...338.1314P</bibcode>
			<title>Binary Millisecond Pulsar Discovery via Gamma-Ray Pulsations</title>
			<authors>Pletsch, H. J.; Guillemot, L.; Fehrmann, H.; Allen, B.; Kramer, M.; Aulbert, C.; Ackermann, M.; Ajello, M.; de Angelis, A.; Atwood, W. B.; Baldini, L.; Ballet, J.; Barbiellini, G.; Bastieri, D.; Bechtol, K.; Bellazzini, R.; Borgland, A. W.; Bottacini, E.; Brandt, T. J.; Bregeon, J.; Brigida, M.; Bruel, P.; Buehler, R.; Buson, S.; Caliandro, G. A.; Cameron, R. A.; Caraveo, P. A.; Casandjian, J. M.; Cecchi, C.; elik, .; Charles, E.; Chaves, R. C. G.; Cheung, C. C.; Chiang, J.; Ciprini, S.; Claus, R.; Cohen-Tanugi, J.; Conrad, J.; Cutini, S.; D'Ammando, F.; Dermer, C. D.; Digel, S. W.; Drell, P. S.; Drlica-Wagner, A.; Dubois, R.; Dumora, D.; Favuzzi, C.; Ferrara, E. C.; Franckowiak, A.; Fukazawa, Y.; Fusco, P.; Gargano, F.; Gehrels, N.; Germani, S.; Giglietto, N.; Giordano, F.; Giroletti, M.; Godfrey, G.; Grenier, I. A.; Grondin, M.-H.; Grove, J. E.; Guiriec, S.; Hadasch, D.; Hanabata, Y.; Harding, A. K.; den Hartog, P. R.; Hayashida, M.; Hays, E.; Hill, A. B.; Hou, X.; Hughes, R. E.; Jhannesson, G.; Jackson, M. S.; Jogler, T.; Johnson, A. S.; Johnson, W. N.; Kataoka, J.; Kerr, M.; Kn dlseder, J.; Kuss, M.; Lande, J.; Larsson, S.; Latronico, L.; Lemoine-Goumard, M.; Longo, F.; Loparco, F.; Lovellette, M. N.; Lubrano, P.; Massaro, F.; Mayer, M.; Mazziotta, M. N.; McEnery, J. E.; Mehault, J.; Michelson, P. F.; Mitthumsiri, W.; Mizuno, T.; Monzani, M. E.; Morselli, A.; Moskalenko, I. V.; Murgia, S.; Nakamori, T.; Nemmen, R.; Nuss, E.; Ohno, M.; Ohsugi, T.; Omodei, N.; Orienti, M.; Orlando, E.; de Palma, F.; Paneque, D.; Perkins, J. S.; Piron, F.; Pivato, G.; Porter, T. A.; Rain, S.; Rando, R.; Ray, P. S.; Razzano, M.; Reimer, A.; Reimer, O.; Reposeur, T.; Ritz, S.; Romani, R. W.; Romoli, C.; Sanchez, D. A.; Parkinson, P. M. Saz; Schulz, A.; Sgr, C.; do Couto e Silva, E.; Siskind, E. J.; Smith, D. A.; Spandre, G.; Spinelli, P.; Suson, D. J.; Takahashi, H.; Tanaka, T.; Thayer, J. B.; Thayer, J. G.; Thompson, D. J.; Tibaldo, L.; Tinivella, M.; Troja, E.; Usher, T. L.; Vandenbroucke, J.; Vasileiou, V.; Vianello, G.; Vitale, V.; Waite, A. P.; Winer, B. L.; Wood, K. S.; Wood, M.; Yang, Z.; Zimmer, S.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 338, Issue 6112, pp. 1314- (2012).</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Sci...338.1314P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012RAA....12..813H</bibcode>
			<title>The nature of the companion of PSR J1719-1438: a white dwarf or an exotic object?</title>
			<authors>Horvath, J. E.</authors>
			<journal>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 12, Issue 7, pp. 813-816 (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012RAA....12..813H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...753L..33B</bibcode>
			<title>Evolutionary Trajectories of Ultracompact "Black Widow" Pulsars with Very Low Mass Companions</title>
			<authors>Benvenuto, O. G.; De Vito, M. A.; Horvath, J. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 753, Issue 2, article id. L33, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;4&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...753L..33B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...543A.121V</bibcode>
			<title>Long-term luminosity behavior of 14 ultracompact X-ray binaries</title>
			<authors>van Haaften, L. M.; Voss, R.; Nelemans, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 543, id.A121, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...543A.121V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..22V</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of the planet around the millisecond pulsar J1719-1438</title>
			<authors>van Haaften, L. M.; Nelemans, G.; Voss, R.; Jonker, P. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A22, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..22V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.419.1752K</bibcode>
			<title>The High Time Resolution Universe Pulsar Survey - IV. Discovery and polarimetry of millisecond pulsars</title>
			<authors>Keith, M. J.; Johnston, S.; Bailes, M.; Bates, S. D.; Bhat, N. D. R.; Burgay, M.; Burke-Spolaor, S.; D'Amico, N.; Jameson, A.; Kramer, M.; Levin, L.; Milia, S.; Possenti, A.; Stappers, B. W.; van Straten, W.; Parent, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 419, Issue 2, pp. 1752-1765.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.419.1752K</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
