<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...551A.108M</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-site campaign for transit timing variations of WASP-12 b: possible detection of a long-period signal of planetary origin</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Seeliger, M.; Raetz, St.; Bukowiecki, L.; Kitze, M.; Errmann, R.; Nowak, G.; Niedzielski, A.; Popov, V.; Marka, C.; Gozdziewski, K.; Neuhuser, R.; Ohlert, J.; Hinse, T. C.; Lee, J. W.; Lee, C.-U.; Yoon, J.-N.; Berndt, A.; Gilbert, H.; Ginski, Ch.; Hohle, M. M.; Mugrauer, M.; Rll, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Tetzlaff, N.; Mancini, L.; Southworth, J.; Dall'Ora, M.; Ciceri, S.; Zambelli, R.; Corfini, G.; Takahashi, H.; Tachihara, K.; Benko , J. M.; Srneczky, K.; Szabo, Gy. M.; Varga, T. N.; Vanko, M.; Joshi, Y. C.; Chen, W. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 551, id.A108, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...551A.108M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...761..163D</bibcode>
			<title>The Photoeccentric Effect and Proto-hot Jupiters. II. KOI-1474.01, a Candidate Eccentric Planet Perturbed by an Unseen Companion</title>
			<authors>Dawson, Rebekah I.; Johnson, John Asher; Morton, Timothy D.; Crepp, Justin R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Howard, Andrew W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 761, Issue 2, article id. 163, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...761..163D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750...84B</bibcode>
			<title>Qatar-2: A K Dwarf Orbited by a Transiting Hot Jupiter and a More Massive Companion in an Outer Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bryan, Marta L.; Alsubai, Khalid A.; Latham, David W.; Parley, Neil R.; Collier Cameron, Andrew; Quinn, Samuel N.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fulton, Benjamin J.; Berlind, Perry; Brown, Warren R.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Calkins, Michael L.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Fursz, Gbor; Gre Jrgensen, Uffe; Horne, Keith D.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Street, Rachel A.; Torres, Guillermo; West, Richard G.; Dominik, Martin; Harpse, Kennet B. W.; Liebig, Christine; Calchi Novati, Sebastiano; Ricci, Davide; Skottfelt, Jesper F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 1, article id. 84, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750...84B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
