<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...555A..92V</bibcode>
			<title>Qatar-1: indications for possible transit timing variations</title>
			<authors>von Essen, C.; Schrter, S.; Agol, E.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 555, id.A92, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;12&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...555A..92V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...554A..28C</bibcode>
			<title>The GAPS programme with HARPS-N at TNG. I. Observations of the Rossiter-McLaughlin effect and characterisation of the transiting system Qatar-1</title>
			<authors>Covino, E.; Esposito, M.; Barbieri, M.; Mancini, L.; Nascimbeni, V.; Claudi, R.; Desidera, S.; Gratton, R.; Lanza, A. F.; Sozzetti, A.; Biazzo, K.; Affer, L.; Gandolfi, D.; Munari, U.; Pagano, I.; Bonomo, A. S.; Collier Cameron, A.; H brard, G.; Maggio, A.; Messina, S.; Micela, G.; Molinari, E.; Pepe, F.; Piotto, G.; Ribas, I.; Santos, N. C.; Southworth, J.; Shkolnik, E.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Bedin, L.; Benatti, S.; Boccato, C.; Bonavita, M.; Borsa, F.; Borsato, L.; Brown, D.; Carolo, E.; Ciceri, S.; Cosentino, R.; Damasso, M.; Faedi, F.; Mart nez Fiorenzano, A. F.; Latham, D. W.; Lovis, C.; Mordasini, C.; Nikolov, N.; Poretti, E.; Rainer, M.; Rebolo Lpez, R.; Scandariato, G.; Silvotti, R.; Smareglia, R.; Alcal , J. M.; Cunial, A.; Di Fabrizio, L.; Di Mauro, M. P.; Giacobbe, P.; Granata, V.; Harutyunyan, A.; Knapic, C.; Lattanzi, M.; Leto, G.; Lodato, G.; Malavolta, L.; Marzari, F.; Molinaro, M.; Nardiello, D.; Pedani, M.; Prisinzano, L.; Turrini, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 554, id.A28, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>6/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...554A..28C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.426.1291S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - V. New results for 38 planets</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 426, Issue 2, pp. 1291-1323.</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.426.1291S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012PASP..124..212S</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planet Transits Observed at Kitt Peak National Observatory</title>
			<authors>Sada, Pedro V.; Deming, Drake; Jennings, Donald E.; Jackson, Brian K.; Hamilton, Catrina M.; Fraine, Jonathan; Peterson, Steven W.; Haase, Flynn; Bays, Kevin; Lunsford, Allen; O'Gorman, Eamon</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 124, issue 913, pp.212-229</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012PASP..124..212S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417..709A</bibcode>
			<title>Qatar-1b: a hot Jupiter orbiting a metal-rich K dwarf star</title>
			<authors>Alsubai, K. A.; Parley, N. R.; Bramich, D. M.; West, R. G.; Sorensen, P. M.; Collier Cameron, A.; Latham, D. W.; Horne, K.; Anderson, D. R.; Bakos, G. .; Brown, D. J. A.; Buchhave, L. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M. E.; Fzr sz, G.; Hartman, J. D.; Hellier, C.; Miller, G. M.; Pollacco, D.; Quinn, S. N.; Smith, J. C.; Stefanik, R. P.; Szentgyorgyi, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 1, pp. 709-716.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417..709A</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
