<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...767L..24D</bibcode>
			<title>Giant Planets Orbiting Metal-rich Stars Show Signatures of Planet-Planet Interactions</title>
			<authors>Dawson, Rebekah I.; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 767, Issue 2, article id. L24, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...767L..24D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764...18L</bibcode>
			<title>Pulsation Frequencies and Modes of Giant Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Le Bihan, Bastien; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. 18, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764...18L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.426..739H</bibcode>
			<title>Seven transiting hot Jupiters from WASP-South, Euler and TRAPPIST: WASP-47b, WASP-55b, WASP-61b, WASP-62b, WASP-63b, WASP-66b and WASP-67b</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Fumel, A.; Gillon, M.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 426, Issue 1, pp. 739-750.</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.426..739H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.426..739H</bibcode>
			<title>Seven transiting hot Jupiters from WASP-South, Euler and TRAPPIST: WASP-47b, WASP-55b, WASP-61b, WASP-62b, WASP-63b, WASP-66b and WASP-67b</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Fumel, A.; Gillon, M.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 426, Issue 1, pp. 739-750.</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.426..739H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..187S</bibcode>
			<title>The RAdial Velocity Experiment (RAVE): Third Data Release</title>
			<authors>Siebert, A.; Williams, M. E. K.; Siviero, A.; Reid, W.; Boeche, C.; Steinmetz, M.; Fulbright, J.; Munari, U.; Zwitter, T.; Watson, F. G.; Wyse, R. F. G.; de Jong, R. S.; Enke, H.; Anguiano, B.; Burton, D.; Cass, C. J. P.; Fiegert, K.; Hartley, M.; Ritter, A.; Russel, K. S.; Stupar, M.; Bienaym, O.; Freeman, K. C.; Gilmore, G.; Grebel, E. K.; Helmi, A.; Navarro, J. F.; Binney, J.; Bland-Hawthorn, J.; Campbell, R.; Famaey, B.; Gerhard, O.; Gibson, B. K.; Matijevic, G.; Parker, Q. A.; Seabroke, G. M.; Sharma, S.; Smith, M. C.; Wylie-de Boer, E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 6, article id. 187 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..187S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
