<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764...18L</bibcode>
			<title>Pulsation Frequencies and Modes of Giant Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Le Bihan, Bastien; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. 18, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764...18L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...549A.134H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-52b, WASP-58b, WASP-59b, and WASP-60b: Four new transiting close-in giant planets</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Collier Cameron, A.; Brown, D. J. A.; Daz, R. F.; Faedi, F.; Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Armstrong, D.; Barros, S. C. C.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Doyle, A. P.; Enoch, B.; Gmez Maqueo Chew, Y.; Hbrard, . M.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Moutou, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Skillen, I.; Southworth, J.; Tregloan-Reed, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; Vanhuysse, M.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 549, id.A134, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...549A.134H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...771...11A</bibcode>
			<title>Low Stellar Obliquities in Compact Multiplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Albrecht, Simon; Winn, Joshua N.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 771, Issue 1, article id. 11, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...771...11A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...551A..73F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-54b, WASP-56b, and WASP-57b: Three new sub-Jupiter mass planets from SuperWASP</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Pollacco, D.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D.; Collier Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Enoch, R.; Gillon, M.; Gmez Maqueo Chew, Y.; Hbrard, G.; Lendl, M.; Liebig, C.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.; Alsubai, K. A.; Anderson, D. R.; Armstrong, D.; Bento, J.; Bochinski, J.; Bouchy, F.; Busuttil, R.; Fossati, L.; Fumel, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Jehin, E.; Kolb, U.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 551, id.A73, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;17&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...551A..73F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...549A.134H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-52b, WASP-58b, WASP-59b, and WASP-60b: Four new transiting close-in giant planets</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Collier Cameron, A.; Brown, D. J. A.; Daz, R. F.; Faedi, F.; Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Armstrong, D.; Barros, S. C. C.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Doyle, A. P.; Enoch, B.; Gmez Maqueo Chew, Y.; Hbrard, . M.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Moutou, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Skillen, I.; Southworth, J.; Tregloan-Reed, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; Vanhuysse, M.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 549, id.A134, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...549A.134H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
