<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...552A..82G</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-64 b and WASP-72 b: two new transiting highly irradiated giant planets</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Fumel, A.; Hellier, C.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Montalbn, J.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Smalley, B.; Southworth, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 552, id.A82, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...552A..82G</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...552A..82G</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-64 b and WASP-72 b: two new transiting highly irradiated giant planets</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Fumel, A.; Hellier, C.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Montalbn, J.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Smalley, B.; Southworth, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 552, id.A82, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;13&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...552A..82G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..193B</bibcode>
			<title>The RAVE Catalog of Stellar Elemental Abundances: First Data Release</title>
			<authors>Boeche, C.; Siebert, A.; Williams, M.; de Jong, R. S.; Steinmetz, M.; Fulbright, J. P.; Ruchti, G. R.; Bienaym, O.; Bland-Hawthorn, J.; Campbell, R.; Freeman, K. C.; Gibson, B. K.; Gilmore, G.; Grebel, E. K.; Helmi, A.; Munari, U.; Navarro, J. F.; Parker, Q. A.; Reid, W.; Seabroke, G. M.; Siviero, A.; Watson, F. G.; Wyse, R. F. G.; Zwitter, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 6, article id. 193, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..193B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..187S</bibcode>
			<title>The RAdial Velocity Experiment (RAVE): Third Data Release</title>
			<authors>Siebert, A.; Williams, M. E. K.; Siviero, A.; Reid, W.; Boeche, C.; Steinmetz, M.; Fulbright, J.; Munari, U.; Zwitter, T.; Watson, F. G.; Wyse, R. F. G.; de Jong, R. S.; Enke, H.; Anguiano, B.; Burton, D.; Cass, C. J. P.; Fiegert, K.; Hartley, M.; Ritter, A.; Russel, K. S.; Stupar, M.; Bienaym, O.; Freeman, K. C.; Gilmore, G.; Grebel, E. K.; Helmi, A.; Navarro, J. F.; Binney, J.; Bland-Hawthorn, J.; Campbell, R.; Famaey, B.; Gerhard, O.; Gibson, B. K.; Matijevic, G.; Parker, Q. A.; Seabroke, G. M.; Sharma, S.; Smith, M. C.; Wylie-de Boer, E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 6, article id. 187 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..187S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
