<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...766....9S</bibcode>
			<title>An Ultraviolet Investigation of Activity on Exoplanet Host Stars</title>
			<authors>Shkolnik, Evgenya L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 766, Issue 1, article id. 9, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...766....9S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764...18L</bibcode>
			<title>Pulsation Frequencies and Modes of Giant Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Le Bihan, Bastien; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. 18, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764...18L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...549A.134H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-52b, WASP-58b, WASP-59b, and WASP-60b: Four new transiting close-in giant planets</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Collier Cameron, A.; Brown, D. J. A.; Daz, R. F.; Faedi, F.; Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Armstrong, D.; Barros, S. C. C.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Doyle, A. P.; Enoch, B.; Gmez Maqueo Chew, Y.; Hbrard, . M.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Moutou, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Skillen, I.; Southworth, J.; Tregloan-Reed, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; Vanhuysse, M.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 549, id.A134, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...549A.134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...760..139B</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of Spin-Orbit Alignment in the WASP-32, WASP-38, and HAT-P-27/WASP-40 Systems</title>
			<authors>Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Daz, R. F.; Doyle, A. P.; Gillon, M.; Lendl, M.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Anderson, D. R.; Enoch, B.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Miller, G. R. M.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Boisse, I.; H brard, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 760, Issue 2, article id. 139, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...760..139B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757...18A</bibcode>
			<title>Obliquities of Hot Jupiter Host Stars: Evidence for Tidal Interactions and Primordial Misalignments</title>
			<authors>Albrecht, Simon; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Arriagada, Pamela; Crane, Jeffrey D.; Shectman, Stephen A.; Thompson, Ian B.; Hirano, Teruyuki; Bakos, Gaspar; Hartman, Joel D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 1, article id. 18 (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757...18A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757....6H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems. II</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 1, article id. 6, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;21&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757....6H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...96P</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Tidal Dissipation in Stars from the Destruction Rates of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Penev, Kaloyan; Jackson, Brian; Spada, Federico; Thom, Nicole</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. 96, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751...96P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.3023S</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angles of the transiting exoplanets WASP-1b, WASP-24b, WASP-38b and HAT-P-8b from Rossiter-McLaughlin observations</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Pollacco, D.; Cameron, A. Collier; Hbrard, G.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Faedi, F.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; Sorensen, P.; Stempels, H. C.; Triaud, A.; Watson, C. A.; Wilson, P. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 4, pp. 3023-3035.</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.3023S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..40F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-39b: a highly inflated Saturn-mass planet orbiting a late G-type star</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Anderson, D. R.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Boisse, I.; Hbrard, G.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A40, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..40F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;10&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..54B</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-38b: a transiting exoplanet in an eccentric, 6.87d period orbit</title>
			<authors>Barros, S. C. C.; Faedi, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Lister, T. A.; McCormac, J.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Hbrard, G.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Bento, J.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Skillen, I.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A54, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..54B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...771...11A</bibcode>
			<title>Low Stellar Obliquities in Compact Multiplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Albrecht, Simon; Winn, Joshua N.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 771, Issue 1, article id. 11, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>7/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...771...11A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...760..139B</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of Spin-Orbit Alignment in the WASP-32, WASP-38, and HAT-P-27/WASP-40 Systems</title>
			<authors>Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Daz, R. F.; Doyle, A. P.; Gillon, M.; Lendl, M.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Anderson, D. R.; Enoch, B.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Miller, G. R. M.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Boisse, I.; H brard, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 760, Issue 2, article id. 139, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>12/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...760..139B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757..161T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Spectroscopic Parameters for Transiting Planet Hosts</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Fischer, Debra A.; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Buchhave, Lars A.; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 2, article id. 161, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;14&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757..161T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.423.1503B</bibcode>
			<title>Rossiter-McLaughlin effect measurements for WASP-16, WASP-25 and WASP-31</title>
			<authors>Brown, D. J. A.; Cameron, A. Collier; Anderson, D. R.; Enoch, B.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Miller, G. R. M.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Simpson, E.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Gillon, M.; Hbrard, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 423, Issue 2, pp. 1503-1520.</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.423.1503B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.3151H</bibcode>
			<title>Observational constraints on tidal effects using orbital eccentricities</title>
			<authors>Husnoo, Nawal; Pont, Frdric; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel; Hbrard, Guillaume; Bouchy, Franois; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 4, pp. 3151-3177.</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.3151H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A.116D</bibcode>
			<title>Prospecting transit duration variations in extrasolar planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Damiani, C.; Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A116, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A.116D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534L...6T</bibcode>
			<title>The time dependence of hot Jupiters' orbital inclinations</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.L6, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;5&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534L...6T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.3023S</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angles of the transiting exoplanets WASP-1b, WASP-24b, WASP-38b and HAT-P-8b from Rossiter-McLaughlin observations</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Pollacco, D.; Cameron, A. Collier; Hbrard, G.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Faedi, F.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; Sorensen, P.; Stempels, H. C.; Triaud, A.; Watson, C. A.; Wilson, P. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 4, pp. 3023-3035.</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.3023S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>The retrograde orbit of the HAT-P-6b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Moutou, C.; Arnold, L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; Daz, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.L11, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;4&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..54B</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-38b: a transiting exoplanet in an eccentric, 6.87d period orbit</title>
			<authors>Barros, S. C. C.; Faedi, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Lister, T. A.; McCormac, J.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Hbrard, G.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Bento, J.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Skillen, I.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A54, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..54B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
