<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...766....9S</bibcode>
			<title>An Ultraviolet Investigation of Activity on Exoplanet Host Stars</title>
			<authors>Shkolnik, Evgenya L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 766, Issue 1, article id. 9, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...766....9S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764...18L</bibcode>
			<title>Pulsation Frequencies and Modes of Giant Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Le Bihan, Bastien; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. 18, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764...18L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...549A.134H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-52b, WASP-58b, WASP-59b, and WASP-60b: Four new transiting close-in giant planets</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Collier Cameron, A.; Brown, D. J. A.; Daz, R. F.; Faedi, F.; Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Armstrong, D.; Barros, S. C. C.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Doyle, A. P.; Enoch, B.; Gmez Maqueo Chew, Y.; Hbrard, . M.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Moutou, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Skillen, I.; Southworth, J.; Tregloan-Reed, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; Vanhuysse, M.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 549, id.A134, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>1/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...549A.134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757....6H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems. II</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 1, article id. 6, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;21&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757....6H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.2024J</bibcode>
			<title>The coronal X-ray-age relation and its implications for the evaporation of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Alan P.; Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 3, pp. 2024-2043.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.2024J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;11&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AstL...38..180S</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of extrasolar planet transits with the automated telescopes of the Pulkovo Astronomical Observatory</title>
			<authors>Sokov, E. N.; Vereshchagina, I. A.; Gnedin, Yu. N.; Devyatkin, A. V.; Gorshanov, D. L.; Slesarenko, V. Yu.; Ivanov, A. V.; Naumov, K. N.; Zinov'ev, S. V.; Bekhteva, A. S.; Romas, E. S.; Karashevich, S. V.; Kupriyanov, V. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Volume 38, Issue 3, pp.180-190</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AstL...38..180S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...86E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-35b, WASP-48b, and HAT-P-30b/WASP-51b: Two New Planets and an Independent Discovery of a Hat Planet</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Faedi, F.; Gillon, M.; Hbrard, G.; Lister, T. A.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bouchy, F.; Bento, J.; Butters, O.; Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 3, article id. 86, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...86E</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.426.1338S</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision photometry by telescope defocusing - IV. Confirmation of the huge radius of WASP-17 b</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Dominik, M.; Fang, X.-S.; Harpse, K.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kerins, E.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Skottfelt, J.; Anderson, D. R.; Smalley, B.; Tregloan-Reed, J.; Wertz, O.; Alsubai, K. A.; Bozza, V.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dreizler, S.; Gu, S.-H.; Hundertmark, M.; Jessen-Hansen, J.; Kains, N.; Kjeldsen, H.; Lund, M. N.; Lundkvist, M.; Mathiasen, M.; Penny, M. T.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 426, Issue 2, pp. 1338-1348.</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.426.1338S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012PASP..124..212S</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planet Transits Observed at Kitt Peak National Observatory</title>
			<authors>Sada, Pedro V.; Deming, Drake; Jennings, Donald E.; Jackson, Brian K.; Hamilton, Catrina M.; Fraine, Jonathan; Peterson, Steven W.; Haase, Flynn; Bays, Kevin; Lunsford, Allen; O'Gorman, Eamon</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 124, issue 913, pp.212-229</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012PASP..124..212S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...86E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-35b, WASP-48b, and HAT-P-30b/WASP-51b: Two New Planets and an Independent Discovery of a Hat Planet</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Faedi, F.; Gillon, M.; Hbrard, G.; Lister, T. A.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bouchy, F.; Bento, J.; Butters, O.; Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 3, article id. 86, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...86E</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
