<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...552A.119S</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic energy fluxes in sub-Alfvnic planet star and moon planet interactions</title>
			<authors>Saur, J.; Grambusch, T.; Duling, S.; Neubauer, F. M.; Simon, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 552, id.A119, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>4/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...552A.119S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764...18L</bibcode>
			<title>Pulsation Frequencies and Modes of Giant Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Le Bihan, Bastien; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. 18, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;20&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764...18L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...547A..61S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-78b and WASP-79b: two highly-bloated hot Jupiter-mass exoplanets orbiting F-type stars in Eridanus</title>
			<authors>Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Fumel, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, , C.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 547, id.A61, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>11/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...547A..61S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.426..739H</bibcode>
			<title>Seven transiting hot Jupiters from WASP-South, Euler and TRAPPIST: WASP-47b, WASP-55b, WASP-61b, WASP-62b, WASP-63b, WASP-66b and WASP-67b</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Fumel, A.; Gillon, M.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 426, Issue 1, pp. 739-750.</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.426..739H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013A&amp;A...551A..73F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-54b, WASP-56b, and WASP-57b: Three new sub-Jupiter mass planets from SuperWASP</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Pollacco, D.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D.; Collier Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Enoch, R.; Gillon, M.; Gmez Maqueo Chew, Y.; Hbrard, G.; Lendl, M.; Liebig, C.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.; Alsubai, K. A.; Anderson, D. R.; Armstrong, D.; Bento, J.; Bochinski, J.; Bouchy, F.; Busuttil, R.; Fossati, L.; Fumel, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Jehin, E.; Kolb, U.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 551, id.A73, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;17&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>3/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013A%26A...551A..73F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...547A..61S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-78b and WASP-79b: two highly-bloated hot Jupiter-mass exoplanets orbiting F-type stars in Eridanus</title>
			<authors>Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Doyle, A. P.; Fumel, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, , C.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 547, id.A61, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>11/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...547A..61S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.426.1338S</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision photometry by telescope defocusing - IV. Confirmation of the huge radius of WASP-17 b</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Dominik, M.; Fang, X.-S.; Harpse, K.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kerins, E.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Skottfelt, J.; Anderson, D. R.; Smalley, B.; Tregloan-Reed, J.; Wertz, O.; Alsubai, K. A.; Bozza, V.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dreizler, S.; Gu, S.-H.; Hundertmark, M.; Jessen-Hansen, J.; Kains, N.; Kjeldsen, H.; Lund, M. N.; Lundkvist, M.; Mathiasen, M.; Penny, M. T.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 426, Issue 2, pp. 1338-1348.</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.426.1338S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
