<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2013ApJ...764..101B</bibcode>
			<title>The Coldest Brown Dwarf (or Free-floating Planet)?: The Y Dwarf WISE 1828+2650</title>
			<authors>Beichman, C.; Gelino, Christopher R.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Barman, Travis S.; Marsh, Kenneth A.; Cushing, Michael C.; Wright, E. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 764, Issue 1, article id. 101, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;16&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2013).</journal>
			<date>2/2013</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2013ApJ...764..101B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...758...57L</bibcode>
			<title>Two Extraordinary Substellar Binaries at the T/Y Transition and the Y-band Fluxes of the Coolest Brown Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Liu, Michael C.; Dupuy, Trent J.; Bowler, Brendan P.; Leggett, S. K.; Best, William M. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 758, Issue 1, article id. 57, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;15&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>10/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...758...57L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757..100D</bibcode>
			<title>LHS 2803B: A Very Wide Mid-T Dwarf Companion to an Old M Dwarf Identified from Pan-STARRS1</title>
			<authors>Deacon, Niall R.; Liu, Michael C.; Magnier, Eugene A.; Bowler, Brendan P.; Mann, Andrew W.; Redstone, Joshua A.; Burgett, William S.; Chambers, Ken C.; Hodapp, Klaus W.; Kaiser, Nick; Kudritzki, Rolf-Peter; Morgan, Jeff S.; Price, Paul A.; Tonry, John L.; Wainscoat, Richard J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 1, article id. 100, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;7&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757..100D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...757....7M</bibcode>
			<title>WISE Detections of Dust in the Habitable Zones of Planet-bearing Stars</title>
			<authors>Morales, Farisa Y.; Padgett, D. L.; Bryden, G.; Werner, M. W.; Furlan, E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 757, Issue 1, article id. 7, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;6&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...757....7M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...755...94D</bibcode>
			<title>HIP 38939B: A New Benchmark T Dwarf in the Galactic Plane Discovered with Pan-STARRS1</title>
			<authors>Deacon, Niall R.; Liu, Michael C.; Magnier, Eugene A.; Bowler, Brendan P.; Redstone, Joshua; Goldman, Bertrand; Burgett, W. S.; Chambers, K. C.; Flewelling, H.; Kaiser, N.; Morgan, J. S.; Price, P. A.; Sweeney, W. E.; Tonry, J. L.; Wainscoat, R. J.; Waters, C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 755, Issue 2, article id. 94, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;9&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...755...94D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...753..156K</bibcode>
			<title>Further Defining Spectral Type "Y" and Exploring the Low-mass End of the Field Brown Dwarf Mass Function</title>
			<authors>Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Gelino, Christopher R.; Cushing, Michael C.; Mace, Gregory N.; Griffith, Roger L.; Skrutskie, Michael F.; Marsh, Kenneth A.; Wright, Edward L.; Eisenhardt, Peter R.; McLean, Ian S.; Mainzer, Amanda K.; Burgasser, Adam J.; Tinney, C. G.; Parker, Stephen; Salter, Graeme</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 753, Issue 2, article id. 156, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;38&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...753..156K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...26B</bibcode>
			<title>Resolved Spectroscopy of a Brown Dwarf Binary at the T Dwarf/Y Dwarf Transition</title>
			<authors>Burgasser, Adam J.; Gelino, Christopher R.; Cushing, Michael C.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 26, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...26B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..135L</bibcode>
			<title>Confirmation of One of the Coldest Known Brown Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Luhman, K. L.; Burgasser, A. J.; Labb, I.; Saumon, D.; Marley, M. S.; Bochanski, J. J.; Monson, A. J.; Persson, S. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 135, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;8&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..135L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...19K</bibcode>
			<title>The First Hundred Brown Dwarfs Discovered by the Wide-field Infrared Survey Explorer (WISE)</title>
			<authors>Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Cushing, Michael C.; Gelino, Christopher R.; Griffith, Roger L.; Skrutskie, Michael F.; Marsh, Kenneth A.; Wright, Edward L.; Mainzer, A.; Eisenhardt, Peter R.; McLean, Ian S.; Thompson, Maggie A.; Bauer, James M.; Benford, Dominic J.; Bridge, Carrie R.; Lake, Sean E.; Petty, Sara M.; Stanford, S. A.; Tsai, Chao-Wei; Bailey, Vanessa; Beichman, Charles A.; Bloom, Joshua S.; Bochanski, John J.; Burgasser, Adam J.; Capak, Peter L.; Cruz, Kelle L.; Hinz, Philip M.; Kartaltepe, Jeyhan S.; Knox, Russell P.; Manohar, Swarnima; Masters, Daniel; Morales-Caldern, Maria; Prato, Lisa A.; Rodigas, Timothy J.; Salvato, Mara; Schurr, Steven D.; Scoville, Nicholas Z.; Simcoe, Robert A.; Stapelfeldt, Karl R.; Stern, Daniel; Stock, Nathan D.; Vacca, William D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 2, article id. 19, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;55&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.  (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...19K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...50C</bibcode>
			<title>The Discovery of Y Dwarfs using Data from the Wide-field Infrared Survey Explorer (WISE)</title>
			<authors>Cushing, Michael C.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Gelino, Christopher R.; Griffith, Roger L.; Skrutskie, Michael F.; Mainzer, A.; Marsh, Kenneth A.; Beichman, Charles A.; Burgasser, Adam J.; Prato, Lisa A.; Simcoe, Robert A.; Marley, Mark S.; Saumon, D.; Freedman, Richard S.; Eisenhardt, Peter R.; Wright, Edward L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 50, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;17&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...50C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2104V</bibcode>
			<title>The great escape: how exoplanets and smaller bodies desert dying stars</title>
			<authors>Veras, Dimitri; Wyatt, Mark C.; Mustill, Alexander J.; Bonsor, Amy; Eldridge, John J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2104-2123.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2104V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532L...5S</bibcode>
			<title>Two very nearby (d ~ 5 pc) ultracool brown dwarfs detected by their large proper motions from WISE, 2MASS, and SDSS data</title>
			<authors>Scholz, R.-D.; Bihain, G.; Schnurr, O.; Storm, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.L5, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;4&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532L...5S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..29R</bibcode>
			<title>The Ultra Cool Brown Dwarf Companion of WD 0806-661B: Age, Mass, and Formation Mechanism</title>
			<authors>Rodriguez, David R.; Zuckerman, B.; Melis, Carl; Song, Inseok</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L29, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;4&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..29R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Candidate for the Coolest Known Brown Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Luhman, K. L.; Burgasser, A. J.; Bochanski, J. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. L9, &lt;NUMPAGES&gt;4&lt;/NUMPAGES&gt; pp. (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730L...9L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
