<planet>
	<id_exoplaneteu>Gliese 667 C f</id_exoplaneteu>
	<name>Gliese 667 C f</name>
	<name>GJ 667C f</name>
	<name>HR 6426C f</name>
	<id>Gliese 667 C f</id>
	<discoverymethod>RV</discoverymethod>
	<properties>
		<mass>0.008493</mass>
		<radius />
		<orbit>
			<period>39.026</period>
			<semimajoraxis>0.156</semimajoraxis>
			<eccentricity>0.03</eccentricity>
			<inclination />
			<periastron>103.132403</periastron>
			<longitude>34</longitude>
			<ascendingnode />
		</orbit>
	</properties>
	<star>
		<spectraltype />
		<mass>0.73</mass>
		<radius>0.76</radius>
		<metallicity>-0.59</metallicity>
		<distance>6.97</distance>
		<temperature />
		<rightascension>17 18 57</rightascension>
		<declination>-34 59 23</declination>
		<angulardistance />
		<magV>10.22</magV>
		<magI />
		<magH />
		<magJ />
		<magK />
	</star>
	<multiplicity>7</multiplicity>
	<discoveryyear>2013</discoveryyear>
	<lastupdate>13/06/25</lastupdate>
	<description>Gliese 667 is a nearby triple star system in the constellation Scorpius, about 22 light years away. The star Gliese 667 C hosts at least six planets. Three of them, all Super-Earths, are located in the habitable zone. The habitable zone is so densely packed that any additional planet is likely to destabilize the system. This planet, Gliese 667 C f, is right in the middle of the habitable zone.</description>
	<new />
	<image>Gliese667</image>
	<imagedescription>This artist's impression shows the view from the exoplanet Gliese 667C d looking towards the planet's parent star (Gliese 667 C). In the background to the right the more distant stars in this triple system (Gliese 667 A and Gliese 667 B) are visible and to the left in the sky one of the other planets, the newly discovered Gliese 667 Ce, can be seen as a crescent. A record-breaking three planets in this system are super-Earths lying in the zone around the star where liquid water could exist, making them possible candidates for the presence of life. This is the first system found with a fully packed habitable zone.

	Credit: ESO/M. Kornmesser</imagedescription>
	<list>Confirmed planets</list>
</planet>
